[
{
        "answer": "13.0 and 49.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 424731,
        "question": "The difference between two numbers is 36 . The sum of these numbers is 62 . Find the numbers .",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 36 (Minus _smt1 _smt0)) (Equals 62 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "test"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "12.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 243085,
        "question": "A number added to 6 is equal to 30 less than four times the number . what is the number .",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 _smt0) (Equals (Plus _smt0 6) (Minus (Times 4 _smt0) 30)))",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "train"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "5.0 and -3.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 669386,
        "question": "The sum of two numbers is 2 . If the larger number is 14 more than three times the smaller , find the larger number .",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "train"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "36.0 and 45.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 748694,
        "question": "the sum of two numbers is 81 the differance of the same two numbers is 9 . What are the two numbers ?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "train"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "4.25 and 12.75",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 349390,
        "question": "The sum of two number is 17 . The second number is three times as much as the first number . What are the two numbers ?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "train"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "21.0 and 26.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 223977,
        "question": "Two numbers have a sum of 47 their difference is 5 . what are the two numbers ?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "train"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "78.0 and 62.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 414889,
        "question": "the sum of two numbers is 140 and their difference is 16 . find the numbers",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 140 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals 16 (Minus _smt1 _smt0)) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "test"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "18.0 and 7.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 240645,
        "question": "One number is 4 more than twice the second number . Their total is 25 . Find the numbers .",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "train"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "24.0 and 8.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 220494,
        "question": "The difference between two numbers is 16 . Three times the larger number is 9 times the smaller . What are the numbers ?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 16 (Minus _smt1 _smt0)) (Equals (Times 9 _smt0) (Times 3 _smt1)) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "train"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "45.0 and 62.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 889960,
        "question": "if the sum of 2 numbers is 107 and the difference is 17 find the number",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "train"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "7.0 and 2.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 136036,
        "question": "a number is 8 times the sum of its digits . the tens digits is 5 greater than the units digit . find the number .",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "dev"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "4.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 354468,
        "question": "HOW MANY LITERS OF A 20 % SALT SOLUTION MUST BE ADDED TO 8 LITERS OF A 5 % SALT SOLUTION TO YIELD AN ALLOY THAT IS A 10 % SALT SOLUTION ?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "test"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "7.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 361062,
        "question": "14 less than three times a number is equal to the number . What is the number ?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 _smt0) (Equals (Minus (Times 3 _smt0) 14) _smt0))",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "train"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "24.0000960004 and 31.9999039996",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 625848,
        "question": "the sum of two numbers is 56 . One-third of the first number plus one-fourth of the second number is 16 . find the numbers .",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus (Div (Times 1 _smt0) 3) (Div (Times 1 _smt1) 4)) 16) (Equals 56 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "test"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-2.0 and 2.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 165256,
        "question": "One number is four more than a second number . Two times the first number is 12 more than four times the second number .",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "train"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "2.0 and 1.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 353419,
        "question": "The sum of three times a first number and twice a second number is 8 . If the second number is subtracted from twice the first number , the result if 3 . Find the numbers .",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "dev"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "21.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 547664,
        "question": "nineteen more than four times a number is equal to the difference between 166 and three times the number . find the number ?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 _smt0) (Equals (Plus 19 (Times 4 _smt0)) (Difference (Elements 166 (Times 3 _smt0)))))",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "dev"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "9.0 and 4.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 243375,
        "question": "the greater of two numbers is 5 more than the smaller . if the smaller is added to twice the greater , the result is 22 . find both of the numbers .",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "test"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "6.0 and 19.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 444464,
        "question": "the sum of two numbers is 25 . One number is twice the second plus seven . What are the two numbers",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "train"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "2.0 and 16.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 857277,
        "question": "The sum of two numbers is 18 . The sum of 3 times the smaller number and 4 times the larger number is 56 . What are the numbers ?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "dev"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "8.0 and 10.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 351469,
        "question": "one number is two more than a second number , twice the first is four less than three times the second .",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "train"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "6.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 812830,
        "question": "eight less than three times a number is equal to the sum of the number and four . What is the number",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 _smt0) (Equals (Minus (Times 3 _smt0) 8) (Plus _smt0 4)))",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "test"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "140.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 46941,
        "question": "When 80 % of a number is added to the number , the result is 252 . What is the number ?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 252 (Plus (Div (Times 80 _smt0) 100) _smt0)) (Equals ?_x1 _smt0))",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "dev"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "11.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 513639,
        "question": "a number when multiplied by 4 is 33 more than itself . Find the number .",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "train"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "15.5 and 27.5",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 251790,
        "question": "The sum of two numbers is 43 . The difference of the same two numbers is 12 . What are the two numbers ?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "dev"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "13.0 and 54.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 804723,
        "question": "The larger of two numbers is 2 more than 4 times the smaller . Their sum is 67 . FIND THE numbers",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Max (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Plus 2 (Times 4 _smt0))) (Equals 67 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "dev"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "22.25 and 57.75",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 360099,
        "question": "The sum of two numbers is 80 . The larger number is nine less than three times the smaller . Find both numbers .",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 80 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals _smt1 (Minus (Times 3 _smt0) 9)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "test"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "150.0 and 105.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 230975,
        "question": "Two integers have a sum of 255 . The difference of the two numbers is 45 . What are the two numbers .",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "test"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "44.0 and 23.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 840960,
        "question": "Two numbers have a sum of 67 . The smaller number is 21 less than the larger number . Find the two numbers .",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "test"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "49.0 and 26.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 657718,
        "question": "The sum of two numbers is 75 . The second number is 3 less than twice the first . Find the two numbers .",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "test"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "45.0 and 8.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 267386,
        "question": "The difference of two numbers is 37 . The larger number is three less than six times the smaller number .",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "train"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-16.0 and -26.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 550023,
        "question": "the difference between two numbers is 10 . When eight times the smaller number is added to 40 , the result is ten less than three times the larger number . find the numbers .",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "dev"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "29.0 and 16.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 632980,
        "question": "The sum of two numbers is 45 . Twice the smaller number is three more the larger number . What is the product of the two numbers ?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "test"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "46.0 and 34.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 347438,
        "question": "the sum of two numbers is 80 their difference is 12 . what are the numbers",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "dev"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "8.0 and 10.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 234098,
        "question": "The sum of two numbers equals eighteen . The total of three times the smaller and two times the larger is 44 .",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "train"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "47.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 209845,
        "question": "the difference of twice a number and five is 89 . find the number .",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Difference (Elements (Times 2 _smt0) 5)) 89) (Equals ?_x1 _smt0))",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "dev"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "3.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 626669,
        "question": "if 5 is added to a number and the sum is tripled , the result is 21 more than the number . Find the number .",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "train"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "20.0 and 28.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 185005,
        "question": "The sum of two numbers is 48 . Three times the smaller number is the same as 32 more than the larger . Find the two numbers .",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "train"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "29.0 and 25.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 926067,
        "question": "Find the value of two numbers if their sum is 54 and the difference is 4 .",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "train"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "110.0 and 22.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 296468,
        "question": "THE DIFFERENCE OF TWO NUMBERS IS 88 . THE SECOND NUMBER IS 20 % OF THE FIRST NUMBER . WHAT ARE THE NUMBERS ?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 88 (Difference (Elements _smt0 _smt1))) (Equals (Times 20 _smt0) (Times 100 _smt1)) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "dev"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "20.0 and 13.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 57740,
        "question": "The sum of two numbers is 33 . Their differeence is 7 . What are the two numbers .",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "train"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-4.0 and 9.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 514217,
        "question": "the sum of two integers is 5 . their difference is 13 . find the two integers",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "train"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "23.0 and 16.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 103718,
        "question": "The sum of Two numbers is 39 . Twice the first number and plus 3 times the second number is 101 . What are the numbers ?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "train"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "12.0 and 27.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 802678,
        "question": "the sum of two numbers is 39 and the difference is 15 what is the two numbers ?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "train"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "40.0 and 18.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 225986,
        "question": "the difference between two numbers is 22 . If the larger number is 4 more than twice the smaller . Find the numbers",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "train"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "12.0 and 21.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 96991,
        "question": "The sum of two numbers is 33 . Their difference is 9 . What are the two numbers ?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "train"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "13.0 and 63.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 759519,
        "question": "What is the sum of two numbers is 76 . If larger is two less than 5 times the smaller .",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "train"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "24.0 and 21.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 464290,
        "question": "the sum of two numbers is 45 . 4 times the first number is 9 less than 5 times the second . what are the two numbers ?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "dev"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-6.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 146171,
        "question": "One half of a number is 3 more than the same number . What is the number ?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 _smt0) (Equals (Plus 3 _smt0) (Times 0.5 _smt0)))",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "test"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "14.0 and 9.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 4885,
        "question": "The sum of two numbers is 23 and their difference is 5 . Find the numbers .",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 23 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals 5 (Minus _smt1 _smt0)) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "train"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "1.0 and 3.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 775416,
        "question": "The sum of 4 times the first number and three times the second number is 15 . The difference of three times the first number and twice the second number is 7 . Find the numbers .",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 15 (Plus (Times 4 _smt0) (Times 3 _smt1))) (Equals 7 (Difference (Elements (Times 3 _smt0) (Times 2 _smt1)))) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "dev"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "81.0 and 14.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 179043,
        "question": "The difference of two numbers is 67 . The larger number is three less than six times the smaller number . Find the numbers .",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 67 (Minus _smt1 _smt0)) (Equals _smt1 (Minus (Times 6 _smt0) 3)) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "train"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "14.0 and 11.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 666059,
        "question": "One number is 3 less than a second number . Twice the second number is 5 less than 3 times the first . Find the two numbers .",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "train"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "41.0 and 147.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 499968,
        "question": "the sum of 2 numbers is 188 . the larger number is 24 more than 3 times the smaller . find the numbers",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 188 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals _smt1 (Plus 24 (Times 3 _smt0))) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "train"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "18.0 and 7.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 427962,
        "question": "One number is 4 more than twice the second number . Their total is 25 . What are the 2 numbers .",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "train"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "17.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 760914,
        "question": "X represents a certain number , when the number is multiplied by 3 the result is as adding 34 to the number . What is the number ?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "dev"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "52.0 and 3.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 219569,
        "question": "The sum of two numbers is 55 . The greater number is seventeen times the smaller number plus one . Find the numbers .",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 55 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals _smt1 (Plus (Times 17 _smt0) 1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "dev"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "17.0 and 86.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 311656,
        "question": "The sum of two numbers is 103 . The larger number is one more than five times the smaller number . Find the numbers",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 103 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals _smt1 (Plus 1 (Times 5 _smt0))) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "dev"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "82.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 765427,
        "question": "Three less than 4 times a number is 325 . What is the number ?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Minus (Times 4 _smt0) 3) 325) (Equals ?_x1 _smt0))",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "dev"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "16.0 and 78.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 673170,
        "question": "A larger number is 2 less than 5 times the smaller number . If the sum of these numbers is 94 , find the larger number .",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "dev"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "9.0 and 13.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 108337,
        "question": "Two numbers have a sum of 22 . Their difference is 4 . what are the two numbers ?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "dev"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "65.0 and 25.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 631993,
        "question": "the sum of two numbers is 90 . three times the smaller is 10 more than the larger . find the larger number .",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "dev"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "10.0 and 4.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 127730,
        "question": "The sum of two numbers is 6 less than twice the first number . Their difference is 10 less than four times the second number .",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "dev"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "4.0 and -2.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 370467,
        "question": "The larger of two numbers is 8 more than twice the smaller . The sum of the numbers is 10 less than three times the larger . Find the numbers .",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Max (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Plus 8 (Times 2 _smt0))) (Equals (Plus _smt0 _smt1) (Minus (Times 3 _smt1) 10)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "dev"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "21.6 and 24.8",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 376120,
        "question": "The difference between two numbers is 3.2 . The sum of the numbers is 46.4 . What are the two numbers ?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "train"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "19.0 and 33.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 513521,
        "question": "the sum of two numbers is 52 . the sum of the smaller and 5 times the larger is 184 . find the numbers",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 52 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals 184 (Plus _smt0 (Times 5 _smt1))) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "train"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "1.25 and 13.75",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 225035,
        "question": "Two numbers are in the ratio 1 to 11 and their sum is 15 . Find the numbers .",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "train"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "108.0 and 35.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 652539,
        "question": "Find two numbers whose sum is 143 such that when the larger number is divided by the smaller , the quotient is 3 . and the remainder is 3 . What are the numbers ?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "test"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "35.0 and 69.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 242101,
        "question": "The sum of two numbers is 104 . The larger is 1 less than twice the smaller number . Find the numbers .",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 104 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals _smt1 (Minus (Times 2 _smt0) 1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "test"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "11.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 672794,
        "question": "Twenty-three less than 4 times a number is twenty-one . What is the number ?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 _smt0) (Equals (Plus 20 1) (Minus (Times 4 _smt0) (Plus 20 3))))",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "train"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "47.0 and 16.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 482896,
        "question": "The larger of two numbers is one less than three times the smaller . if their sum is 63 .",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "dev"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-53.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 38538,
        "question": "which 2 consecutive integers have a sum of -105",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "test"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "4.0 and 5.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 853841,
        "question": "The sum of two positive integers is 9 . Twice the first integer plus thrice the second integer is 22 . Determine the numbers",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "train"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "81.0 and 14.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 265873,
        "question": "the difference between of two numbers is 67 , the larger number is three less than 6 times the smaller number .",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "test"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "396.0 and 132.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 362485,
        "question": "The difference of two positive numbers is 264 . The larger is three times the smaller number . Find the two numbers .",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "train"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "6.2",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 770731,
        "question": "the sum of 9 and a certain number is equal to four times the number subtracted from 40 . find the number .",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals _smt0 ?_x0) (Equals (Plus 9 _smt0) (Minus 40 (Times 4 ?_x0))))",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "test"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "608.0 and 912.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 630415,
        "question": "adding together two numbers 1520 . three times the smaller is equal to two times the larger . find the two numbers",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "train"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "32.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 369466,
        "question": "ONE-SIXTH OF A DENTIST 'S AGE 8 YEARS AGO EQUALS ONE-TENTH OF HIS AGE 8 YEARS HENCE . WHAT IS HIS AGE NOW ?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "dev"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "14.0 and 25.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 16062,
        "question": "Two numbers have a sum of 39 . Their difference is 11 . What are the two numbers .",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "train"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "11.5 and 32.5",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 351101,
        "question": "The Sum of two numbers is 44 . If the larger number is two less than three times the smaller number , find the number .",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "train"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "13.0 and 40.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 280654,
        "question": "the sum of two numbers is 53 . if three times the smaller is one less than the larger , find the numbers .",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 53 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals (Minus _smt1 1) (Times 3 _smt0)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "train"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-4.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 389405,
        "question": "What is twenty more than three times a number is the same as the sum of that number and twelve ?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "train"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "342.0 and 236.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 185146,
        "question": "THE ATTENDANCE AT A SCHOOL CONCERT WAS 578 . ADMISSION COST $ 2.00 FOR ADULTS AND $ 1.50 FOR CHILDREN . THE RECEIPTS WERE $ 985.00 . HOW MANY ADULTS AND HOW MANY CHILDREN ATTENDED THE CONCERT ?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "train"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "17.0 and 35.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 541835,
        "question": "The sum of three times first number and the second number is 86 . Two times the first number is 1 less than the second number . What are the numbers ?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 86 (Plus (Times 3 _smt0) _smt1)) (Equals (Minus _smt1 1) (Times 2 _smt0)) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "dev"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "24.0 and 8.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 182090,
        "question": "The difference between two numbers is 16 . Five times the smaller is the same as 8 less than twice the larger . Find the numbers .",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 16 (Minus _smt1 _smt0)) (Equals (Times 5 _smt0) (Minus (Times 2 _smt1) 8)) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "train"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "7.0 and 21.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 749368,
        "question": "the sum of two number is 28 . if the second number is thrice the first , what is the second number .",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "test"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "33.0 and 19.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 871121,
        "question": "The greater of two numbers is 5 less than twice the smaller . And the sum of the numbers is 52",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "train"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "34.0 and 29.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 237977,
        "question": "Find two numbers whose sum is 63 and whose difference is 5 .",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 63 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals 5 (Minus _smt1 _smt0)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "test"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "5.0 and 8.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 183226,
        "question": "The difference of two numbers is 3 . Their sum is 13 . Find the numbers .",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 3 (Minus _smt1 _smt0)) (Equals 13 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "train"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "24.0 and 8.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 53380,
        "question": "The difference of two numbers is 16 . Three-fourths of the larger number is 14 larger than one-half of the smaller number . Find the numbers .",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 16 (Minus _smt1 _smt0)) (Equals (Times 3 _smt1) (Times 4 (Plus 14 (Times 0.5 _smt0)))) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "train"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "64.0 and -16.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 368038,
        "question": "The sum of two numbers is 48 and their difference is 80 . Find each ofthe number .",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "train"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "4.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 664253,
        "question": "If a number is substracted from five more than twice the number , the result is 9 . Find the number",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "train"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "30.0 and 20.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 379721,
        "question": "the sum of two numbers is 50 . The difference between these numbers is 10 than find the numbers",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "test"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "35.0 and 54.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 767344,
        "question": "The sum of 2 two-digit numbers is 89 and their difference is 19 . What are the two numbers ?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "train"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "14.0 and 9.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 310397,
        "question": "The larger of two numbers is four less than twice the smaller . Their sum is twenty-three . Find the larger number .",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "dev"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "8.0 and 10.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 389184,
        "question": "The greater of the two consecutive even numbers is 6 less than twice the smaller .",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "train"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "5.0 and 8.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 167571,
        "question": "The smaller of two numbers is 3 less that the larger . Twice the larger plus 4 times the smaller is 36 . Find the numbers",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "test"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "24.0 and 56.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 264997,
        "question": "Two numbers are in the ratio 3 to 7 . Two-fifths of their sum is 32 .",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "train"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "7.0 and 21.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 357498,
        "question": "The sum of two numbers is twice their difference . The larger number is 7 more than twice the smaller . Find the numbers .",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus _smt0 _smt1) (Times 2 (Minus _smt1 _smt0))) (Equals _smt1 (Plus 7 (Times 2 _smt0))) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "train"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "43.0 and 57.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 787643,
        "question": "find 2 numbers whose sum is 100 and whose difference is 14 .",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 100 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals 14 (Minus _smt1 _smt0)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "train"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "2.0 and -1.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 231083,
        "question": "the sum of two integers is 1 . if the smaller integer is 11 less than 5 times the larger , what are the integers ?",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Equals 1 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals _smt0 (Minus (Times 5 _smt1) 11)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "test"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "250.0 and 50.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 276559,
        "question": "find two numbers whose difference is 200 , such that the larger number is 5 times the smaller .",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals _smt1 (Times 5 _smt0)) (Equals 200 (Minus _smt1 _smt0)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "dev"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-15.0 and 12.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 164775,
        "question": "the sum of two numbers is -3 . if the second number is subtracted from the first , the difference is 27 . find the numbers",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus _smt0 _smt1) (Minus 0 3)) (Equals 27 (Minus _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "test"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "48.0 and 40.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 301832,
        "question": "The ratio between two positive number is 6 to 5 . if the difference between the two numbers is 8 , what are the two numbers ? Thanks !",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "train"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "8.0 and 6.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 765055,
        "question": "The sum of the two digits of a number is 14 , the value of the number is 2 less than 11 times the tens digit , what is the number ?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "train"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "12.0 and 8.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 571512,
        "question": "Twice the larger number is three times the smaller , and their sum is 20 . Find the numbers .",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "train"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "2.66666666667",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 151676,
        "question": "five times the difference of a number and one yields the same result as twice the same number increase by three . Find the number .",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "train"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "15.0 and 13.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 244172,
        "question": "the sume of two numbers is 28 , their difference is 2 . what are the numbers ?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "train"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "17.0 and 19.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 828645,
        "question": "The sum of two consecutive odd integers is at least 36 . What are the integers ?",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Equals 36 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "train"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "3.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 505150,
        "question": "The difference of four times a number and seven times the number is 9 .",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "train"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "61.0 and 33.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 796706,
        "question": "the sum of two numbers is 94 , and the larger number is 5 less than twice the smaller number . find the numbers",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 94 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals _smt1 (Minus (Times 2 _smt0) 5)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "train"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "92.0 and 156.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 548627,
        "question": "The sum of 2 digits is 248 . Their difference is 64 . Find the numbers .",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "train"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "17.0 and 51.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 919697,
        "question": "The difference of two positive integers is 34 . The larger of the numbers is three times the smaller . What are these numbers ?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Max (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Times 3 _smt0)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (LessThan 0 _smt0) (LessThan 0 _smt1) (Equals 34 (Minus _smt1 _smt0)) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "train"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "14.0 and 5.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 120139,
        "question": "Twice the larger of the two numbers is three more than five times the smaller , and then the sum of four times the larger and three times the smaller is 71 . What are the nos . ?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "test"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "6.0 and 4.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 157467,
        "question": "The sum of two numbers is 10 . Three times one of them is more than four times the second by 2 . Find the numbers .",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "test"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "49.0 and 15.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 190263,
        "question": "The sum of two numbers is 64 . Two more than twice the larger number is five less than seven times the smaller . Find the numbers .",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 64 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals (Minus (Times 7 _smt0) 5) (Plus 2 (Times 2 _smt1))) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "test"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "4.33333333333",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 307088,
        "question": "twice the sum of 4 and 3 times some number is 34 . what is the number ?",
        "semantics": "(Equals 34 (Times 2 (Plus 4 (Times 3 ?_x0))))",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "dev"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "23.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 320536,
        "question": "If 19 is subtracted from 4 times a number , the result is 73 . Find the number",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 73 (Minus (Times 4 _smt0) 19)) (Equals ?_x1 _smt0))",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "train"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "2.66666666667 and 4.66666666667",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 347492,
        "question": "The smaller of two consecutive even integers is five more than one half of the greater .",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "train"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "51.6129032258 and 48.3870967742",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 45656,
        "question": "A 14 % ETHANOL SOLUTION IS TO BE MIXED WITH A 45 % ETHANOL SOLUTION TO PRODUCE A FINAL SOLUTION WHICH IS 30 % ETHANOL . IF THE FINAL SOLUTION IS 100 GALLONS . FIND THE AMOUNT OF EACH SOLUTION NEEDED FOR DELISHA TO MIX .",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "train"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "5.0 and 4.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 4985,
        "question": "a two digit number is 6 times the sum of its digits . the tens digit is 1 more than the units digit . find the number .",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "train"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "24.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 604682,
        "question": "the sum of twice a number and 16 less than the number is the same as the difference between -32 and the number . what is the number",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 _smt0) (Equals (Plus (Times 2 _smt0) (Minus _smt0 16)) (Difference (Elements (Minus 0 32) _smt0))))",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "train"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "81.0 and 39.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 755492,
        "question": "If the sum of two numbers is 120 , and thier difference is 42 , find the smaller number .",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "dev"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "13.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 757959,
        "question": "The sum of two consecutive whole numbers is 27 . Find the numbers .",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "dev"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "9.0 and 10.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 764947,
        "question": "When the smaller of two consecutive integers is added to three times the larger , the result is 39 . Find the integers .",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "train"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "61.0 and 63.0",
        "dbidOption": "draw",
        "id": 97995,
        "question": "The sum of two consecutive odd integers in 124 . What are the integers ?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "train"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{40;29}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1557,
        "question": "one number is 11 more than another number. Find the two numbers if three times the larger exceeds four times the smaller number by 4.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals _smt0 (Plus 11 _smt1)) (Equals (Times 3 (Max (Elements _smt0 _smt1))) (Plus (Times 4 (Min (Elements _smt0 _smt1))) 4)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "6; 9",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1558,
        "question": "One number is 3 less than a second number. Twice the second number is 12 less than 5 times the first. Find the two numbers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{34; 28}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1559,
        "question": "Find two numbers whose sum is 62 and whose difference is  6.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 62 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals 6 (Minus _smt1 _smt0)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{42;26}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1560,
        "question": "the sum of two numbers is 68. their difference is 16. what are the numbers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 68 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals 16 (Minus _smt1 _smt0)) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{77; 20}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1561,
        "question": "the sum of two numbers is 97. the difference of the two numbers is 57. find the two numbers",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{20; -2}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1562,
        "question": "the sum of two numbers is 18. their difference is 22. what are the numbers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 18 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals 22 (Minus _smt1 _smt0)) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{45/2; 27/2} | {22.5; 13.5}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1563,
        "question": "i have two numbers. the sum is 36 and the difference is 9. what are the two numbers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{20; 16}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1564,
        "question": "The sum of 2 integers is 36. The difference of the same 2 numbers is 4. Find the integers.",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Equals 36 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals 4 (Minus _smt1 _smt0)) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{23; 14}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1565,
        "question": "The difference of two numbers is 9 and their sum is 37. what are the numbers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 9 (Minus _smt1 _smt0)) (Equals 37 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "13; 20",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1566,
        "question": "One number is seven less than another number. The sum of the numbers is thirty-three. Find the numbers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals _smt0 (Minus _smt1 7)) (Equals (Plus _smt0 _smt1) (Plus 30 3)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{32; 56}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1567,
        "question": "The difference between two numbers is 24. Find the numbers if their sum is 88.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 24 (Minus _smt1 _smt0)) (Equals 88 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{8; 20}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1568,
        "question": "A number is 12 less than another.  The sum of the numbers is 28.  find the Numbers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals _smt0 (Minus _smt1 12)) (Equals 28 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{9; 14}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1569,
        "question": "The sum of two numbers is twenty-three, and the larger number is five more than the smaller number. Find these numbers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus _smt0 _smt1) (Plus 20 3)) (Equals _smt1 (Plus 5 _smt0)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "10; 12; 14",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1570,
        "question": "If the first and third of three consecutive even integers are added, the result is 12 less than three times the second integer. find the integers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals (Plus _smt0 _smt2) (Minus (Times 3 _smt1) 12)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-93; -91; -89",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1571,
        "question": "The sum of three consecutive odd integers is -273. What are the integers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Minus 0 273)) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-41; -39; -37",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1572,
        "question": "the sum of three consecutive odd integers is -117. what are the three integer?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Minus 0 117)) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-27; -25; -23",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1573,
        "question": "what three consecutive odd integers have a sum of -75?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Minus 0 75)) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{2.764; 7.236}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1574,
        "question": "Find two numbers with sum 10 and product 20.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 20 (Times _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals 10 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{16; 48}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1575,
        "question": "The sum of two numbers is 64. If twice the smaller number is subtracted from the larger number, the result is 16. Find the two numbers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{18; 73}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1576,
        "question": "The sum of two numbers is 91.  The larger number is 1 more than 4 times the smaller number. Find the numbers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 91 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals _smt1 (Plus 1 (Times 4 _smt0))) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "226",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1577,
        "question": "What is the sum of the distinct prime factors of 2007?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 (Sum _x1)) (LessThan 0 _x2) (IsInteger 2007) (IsInteger _x2) (Equals (Mod 2007 _x2) 0) (IsPrime _x2) (Le 2 _x2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "4; 7",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1578,
        "question": "One positive integer is 3 less than a second positive integer. The sum of the squares of the two integers is 65. Find both positive integers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals _smt0 (Minus _smt1 3)) (Equals (Plus (Pow _smt0 2) (Pow _smt1 2)) 65) (IsInteger _smt0) (LessThan 0 _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (LessThan 0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "7; 8; 9",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1579,
        "question": "Three times the sum of three consecutive integers x, x + 1, and x + 2, is 72. What are the integers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Times 3 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) 72) (IsInteger x) (IsInteger (Plus x 1)) (IsInteger (Plus x 2)) (Equals (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2) (Elements x (Plus x 1) (Plus x 2))) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "6",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1580,
        "question": "2 more than 6 times a number is 20 more than 3 times the number. Find the number.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 _smt0) (Equals (Plus 20 (Times 3 _smt0)) (Plus 2 (Times 6 _smt0))))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "9",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1581,
        "question": "Fifteen more than four times a number is 6 more than five times the number. what's the value of the number?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus 6 (Times 5 _smt0)) (Plus 15 (Times 4 _smt0))) (Equals ?_x2 _smt0))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "2",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1582,
        "question": "5 less than 6 times a whole number is 9 less than 8 times that number. Find the number.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 _smt0) (IsInteger _smt0) (Equals (Minus (Times 8 _smt0) 9) (Minus (Times 6 _smt0) 5)))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "11; 12 or -12; -11",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1583,
        "question": "The square of the sum of two consecutive integers is 529.  What are the integers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Pow (Plus _smt0 _smt1) 2) 529) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "59",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1584,
        "question": "a no. has two digits whose sum is 14. if 36 is added to the no., its digits are interchanged. find the no.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "digits",
            "informal",
            "algebra",
            "sigmadolphin-dev"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "26",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1585,
        "question": "The sum of the digits of a two digit number is 8. When the digits are reversed, the number is increased by 36. Find the number.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "digits",
            "informal",
            "algebra",
            "sigmadolphin-dev"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "78",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1586,
        "question": "the sum of the digits of a two digit number is 15. if the digits are interchanged the result exceeds the original number by 9. find the number.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus _smt2_d1 _smt2_d0) 15) (Equals ?_x1 (Plus (Times _smt2_d0 1) (Times _smt2_d1 10))) (Le (Plus (Times _smt2_d0 1) (Times _smt2_d1 10)) (Minus (Pow 10 2) 1)) (Le (Pow 10 (Minus 2 1)) (Plus (Times _smt2_d0 1) (Times _smt2_d1 10))) (Equals (Plus (Times _smt1_d0 1) (Times _smt1_d1 10)) (Plus (Times _smt2_d0 1) (Times _smt2_d1 10))) (Le 0 _smt1_d1) (Le _smt1_d1 9) (IsInteger _smt1_d1) (Le 0 _smt1_d0) (Le _smt1_d0 9) (IsInteger _smt1_d0) (Le 0 _smt2_d1) (Le _smt2_d1 9) (IsInteger _smt2_d1) (Le 0 _smt2_d0) (Le _smt2_d0 9) (IsInteger _smt2_d0) (Equals (Plus (Plus (Times _smt2_d0 1) (Times _smt2_d1 10)) 9) (Plus (Times _smt2_d1 1) (Times _smt2_d0 10))))",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "digits",
            "informal",
            "algebra",
            "sigmadolphin-dev"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{33; 9}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1587,
        "question": "The sum of two numbers is 42. one number is 3 less than 4 times the other number. what are the numbers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 42 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals _smt0 (Minus (Times 4 _smt1) 3)) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{219;111}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1588,
        "question": "One number is 3 less than twice another number.  If the sum of the numbers is 330, find the two numbers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "11; 13",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1590,
        "question": "find two consecutive odd integers such that three times the smaller one exceeds two times the larger one by 7",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{11; 3}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1591,
        "question": "The sum of two numbers is fourteen. The sum of the squares of the two numbers is one hundred thirty. Find the two numbers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "22; 24; 26",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1592,
        "question": "Find three consecutive even integers such that twice the sum of the second and the third exceeds three times the first by 34.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals (Plus (Times 3 _smt0) 34) (Times 2 (Plus _smt1 _smt2))) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{3; 7}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1593,
        "question": "The sum of two integers is 10. Three times the larger integer is three less than eight times the smaller integer. Find the integers.",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Equals 10 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals (Minus (Times 8 _smt0) 3) (Times 3 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{12; 17}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1594,
        "question": "The sum of two integers is twenty-nine. Eight times the smaller integer is eleven more than five times the larger integer. Find the integers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus _smt0 _smt1) (Plus 20 9)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Equals (Plus 11 (Times 5 _smt1)) (Times 8 _smt0)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{52; 73}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1595,
        "question": "The sum of two numbers is 125. Five times one number minus three times the other is 41. Find the numbers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 125 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals 41 (Minus (Times 5 _smt0) (Times 3 _smt1))) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "ans_no_result",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1596,
        "question": "find two consecutive multiples of 7 whose sum is 84",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "92; 93",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1597,
        "question": "the sum of two consecutive integers is 185. Find the 2 integers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "90",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1598,
        "question": "Sixty more than a number divided by three is equal to eighty-four more than the same number divided by fifteen. What is the number?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 _smt0) (Equals (Plus 60 (Div _smt0 3)) (Plus (Plus 80 4) (Div _smt0 15))))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "17; 18; 19",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1599,
        "question": "Find 3 consecutive numbers such that twice the second is 17 more than the third.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Equals (Plus 17 _smt2) (Times 2 _smt1)) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "19; 21",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1600,
        "question": "the sum of two consecutive odd integers is 40. find the numbers",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Equals 40 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "21; 22",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1601,
        "question": "Find two consecutive integers such that 3 times the first integer plus 2 times the second integer is equal to 107.",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals 107 (Plus (Times 3 _smt0) (Times 2 _smt1))) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "7;8",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1602,
        "question": "Find two consecutive  whole numbers such that 5 times the smaller number added by 3 times the greater number makes 59",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "8; 10",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1603,
        "question": "The greater of two consecutive even integers is 14 less than three times the smaller integer. Find the integers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Equals (Max (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Minus (Times 3 _smt0) 14)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "23; 24; 25",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1604,
        "question": "Find three consecutive numbers whose sum is 72.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 72 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "47; 48; 49",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1605,
        "question": "The sum of three consecutive integers is 144. find the integers.",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Equals 144 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "7; 8; 9",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1606,
        "question": "The sum of three consecutive whole numbers is 24.  What are the integers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "51",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1607,
        "question": "Three consecutive integers have the sum of 153. What is the second integer?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) 153) (Equals ?_x1 _smt1) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "158; 160; 162",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1608,
        "question": "The sum of three consecutive even integers is 480. Find the three integers",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "81; 83; 85",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1609,
        "question": "THE SUM OF  3 CONSECUTIVE ODD NUMBERS IS 249. FIND THE INTEGERS",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Equals 249 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-1; 1; 3; 5",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1610,
        "question": "find four consecutive odd integers whose sum is 8 using an equation",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 8 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3))) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (IsInteger _smt3) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Le _smt2 _smt3) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_3 _smt3))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "30",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1611,
        "question": "1/3 of a number is 5 less than half of the same number. what is the number?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Times 1 _smt0) (Times 3 (Minus (Times 0.5 _smt0) 5))) (Equals ?_x1 _smt0))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "5; 6 or -2; -1",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1612,
        "question": "The Product of two consecutive integers is 8 more than twice their sum. Find the integers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-20",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1613,
        "question": "twice a number is 60 more than five times the number. what is that number?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Times 2 _smt0) (Plus 60 (Times 5 _smt0))) (Equals ?_x1 _smt0))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "5",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1614,
        "question": "five times a number is ten more than three times the number. Find the number.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Times 5 _smt0) (Plus 10 (Times 3 _smt0))) (Equals ?_x1 _smt0))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "11",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1615,
        "question": "I think of a number multiply it by 8 then subtract 66. The result is twice the number that i was thinking.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "4",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1616,
        "question": "eight times a number equals 24 more than two times the number. What is the number?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Times 8 _smt0) (Plus 24 (Times 2 _smt0))) (Equals ?_x1 _smt0))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "91;93;95",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1617,
        "question": "the sum of three consecutive odd integers is 279. what are the integers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals 279 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "3; 5; 7",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1618,
        "question": "Find 3 consecutive odd integers such that the sum of adds to 15",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "77; 79; 81",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1619,
        "question": "3 consecutive odd integers with the sum of 237.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 237 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "117; 119; 121",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1620,
        "question": "The sum of three consecutive odd numbers is 357. What are the three numbers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "12; 14; 16",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1621,
        "question": "Find three consecutive even integers if twice the second is 12 more than the third.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals (Plus 12 _smt2) (Times 2 _smt1)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "12; 14",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1622,
        "question": "the sum of the squares of two consecutive positive even integers is 340. find the integers",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus (Pow _smt0 2) (Pow _smt1 2)) 340) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (LessThan 0 _smt0) (LessThan 0 _smt1) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "7; 9",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1623,
        "question": "The sum of the squares of two consecutive positive odd integers is one hundred thirty. Find the two integers",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "60; 62; 64",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1624,
        "question": "sum of three consecutive even numbers is 186 what are the numbers",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "60; 62; 64",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1625,
        "question": "Find 3 consecutive even integers whose sum is 186",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 186 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "6; 8; 10",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1626,
        "question": "Find three consecutive even integers such that the sum of five times the first, six times the second and seven times the third is 148",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals 148 (Sum (Elements (Times 5 _smt0) (Times 6 _smt1) (Times 7 _smt2)))) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "8; 10 or -10; -8",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1627,
        "question": "Find two consecutive even integers x and x+2 with a product of 80.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 80 (Times _smt0 _smt1)) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger x) (IsInteger (Plus x 2)) (Equals (Elements _smt0 _smt1) (Elements x (Plus x 2))) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "10; 12 or -12; -10",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1628,
        "question": "find two consecutive even integers whose product equal 120",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 120 (Times _smt0 _smt1)) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "7;8",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1629,
        "question": "the product of two positive consecutive integers is 56 , find the numbers",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (LessThan 0 _smt0) (LessThan 0 _smt1) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals 56 (Times _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-1",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1630,
        "question": "find the value of y to make this an arithmetic sequencey+8, 4y+6, 3y",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-59; -57",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1632,
        "question": "what are two consecutive odd integers whose sum is -116?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Minus 0 116) (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "20; 22",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1633,
        "question": "find two consecutive even integers such that the sum of the larger and twice the smaller is 62",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Equals 62 (Plus _smt1 (Times 2 _smt0))) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "58; 60",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1634,
        "question": "Find two consecutive even integers such that the sum of the larger and 3 times the smaller is 234",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Equals 234 (Plus _smt1 (Times 3 _smt0))) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "114; 116",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1635,
        "question": "Find two consecutive even integers such that the sum of twice the smaller integer plus the larger is 344.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Equals 344 (Plus (Times 2 _smt0) _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "8; 10; 12 or 10; 12; 14 or 12; 14; 16",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1636,
        "question": "Find all the sets of three consecutive even integers whose sum is between 25 and 45.",
        "semantics": "(And (LessThan 25 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (LessThan (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) 45) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "3; 5; 7",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1637,
        "question": "Find three consecutive odd integers such that the sum of the first and twice the second is 6 more than the third",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals (Plus 6 _smt2) (Plus _smt0 (Times 2 _smt1))) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "15; 17; 19",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1638,
        "question": "find three positive consecutive odd integers such that the largest decreased by three times the second is 47 less than the smallest",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (LessThan 0 _smt0) (LessThan 0 _smt1) (LessThan 0 _smt2) (Equals (Minus (Min (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) 47) (Minus (Max (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Times 3 _smt1))) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "5; 6; 7 or -7; -6; -5",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1639,
        "question": "Find 3 consecutive integers whose squares add up to 110.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 110 (Sum (Elements (Pow _smt0 2) (Pow _smt1 2) (Pow _smt2 2)))) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "15; 16 or 0; 1",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1640,
        "question": "The product of two consecutive integers is 8 less than 8 times their sum. Find the integers",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "5;6 or -4;-3",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1641,
        "question": "Find the two consecutive integers whose product exceeds their sum by 19.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "9; 10 or -8; -7",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1642,
        "question": "the product of two consecutive integers is 71 more than their sum. Find the integers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "7; 8",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1643,
        "question": "the product of two consecutive positive integers is 41 more than their sums. find the integers",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "9; 10 or -8; -7",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1644,
        "question": "THE PRODUCT OF TWO CONSECUTIVE INTEGERS  IS 71 MORE THAN THE SUM. FIND THE INTEGERS",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-11; -7",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1645,
        "question": "The sum of three consecutive odd integers is 5 less than twice the smallest integer. What's the smallest and largest integer?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Minus (Times 2 _smt0) 5)) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{6; 24}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1647,
        "question": "The larger of two numbers is four times the smaller. If their difference is eighteen, find the numbers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Max (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Times 4 _smt0)) (Equals 18 (Minus _smt1 _smt0)) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "37; 39; 41",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1648,
        "question": "Find three consecutive odd integers such that twice the first, decreased by the second is 35.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals 35 (Minus (Times 2 _smt0) _smt1)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "123",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1649,
        "question": "one number is three times another number and their sum is 164. find the number?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus (Times 3 _smt1) _smt1) 164) (Equals ?_x1 (Times 3 _smt1)))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "492",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1650,
        "question": "The sum of two numbers is 574. One number is six times the other. Find the larger number.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus (Times 6 _smt1) _smt1) 574) (Equals ?_x1 (Max (Elements (Times 6 _smt1) _smt1))))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-12; -10; -8",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1651,
        "question": "Find three consecutive even integers such that the product of five and the third integer is four more than two times the sum of the first two numbers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals (Plus 4 (Times 2 (Plus _smt0 _smt1))) (Times 5 _smt2)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-25; -24; -23",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1652,
        "question": "The sum of three consecutive integers is 47 less than the least of the integers. Find the integers.",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Equals (Minus (Min (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) 47) (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "24; 26",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1653,
        "question": "find 2 consecutive even integers such that eleven more than half the second integer results in the first integer.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Equals _smt0 (Plus 11 (Times 0.5 _smt1))) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "10; 12; 14",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1654,
        "question": "Three times the smallest of three consecutive even integers is two more than twice the largest. Find the integers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "3; 5 or -5; -3",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1655,
        "question": "if the product of two consecutive odd integers is decreased by 3, the result is 12. find the integers",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 12 (Minus (Times _smt0 _smt1) 3)) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "6; 7; 8; 9",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1656,
        "question": "find four consecutive numbers such that the sum of the first three numbers is twelve more than the fourth number",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3)) (Equals (Plus 12 _smt3) (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_2 _smt2) (Equals ?_x1_3 _smt3))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-5",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1657,
        "question": "The product of four greater than an certain negative integer and sixteen less than four times the integers is equal to 36. Determine the integer ?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{12;20}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1658,
        "question": "The difference between two numbers is 8. Five times the larger number is 4 more than 8 time the other. Find the numbers ?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 8 (Difference (Elements _smt0 _smt1))) (Equals (Plus 4 (Times 8 _smt1)) (Times 5 (Max (Elements _smt0 _smt1)))) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "88; 90; 92",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1659,
        "question": "fIND tHREE CONSECUTIVE EVEN INTEGERS SUCH THAT THE SUM OF THE FIRST AND THIRD IS 90 MORE THAN THE SECOND",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals (Plus 90 _smt1) (Plus _smt0 _smt2)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-1; 1; 3",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1661,
        "question": "find three consecutive odd integers such that three times the middle integer is one more than the sum of the first and the third",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals (Plus 1 (Plus _smt0 _smt2)) (Times 3 _smt1)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "31; 33; 35",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1662,
        "question": "The sum of two consecutive odd integer is 29 more than the next odd integer.  Find the three integers in increasing order.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "41; 43; 45",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1663,
        "question": "Find 3 consecutive odd integers such that the sum of the first and third equals the sum of the second and 43.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals (Plus _smt1 43) (Plus _smt0 _smt2)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "29; 31; 33",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1664,
        "question": "Find Three consecutive odd integers such that the sum of the first and third equals the sum of the second and 31.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals (Plus _smt1 31) (Plus _smt0 _smt2)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "9",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1665,
        "question": "For two consecutive integers, the sum of the smaller and twice the larger is 29. Find the smaller integer",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 _smt0) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals 29 (Plus _smt0 (Times 2 _smt1))) (Le _smt0 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "13; 15",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1666,
        "question": "Find two consecutive odd integers such that twice the greater is 17 more than the lesser.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Equals (Plus 17 _smt0) (Times 2 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "25",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1667,
        "question": "Four times an integer is 30 less than five times the next consecutive integer. Find the integers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-52;-11",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1668,
        "question": "The sum of two numbers is  -63. The first number minus the second is -41. Find the numbers",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus _smt0 _smt1) (Minus 0 63)) (Equals (Minus 0 41) (Minus _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{-10; 1}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1669,
        "question": "one number is 11 less than the other number. If their sum is -9, find the two numbers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "7; 9 or 1; 3",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1670,
        "question": "find two consecutive odd integers such that the square of the larger is 3 smaller than 12 times the smaller",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Equals (Minus (Times 12 _smt0) 3) (Pow _smt1 2)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "8; 9; 10",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1671,
        "question": "Find three consecutive numbers where the product of the smallest two numbers is 28 less than the square of the largest numbers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-3",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1672,
        "question": "The product of two consecutive integers is -4 more than the square of the smaller one. What's the larger number?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Times _smt0 _smt1) (Plus (Minus 0 4) (Pow _smt0 2))) (Equals ?_x1 _smt1) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "14",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1673,
        "question": "The sum of four consecutive integers is 50. What is the largest of these integers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "9",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1674,
        "question": "Eighty, decreased by three times a number, is the same as five times the number, increased by eight. Find the number.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 _smt0) (Equals (Minus 80 (Times 3 _smt0)) (Plus (Times 5 _smt0) 8)))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "15",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1675,
        "question": "If you have five consecutive integers such that the even integers add up to 48 what is the smallest odd integer?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "21;23",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1676,
        "question": "find two consecutive odd integers such that 4 times the larger is 29 more than three times the smaller",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Equals (Plus 29 (Times 3 _smt0)) (Times 4 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "63; 65",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1677,
        "question": "Four times the smaller of two consecutive odd integers is the same as 73 less than 5 times the larger. Find the integers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Equals (Times 4 (Min (Elements _smt0 _smt1))) (Minus (Times 5 _smt1) 73)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-11; -9; -7",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1678,
        "question": "find three consecutive odd integers such that three times the first is 9 greater than six times the third",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals (Plus 9 (Times 6 _smt2)) (Times 3 _smt0)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "ans_no_result",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1679,
        "question": "Find four consecutive numbers which, when added together, total 80.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{365; 922}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1680,
        "question": "The sum of two positive integers is 1,287. If the larger number is 9 And 1/2 more than 2 And 1/2 times the smaller number, then what are the two numbers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "22; 23",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1682,
        "question": "Find two consecutive whole numbers such that 3/4 of the first number is 5 more than 1/2 the second number.",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals (Times 3 _smt0) (Times 4 (Plus 5 (Times 0.5 _smt1)))) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "22; 23",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1683,
        "question": "find two consecutive whole numbers, where 3/4 of the first number  is 5 more than 1/2 the second number? Let n represent the first number, and n + 1 the second number?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "17",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1684,
        "question": "The difference of the cubes of two consecutive positive integers is 217. What is the sum of the two integers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (LessThan 0 _smt0) (LessThan 0 _smt1) (Equals 217 (Difference (Elements (Pow _smt0 3) (Pow _smt1 3)))) (Le _smt0 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "2 or -3",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1685,
        "question": "The sum of a number and its square is 6. Find the number",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 _smt0) (Equals 6 (Plus _smt0 (Pow _smt0 2))))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-9 or 8",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1686,
        "question": "the sum of an integer and its square is 72. what is the integer",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 _smt0) (IsInteger _smt0) (Equals 72 (Plus _smt0 (Pow _smt0 2))))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "80",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1687,
        "question": "The smallest integer in a set of three consecutive integers is x, and the largest   integer in this set is z. If the sum of the set is equal to 27, then what is the value of xz?",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _x4) (IsInteger _x5) (Equals 27 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Equals ?_x6 (Times (Min _x0) (Max _x1))) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "5;6;7 or -5;-4;-3",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1688,
        "question": "The product of the smaller two of three consecutive integers is equal to 23 plus the largest.  Find the integers.",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Equals (Times _smt0 _smt1) (Plus 23 _smt2)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "27",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1689,
        "question": "The sum of the digits of two digits number is 9. If the units digit is 5 more than the ten's digit, What is the number?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "digits",
            "informal",
            "algebra",
            "sigmadolphin-dev"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "n = -2 | -2",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1690,
        "question": "four more than the opposite of n equals 6. what is n?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 n) (Equals 6 (Plus 4 (Minus 0 n))))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "4; 6",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1691,
        "question": "Find two consecutive even integers such that six times the first integer equals four times the second integer.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Equals (Times 4 _smt1) (Times 6 _smt0)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "12",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1692,
        "question": "120=100(M/10),what is the value of M?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Times 100 m) (Times 10 120)) (Equals ?_x0 m))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "16",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1693,
        "question": "12 is 3/4 of what number?",
        "semantics": "(Equals (Times 3 ?_x0) (Times 4 12))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "300/7 | 42.857",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1694,
        "question": "60 is 140% of what number?",
        "semantics": "(Equals (Times 140 ?_x0) (Times 100 60))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "21",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1697,
        "question": "If the first and third of three consecutive odd integers are added, the result is 57 less than five times the second integer. Find the third integer.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus _smt0 _smt2) (Minus (Times 5 _smt1) 57)) (Equals ?_x1 _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "21",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1698,
        "question": "If the first and third of 3 consecutive odd integers are added, the result is 57 less than 5 times the second integer.  Find the 3rd integer.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus _smt0 _smt2) (Minus (Times 5 _smt1) 57)) (Equals ?_x1 _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "45",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1699,
        "question": "The sum of two numbers is 87. Three times the smaller plus twice the larger is 216. Find the larger number.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus _smt0 _smt1) 87) (Equals (Plus (Times 3 _smt0) (Times 2 _smt1)) 216) (Equals ?_x1 _smt1) (Le _smt0 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "1",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1700,
        "question": "There are 3 consecutive integers such that 3 times the sum of the first and third is 5 times the second. What is the third integer?",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x2 _smt5) (IsInteger _x1) (Consecutive (Elements _smt3 _smt4 _smt5)) (Equals (Times 5 _smt4) (Times 3 (Plus _smt3 _smt5))) (IsInteger _smt5))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "5; 6; 7 or -1; 0; 1",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1701,
        "question": "find three consecutive integers such that the product of the first and second is five less than five times the third",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Equals (Minus (Times 5 _smt2) 5) (Times _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "24; 25",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1702,
        "question": "if one-half of one integer is subtracted from three-fifths of the next consecutive integer, the difference is 3. what are the two integers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "32",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1703,
        "question": "The sum of two consecutive even integers is 62. Find the larger number.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus _smt0 _smt1) 62) (Equals ?_x1 _smt1) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Le _smt0 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "18;20 or -20;-18",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1704,
        "question": "The product of two consecutive even integers is 360. Find the integers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Equals 360 (Times _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "24; 26 or -26; -24",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1705,
        "question": "the two consecutive even integers whose product is 624",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 624 (Times _smt0 _smt1)) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "11; 13 or -13; -11",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1706,
        "question": "the product of two consecutive odd numbers is 143. find the numbers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals 143 (Times _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "25",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1707,
        "question": "If the sum of the consecutive integers from -22 to x, inclusive, is 72, what is the value of x?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Sum _x0) 72) (IsInteger _x1) (Le (Minus 0 22) _x1) (Le _x1 x) (Consecutive _x0) (Equals ?_x2 x))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "3; 5; 7",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1708,
        "question": "Find 3 consecutive odd numbers where the product of the smaller two numbers is 34 less than the square of the largest number.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Equals (Minus (Pow _smt2 2) 34) (Times _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "4; 6; 8",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1709,
        "question": "find three consecutive even integers such that the square of the third is 28 more than the square of the second.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals (Plus 28 (Pow _smt1 2)) (Pow _smt2 2)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{1.113; 9.887}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1710,
        "question": "Find 2 numbers whose sum AND product are 11.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "21; 23; 25",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1711,
        "question": "Find three consecutive odd integers such that the square of the second added to the first is seventy five less than the square of the third.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals (Minus (Pow _smt2 2) (Plus 70 5)) (Plus (Pow _smt1 2) _smt0)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "13",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1712,
        "question": "12 divided by 3+ 18 divided by 2",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "283",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1713,
        "question": "The number 2002 is equal to the sum of 7 consecutive natural numbers. What is the smallest of these 7 numbers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 (Min (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3 _smt4 _smt5 _smt6))) (LessThan 0 _smt0) (LessThan 0 _smt1) (LessThan 0 _smt2) (LessThan 0 _smt3) (LessThan 0 _smt4) (LessThan 0 _smt5) (LessThan 0 _smt6) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (IsInteger _smt3) (IsInteger _smt4) (IsInteger _smt5) (IsInteger _smt6) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3 _smt4 _smt5 _smt6)) (Equals 2002 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3 _smt4 _smt5 _smt6))) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Le _smt2 _smt3) (Le _smt3 _smt4) (Le _smt4 _smt5) (Le _smt5 _smt6))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "14",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1714,
        "question": "The sum of two consecutive even integers is equal to 30. What is the smaller integer?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 _smt0) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Equals 30 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "19; 21",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1715,
        "question": "Find two consecutive odd integers such that the smaller one is 12 more than one-third the larger",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals _smt0 (Plus 12 (Div (Times 1 _smt1) 3))) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "3;5 or -5;-3",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1716,
        "question": "The sum of the squares of two consecutive odd integers is 34. Find the two integers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-9; -7; -5; -3; -1",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1717,
        "question": "Find five consecutive odd integers such that the sum of the first and the fifth is one less than three times the fourth.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3 _smt4)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (IsInteger _smt3) (IsInteger _smt4) (Equals (Minus (Times 3 _smt3) 1) (Plus _smt0 _smt4)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_3 _smt3) (Equals ?_x0_4 _smt4))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{20; 20/9} | {20; 2.222}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1718,
        "question": "Find two positive numbers so that twice their sum equals their product and one number is 9 times the other number.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals _smt0 (Times 9 _smt1)) (LessThan 0 _smt0) (LessThan 0 _smt1) (Equals (Times _smt0 _smt1) (Times 2 (Plus _smt0 _smt1))) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "17;19;21",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1720,
        "question": "the sum of 3 consecutives odd integers is 40 more than the smallest. What are the integers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "14; 16; 18",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1721,
        "question": "The sum of three consecutive even integers is 30 more than the largest.  What are the integers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Plus 30 _smt2)) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "9; 11; 13",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1722,
        "question": "Find three consecutive odd integers such that the sum of the first integer twice the second integer and three times the third is 70?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{96; 24}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1723,
        "question": "the sum of two numbers is 120. if the larger number is 4 times the smaller number, find the two numbers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "32; 16",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1724,
        "question": "a number is twice another number. if their sum is 48 find the numbers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals _smt0 (Times 2 _smt1)) (Equals 48 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{28; 14}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1725,
        "question": "The sum of two numbers is 42. One number is 2 times as large as the other. What are the numbers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals _smt0 (Times 2 _smt1)) (Equals 42 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "15",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1726,
        "question": "Three times the first of three consecutive odd integers is 3 more than twice the third. Find the third integer ?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Times 3 _smt0) (Plus 3 (Times 2 _smt2))) (Equals ?_x1 _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "3; 4; 5",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1727,
        "question": "Three consecutive integers are such that their sum has the same value as twice the second integer subtracted from 20.  What are the three integers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "14; 16; 18; 20",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1728,
        "question": "The average of four consecutive even integers is 17. Find the integers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (IsInteger _smt3) (Equals (Times (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3)) 1) (Times 4 17)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Le _smt2 _smt3) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_3 _smt3))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-12",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1729,
        "question": "the sum of an even integer and twice the next greater even integer is eight more than four times the greater integer. find the lesser integer.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "24; 25; 26",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1730,
        "question": "Find three consecutive integers such that the sum of twice the smallest and 3 times the largest is 126.",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Equals 126 (Plus (Times 2 _smt0) (Times 3 _smt2))) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "11; 13; 15",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1731,
        "question": "Find three consecutive odd integers such that the sum of the least integer and the greatest integer is 13 more than the middle integer.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (IsInteger (Min (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (IsInteger (Max (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Equals (Plus 13 _smt1) (Plus (Min (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Max (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)))) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-5",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1732,
        "question": "Nine more than four times a number is the same as one less than twice the number. Find the number.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 _smt0) (Equals (Plus 9 (Times 4 _smt0)) (Minus (Times 2 _smt0) 1)))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{14; 6} or {-6; -14}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1733,
        "question": "the product of two integers is 84. one integer is 8 more than the other. what are the two integers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{32; 34} or {0; 2}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1734,
        "question": "The product of two consecutive even integers x and y is 34 less than 17 times their sum. Find the two integers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "7n",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1735,
        "question": "what is the sum of 7 consecutive even integers if the middle integer is n",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-53; -52",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1736,
        "question": "which 2 consecutive integers have a sum of -105",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus _smt0 _smt1) (Minus 0 105)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-11;-10",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1737,
        "question": "The sum of two consecutive integers is -21. Find the two integers",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-36;-35",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1738,
        "question": "the sum of two consecutive integers is -71. what are those integers",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus _smt0 _smt1) (Minus 0 71)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "3; 4; 5",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1740,
        "question": "find 3 consecutive integers such that the product of all 3, decreased by the cube of the first, is 33",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Equals 33 (Minus (Product (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Pow _smt0 3))) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "12",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1742,
        "question": "Twice the sum of a number and 8 is 40. Find the number",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Times 2 (Plus _smt0 8)) 40) (Equals ?_x1 _smt0))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{16; 4}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1744,
        "question": "The product of two positive integers is 64. Determine the two integers if one number is 4 times the other.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals _smt0 (Times 4 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (LessThan 0 _smt0) (LessThan 0 _smt1) (Equals 64 (Times _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "5",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1745,
        "question": "what is the smallest of three positive consecutive odd integers if the product of the second and third integers is 63?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "20; 22; 24",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1746,
        "question": "Eight times the sum of three consecutive even integers is 108 more than 21 times the smallest of three integers",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "24; 12",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1747,
        "question": "One number is twice another number. When the larger is diminished by 10, the result is 2 greater than the smaller. Find the numbers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals _smt0 (Times 2 _smt1)) (Equals (Minus (Max (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) 10) (Plus 2 (Min (Elements _smt0 _smt1)))) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "3",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1749,
        "question": "The sum of two numbers is ten. Three times the larger number is three less than eight times the smaller number. What is the smaller number?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus _smt0 _smt1) 10) (Equals (Times 3 _smt1) (Minus (Times 8 _smt0) 3)) (Equals ?_x1 _smt0) (Le _smt0 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "14; 16; 18",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1750,
        "question": "what is twice the first of three consecutive even integers is ten more than the third. find the integers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "8; 10; 12",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1751,
        "question": "Twice the smallest of three consecutive even integers is four more than the largest. Find the integers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "0; 2; 4",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1752,
        "question": "Find three consecutive even integers, such that 7 times the middle integer is 10 more than the sum of first and third.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals (Plus 10 (Plus _smt0 _smt2)) (Times 7 _smt1)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-3; -1",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1753,
        "question": "The greater of two consecutive odd integers is eight more than three times the smaller. Find the two odd integers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-16; -14; -12",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1754,
        "question": "find three consecutive even integers such that the sum of the first and third equals the sum of the second and -14",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals (Plus _smt1 (Minus 0 14)) (Plus _smt0 _smt2)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "39",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1755,
        "question": "The sum of two numbers is 56. Their difference is 22. Find the larger number.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus _smt0 _smt1) 56) (Equals (Minus _smt1 _smt0) 22) (Equals ?_x1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "10; 12",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1756,
        "question": "The difference of the squares of two positive consecutive even integers is 44. Find the integers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Difference (Elements (Pow _smt0 2) (Pow _smt1 2))) 44) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (LessThan 0 _smt0) (LessThan 0 _smt1) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "5; 7; 9",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1757,
        "question": "Find three consecutive positive odd integers such that the product of the first and the third is 4 less than 7 Times the second",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (LessThan 0 _smt0) (LessThan 0 _smt1) (LessThan 0 _smt2) (Equals (Minus (Times 7 _smt1) 4) (Times _smt0 _smt2)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "9",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1758,
        "question": "find the smallest of three consecutive positive integers such that the product of two smaller integers is 68 more than twice the largest integer",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 (Min (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Equals (Times _smt0 _smt1) (Plus 68 (Times 2 _smt2))) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (LessThan 0 _smt0) (LessThan 0 _smt1) (LessThan 0 _smt2) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "9; 11; 13; 15",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1759,
        "question": "find four consecutive odd integers such that the sum of the 4 is 3 more than 3 times the fourth integer",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (IsInteger _smt3) (Equals (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3)) (Plus 3 (Times 3 _smt3))) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_3 _smt3))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "15",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1760,
        "question": "find the larger of two consecutive integers if the second is 13 less than twice the smaller",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 (Max (Elements _smt0 _smt1))) (Equals _smt1 (Minus (Times 2 (Min (Elements _smt0 _smt1))) 13)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "29",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1761,
        "question": "the sum of four consecutive odd numbers is 128. Then the smallest number is?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3)) 128) (Equals _smt0 ?_x1) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Le _smt2 _smt3))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "2 or -5",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1762,
        "question": "when three times a number is added to the square of the number the result is 10. Find the number.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 10 (Plus (Times 3 _smt0) (Pow _smt0 2))) (Equals ?_x1 _smt0))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "1005006",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1763,
        "question": "What is the largest number which is the product of two positive integers whose sum is 2005?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-10; -9",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1764,
        "question": "Find two consecutive integers such that half the smaller plus three times the larger is -32",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "4; 5; 6",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1765,
        "question": "find three consecutive numbers whose sum is nine greater than the largest number",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Plus 9 _smt2)) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "18; 20; 22",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1766,
        "question": "3 consecutive even integers are given by x, x+2, and x+4.Find these three numbers such that the sum of the first, two times the second, and three times the third is 124.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-41; -40; -39",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1767,
        "question": "Find three consecutive integers such that the sum of the largest and 5 times the smallest is -244.",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Equals (Minus 0 244) (Plus _smt2 (Times 5 _smt0))) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "32;33;34",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1768,
        "question": "find the three consecutive integers whose sum is 99",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 99 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "48; 50; 52",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1769,
        "question": "What three consecutive even integers have a sum of 150?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) 150) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "81; 82; 83; 84",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1770,
        "question": "find 4 consecutive integers such that twice the sum of the two largest integers is 91 more than 3 times the first integer",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (IsInteger _smt3) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3)) (Equals (Plus 91 (Times 3 _smt0)) (Times 2 (Plus _smt2 _smt3))) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_2 _smt2) (Equals ?_x1_3 _smt3))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "7; 9; 11 or -5; -3; -1",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1771,
        "question": "Find three consecutive odd integers such that the product of the first two minus four times the third is 19.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals 19 (Minus (Times _smt0 _smt1) (Times 4 _smt2))) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "8; 10 or 0; 2",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1772,
        "question": "The product of two consecutive even integers is 10 less than five times their sum. Find the two integers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{16;7}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1773,
        "question": "Find two numbers whose sum is 23 and the difference of whose squares is 207",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "10 or -4",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1774,
        "question": "Six times a number subtracted from the number squared is 40. Find the number.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Minus (Pow _smt0 2) (Times 6 _smt0)) 40) (Equals ?_x1 _smt0))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "8 or -2",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1775,
        "question": "Sixteen less than a square of a number is the same as 6 times the number. Find the number.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 _smt0) (Equals (Minus (Pow _smt0 2) 16) (Times 6 _smt0)))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "40; 42; 44",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1776,
        "question": "find three consecutive even integers such that their sum decreased by the third is 82.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Minus (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) _smt2) 82) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "17",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1777,
        "question": "The product of three consecutive odd numbers is 6,783. What is the first number?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Product (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) 6783) (Equals ?_x1 _smt0) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "10;11;12",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1778,
        "question": "find 3 consecutive integers such that the sum of the first two integers is nine more than the third integer.",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Equals (Plus 9 _smt2) (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "47;48;49",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1779,
        "question": "Find three consecutive integers such that the sum of the least integer and the middle integer is 46 more than the greatest integer.",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger (Min (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Equals (Plus 46 (Max (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Plus (Min (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) _smt1)) (IsInteger (Max (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "6;8",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1780,
        "question": "find two consecutive even integers such that the smaller added to four times the larger gives a sum of 38",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "36",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1781,
        "question": "The sum of two consecutive integers is 73. Find the smallest integer.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus _smt0 _smt1) 73) (Equals ?_x1 _smt0) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "16",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1782,
        "question": "the sum of two consecutive numbers is 33. what is the smaller of these numbers",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus _smt0 _smt1) 33) (Equals ?_x1 (Min (Elements _smt0 _smt1))) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "7; 9; 11",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1783,
        "question": "find three consecutive odd integers such that 10 times the first when added to the third is equal to the square of the second",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "53",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1784,
        "question": "The sum of three consecutive odd numbers is 153. Which is the LARGEST number?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) 153) (Equals ?_x1 _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "10; 12",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1785,
        "question": "find 2 consecutive even integers such that twice the smaller is 16 more than one-third the larger",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Equals (Plus 16 (Div (Times 1 _smt1) 3)) (Times 2 _smt0)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "80; 82 or -64; -62",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1786,
        "question": "The product of 2 consecutive even integers is five thousand, one hundred two more than nine times their sum. What are the two integers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "28",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1787,
        "question": "The sum of four consecutive even integers is -100. Find the absolute value of the smallest integer",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3)) (Minus 0 100)) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (IsInteger _smt3) (Equals ?_x2 (Abs _smt0)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Le _smt2 _smt3))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "31; 32; 33",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1788,
        "question": "find three consecutive integers such that the sum of the first and the third increased by 8 is 40 more than the second.",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Equals (Plus 40 _smt1) (Plus (Plus _smt0 _smt2) 8)) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "4; 6",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1789,
        "question": "Find two consecutive positive even integers such that the square of the second integer summed with the first integer is 40.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (LessThan 0 _smt0) (LessThan 0 _smt1) (Equals 40 (Plus (Pow _smt1 2) _smt0)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "15; 16",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1790,
        "question": "Find two consecutive integers such that the sum of three-fifths of the first and one-fourth of the second is 13.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus (Div (Times 3 _smt0) 5) (Div (Times 1 _smt1) 4)) 13) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-2; -1",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1791,
        "question": "one integer is two times the next integer. find both integers.",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger (Next (Elements _smt0))) (Equals (Next (Elements _smt0)) _smt1) (Equals _smt0 (Times 2 (Next (Elements _smt0)))) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "6",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1792,
        "question": "find the smallest of four consecutive integers such that if twice the sum of the two smallest is added to three times the sum of the two largest, the result is 77.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 (Min (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3))) (Equals 77 (Plus (Times 2 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Times 3 (Plus _smt2 _smt3)))) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (IsInteger _smt3) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Le _smt2 _smt3))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-25; -24; -23",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1793,
        "question": "The sum of three consecutive integers is negative 72. Find the numbers",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Equals (Minus 0 72) (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "98; 99; 100; 101",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1794,
        "question": "Find four consecutive integers such that the sum of the second and the fourth is 200",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus _smt1 _smt3) 200) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (IsInteger _smt3) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_3 _smt3))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "6; 8; 10",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1795,
        "question": "Find three consecutive even integers such that the sum of the smallest integer and twice the second is 12 more than the third.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (IsInteger (Min (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Equals (Plus 12 _smt2) (Plus (Min (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Times 2 _smt1))) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "15; 17; 19; 21",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1796,
        "question": "The sum of the three smallest of four consecutive odd integers is 30 more than the largest integer.  What are the four consecutive odd integers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-3; -1; 1",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1797,
        "question": "Four times the sum of the first and third of three consecutive odd integers is one less than seven times the middle integer.  Find the integers",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals (Times 4 (Plus _smt0 _smt2)) (Minus (Times 7 _smt1) 1)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-10; -9; -8; -7",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1798,
        "question": "What 4 consecutive integers have a sum of -34",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "200",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1799,
        "question": "what number increased by 30% equals 260.",
        "semantics": "(Equals 260 (Plus ?_x0 (Div (Times 30 ?_x0) 100)))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "10/7 | 1.429",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1800,
        "question": "When 5 times a number is added to twice the number, the result is 10. Find the number.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 10 (Plus (Times 5 _smt0) (Times 2 _smt0))) (Equals ?_x1 _smt0))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-1;0;1 or 10;11;12",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1801,
        "question": "find three consecutive integers such that four times their sum is equal to the product of the larger two numbers.",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Equals (Times 4 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Times _smt1 _smt2)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-24",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1802,
        "question": "if the sum of a number and 7 is tripled, the result is 3 less than twice the number",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{26; 14}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1803,
        "question": "The sum of two numbers is 40. The sum of twice the larger and 4 times the smaller is 108. Find the numbers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 40 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals 108 (Plus (Times 2 _smt1) (Times 4 _smt0))) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "8; 3",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1804,
        "question": "One number is 5 more than another number. Three times the first plus twice the second is 30. Find the numbers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals _smt0 (Plus 5 _smt1)) (Equals 30 (Plus (Times 3 _smt0) (Times 2 _smt1))) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "22; 4",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1805,
        "question": "The difference between two numbers is 18. Twice the smaller number plus three times the larger is 74. What are the numbers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 18 (Minus _smt1 _smt0)) (Equals 74 (Plus (Times 2 _smt0) (Times 3 _smt1))) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{12; 3}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1806,
        "question": "The difference between two numbers is 9. The sum of twice the larger number and three times the smaller number is 33. Find the two numbers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "6 | 12",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1807,
        "question": "116 is divisible by how many numbers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x1 (Size _x0)) (IsInteger 116) (IsInteger _x2) (Equals (Mod 116 _x2) 0))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-19;-17;-15",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1808,
        "question": "Find three consecutive odd integers such that the largest increased by three times the second is 47 less than the smallest.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals (Minus (Min (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) 47) (Plus (Max (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Times 3 _smt1))) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{9; 13}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1809,
        "question": "One number is 4 less than another.  If 10 times the smaller number minus 3 times the larger number is 51, find the two numbers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{20;2}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1810,
        "question": "The difference of two numbers is 18. Twice the smaller number is 56 less than three time the larger. What are the numbers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 18 (Minus _smt1 _smt0)) (Equals (Minus (Times 3 _smt1) 56) (Times 2 _smt0)) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-12; -6",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1811,
        "question": "One number is 6 less than a second number. Twice the second number is 48 more than 5 times the first.find the 2 numbers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "1;3;5",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1812,
        "question": "The sum of the squares of three consecutive positive odd integers is 35. Find the integers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Sum (Elements (Pow _smt0 2) (Pow _smt1 2) (Pow _smt2 2))) 35) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (LessThan 0 _smt0) (LessThan 0 _smt1) (LessThan 0 _smt2) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{10; 4}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1813,
        "question": "one number is 6 more than another. If the sum of the smaller number and 3 times the larger number is 34, find the two numbers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "ans_no_result",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1814,
        "question": "find three consecutive integers such that the sum of the first and third is 63",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{22; 10}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1815,
        "question": "The difference of two numbers is 12. The sum of 2 times the greater number and 6 more than the lesser number is 60. What are the two numbers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "ans_no_result",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1816,
        "question": "Three consecutive integers are such that the square of the third is 76more than the square of the second.  Find the integers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "6",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1817,
        "question": "Twice the square of a positive integer is 12 more than 10 times that integer. What is the integer?",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger ?_x0) (LessThan 0 ?_x0) (Equals _smt0 ?_x0) (Equals (Plus 12 (Times 10 ?_x0)) (Times 2 (Pow _smt0 2))))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{4;3}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1818,
        "question": "Three times a larger number added to 4 times a smaller number totals 24. When twice the smaller number is subtracted from twice the larger number, the result is 2. What are the two numbers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "25",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1820,
        "question": "the sum of the two digit number is 7, when you reversed the number it was increased by 27. what is the original number?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "digits",
            "informal",
            "algebra",
            "sigmadolphin-dev"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "27",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1821,
        "question": "The sum of the digits of a two digit number is 9. If the digits are reversed, the number is increased by 45. Find the original number.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "digits",
            "informal",
            "algebra",
            "sigmadolphin-dev"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "ans_no_result",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1822,
        "question": "Find a 2 digit number whose tens digit is 3 less than the units digit.  The original number is 5 more than 4 times the sum of the digits",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "digits",
            "informal",
            "algebra",
            "sigmadolphin-dev"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-26",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1823,
        "question": "If 4 is added to a number and the sum is doubled, the result is 18 less than the number. Find the number?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "18",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1824,
        "question": "There is only one positive integer which is exactly twice the sum of its digits. What is the two-digit number?",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger ?_x1) (LessThan 0 ?_x1) (Equals (Times 2 (Sum (Elements _smt1_d5 _smt1_d4 _smt1_d3 _smt1_d2 _smt1_d1 _smt1_d0))) ?_x1) (Equals (Sum (Elements (Times _smt1_d0 1) (Times _smt1_d1 10) (Times _smt1_d2 100) (Times _smt1_d3 1000) (Times _smt1_d4 10000) (Times _smt1_d5 100000))) ?_x1) (Le 0 _smt1_d5) (Le _smt1_d5 9) (IsInteger _smt1_d5) (Le 0 _smt1_d4) (Le _smt1_d4 9) (IsInteger _smt1_d4) (Le 0 _smt1_d3) (Le _smt1_d3 9) (IsInteger _smt1_d3) (Le 0 _smt1_d2) (Le _smt1_d2 9) (IsInteger _smt1_d2) (Le 0 _smt1_d1) (Le _smt1_d1 9) (IsInteger _smt1_d1) (Le 0 _smt1_d0) (Le _smt1_d0 9) (IsInteger _smt1_d0) (Le ?_x1 (Minus (Pow 10 2) 1)) (Le (Pow 10 (Minus 2 1)) ?_x1))",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "digits",
            "informal",
            "algebra",
            "sigmadolphin-dev"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "12",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1825,
        "question": "Four times the difference of a number and six is equal to twice the number.  Find the number.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "3;5",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1826,
        "question": "Find two consecutive odd positive integers such that the twice the square of the larger minus the square of the smaller is 41.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "29",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1827,
        "question": "The sum of a two-digit number and its reverse is 121. The ones digit is seven more than the tens digit. what is the number?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Mod (Div ?_x0 1) 10) (Plus 7 (Mod (Div ?_x0 10) 10))) (Le ?_x0 (Minus (Pow 10 2) 1)) (Le (Pow 10 (Minus 2 1)) ?_x0) (Equals _smt0 ?_x0) (Equals 121 (Plus _smt0 _smt2)) (Equals (Plus (Times _smt1_d0 1) (Times _smt1_d1 10)) ?_x0) (Implies (And (Le (Plus (Times _smt1_d0 1) (Times _smt1_d1 10)) 9) (Le 1 (Plus (Times _smt1_d0 1) (Times _smt1_d1 10)))) (Equals _smt2 (Sum (Elements (Times _smt1_d0 1))))) (Implies (And (Le (Plus (Times _smt1_d0 1) (Times _smt1_d1 10)) 99) (Le 10 (Plus (Times _smt1_d0 1) (Times _smt1_d1 10)))) (Equals _smt2 (Plus (Times _smt1_d0 10) (Times _smt1_d1 1)))) (Implies (Le 1 (Plus (Times _smt1_d0 1) (Times _smt1_d1 10))) (Le (Sum (Elements (Times _smt1_d0 1))) _smt2)) (Implies (Le 10 (Plus (Times _smt1_d0 1) (Times _smt1_d1 10))) (Le (Plus (Times _smt1_d0 10) (Times _smt1_d1 1)) _smt2)) (Le 0 _smt1_d1) (Le _smt1_d1 9) (IsInteger _smt1_d1) (Le 0 _smt1_d0) (Le _smt1_d0 9) (IsInteger _smt1_d0))",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "digits",
            "informal",
            "algebra",
            "sigmadolphin-dev"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "40/3 | 13.333",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1829,
        "question": "I THINK OF A NUMBER IF I MULTIPLY IT BY 6 THE ANSWER WILL BE 80. what IS the number?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "95",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1830,
        "question": "76 is 80% of what number?",
        "semantics": "(Equals (Times 80 ?_x0) (Times 100 76))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-24",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1831,
        "question": "Twice the difference of a number and 6 is equal to three times the sum of the number and 4.  Find the number.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "5",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1832,
        "question": "The difference when 7 less than a number is subtracted from twice the number is 12. What is the number",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 12 (Minus (Times 2 _smt0) (Minus _smt0 7))) (Equals ?_x1 _smt0))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "7",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1833,
        "question": "if three is added to five times a number, the result is thirty-one more than the number. find the number..",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus 3 (Times 5 _smt0)) (Plus (Plus 30 1) _smt0)) (Equals ?_x1 _smt0))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "72",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1834,
        "question": "A two digit number exceeds the sum of the squares of the digits by 19 and double the product of the digits by 44. Find the sum of the digits of the number.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "digits",
            "informal",
            "algebra",
            "sigmadolphin-dev"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "1 or 2/3 | 1 or 0.667",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1835,
        "question": "When 3 times a certain number is added to twice its reciprocal the result is 5. What is the number",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 5 (Plus (Times 3 _smt0) (Div (Times 2 1) ?_x1))) (Equals _smt0 ?_x1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "4 or 3",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1836,
        "question": "The sum of a number and 12 times its reciprocal is 7. Find all numbers that meet this condition.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "45",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1837,
        "question": "a two digit number is 5 times the sum of its digits.  when 9 is added to the number the result is the original number with its digits reversed.  find the original number",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "digits",
            "informal",
            "algebra",
            "sigmadolphin-dev"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "8;9;10",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1839,
        "question": "find three consecutive integers such that 3 times the least is 4 more than twice the greatest",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-9;-7;-5;-3;-1",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1840,
        "question": "Find the five odd consecutive integers if the sum of the first and the fifth is one less than three times the fourth?",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3 _smt4)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (IsInteger _smt3) (IsInteger _smt4) (Equals (Minus (Times 3 _smt3) 1) (Plus _smt0 _smt4)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_3 _smt3) (Equals ?_x0_4 _smt4))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-9;-7;-5;-3;-1",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1841,
        "question": "Find 5 consecutive odd integers such that the sum of the first and the fifth is one less than 3 times the fourth.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3 _smt4)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (IsInteger _smt3) (IsInteger _smt4) (Equals (Minus (Times 3 _smt3) 1) (Plus _smt0 _smt4)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_3 _smt3) (Equals ?_x0_4 _smt4))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "30 or 41 or 52 or 63 or 74 or 85 or 96",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1842,
        "question": "In a two-digit number, the ten's digit is 3 more than the one's digit. If the digits are reversed, the difference between the two numbers is 27. Find the number.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "digits",
            "informal",
            "algebra",
            "sigmadolphin-dev"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-2;0;2",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1844,
        "question": "Find three consecutive even integers such that five times the second equals twice the sum of the first and the third?",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals (Times 2 (Plus _smt0 _smt2)) (Times 5 _smt1)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "17 or 71",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1845,
        "question": "It is an odd two-digit number, the sum of its digits is 8, the sum of the squares of its digits is 50. What is it?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "digits",
            "informal",
            "algebra",
            "sigmadolphin-dev"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "123 or 234 or 345 or 456 or 567 or 678 or 789",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1846,
        "question": "The tens digit of a three-digit number exceeds the hundreds digit by the same amount that the units digit exceeds the tens digit.  When the digits are reversed, the new number exceeds the original number by 198.  Find the original number.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "digits",
            "informal",
            "algebra",
            "sigmadolphin-dev"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-17;-16;-15",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1847,
        "question": "Given three consecutive integers.  When half the second integer is subtracted from twice the first one the result is eleven less than the third one.  Find the three integers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-3/4 | -0.75",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1848,
        "question": "if 1/3 is added to the reciprocal of a number , the result is 3 more than 3 times the reciprocal of the original number. find the number",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 _smt0) (Equals (Plus (Div 1 3) (Div 1 _smt0)) (Plus 3 (Div (Times 3 1) _smt0))))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "14; 62 or -10; -58 | 14; 62 | -10; -58",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1849,
        "question": "The difference of two numbers is 48.  The second is 8 less than 5 times the first. What are the two numbers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "35",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1850,
        "question": "a two-digit number is equal to 7 times the units digit. if 18 is added to the number, its digits are reversed. find the number.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 _smt0) (Le _smt0 (Minus (Pow 10 2) 1)) (Le (Pow 10 (Minus 2 1)) _smt0) (Equals _smt0 (Times 7 (Mod (Div _smt0 1) 10))))",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "digits",
            "informal",
            "algebra",
            "sigmadolphin-dev"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "6; 8; 10; 12",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1851,
        "question": "Find 4 consecutive even integers where the product of the two smaller numbers is 72 less than the product of the two larger numbers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (IsInteger _smt3) (Equals (Minus (Times _smt2 _smt3) 72) (Times _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Le _smt2 _smt3) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_3 _smt3))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "25",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1852,
        "question": "The sum of the digits of a 2-digit number is 7. If 27 is added to the number, the result is expressed by the digits in reverse order. Find the number",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "digits",
            "informal",
            "algebra",
            "sigmadolphin-dev"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{2; 30}; {4; 15}; {5; 12} | 2; 30; {4; 15}; {5; 12} | 2; 30; 4; 15; 5; 12",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1853,
        "question": "The products of three pairs of numbers are equal. One number in the second pair is 2 bigger, and one in the third pair is 3 bigger, than the first number in the first pair. The other numbers in the second and third pairs are respectively 15 and 18 less than second number of the first pair. Find each pair.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "9 or -8 | {9; -8}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1854,
        "question": "A number is 72 less than its square. Find all such numbers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals _smt0 (Minus (Pow _smt0 2) 72)) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "25",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1855,
        "question": "If the average of ten consecutive odd integers is 20, what is the average of the last five of those integers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Times (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3 _smt4 _smt5 _smt6 _smt7 _smt8 _smt9)) 1) (Times 10 20)) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3 _smt4 _smt5 _smt6 _smt7 _smt8 _smt9)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (IsInteger _smt3) (IsInteger _smt4) (IsInteger _smt5) (IsInteger _smt6) (IsInteger _smt7) (IsInteger _smt8) (IsInteger _smt9) (Equals (Times (Sum (Elements _smt5 _smt6 _smt7 _smt8 _smt9)) 1) (Times 5 ?_x2)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Le _smt2 _smt3) (Le _smt3 _smt4) (Le _smt4 _smt5) (Le _smt5 _smt6) (Le _smt6 _smt7) (Le _smt7 _smt8) (Le _smt8 _smt9))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "20; 22; 24",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1856,
        "question": "three consecutive even integers are such that the sum of the smallest and 3 times the second is 38 more than twice the third. what are the integers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals (Plus 38 (Times 2 _smt2)) (Plus (Min (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Times 3 _smt1))) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-11",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1858,
        "question": "two consecutive odd numbers total -20. Find the smaller.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Minus 0 20) (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals ?_x1 _smt0) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "10 or -10",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1859,
        "question": "The sum of half a number and its reciprocal is the same as 51 divided by the number. Find the number.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 _smt0) (Not (Equals _smt0 0)) (Equals 51 (Times _smt0 (Plus (Times 0.5 _smt0) (Div 1 _smt0)))))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-4",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1860,
        "question": "Three times the sum of twice a number and five is equal to five less than the number.  What is the number?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 _smt0) (Equals (Minus _smt0 5) (Times 3 (Plus (Times 2 _smt0) 5))))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{11; 8}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1861,
        "question": "Two numbers differ by 3. The sum of the larger and one fourth the smaller is 13. What are the numbers??",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus _smt1 (Div (Times 1 _smt0) 4)) 13) (Equals 3 (Minus _smt1 _smt0)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "74",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1863,
        "question": "the tens digit of a two-digit number is 3 more than the units digit. the number is 8 more than six times the sum of the digits. What is the number?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 (Plus 8 (Times 6 (Plus _smt1_d1 _smt1_d0)))) (Le (Plus 8 (Times 6 (Plus _smt1_d1 _smt1_d0))) (Minus (Pow 10 2) 1)) (Le (Pow 10 (Minus 2 1)) (Plus 8 (Times 6 (Plus _smt1_d1 _smt1_d0)))) (Equals (Mod (Div (Plus 8 (Times 6 (Plus _smt1_d1 _smt1_d0))) 10) 10) (Plus 3 (Mod (Div (Plus 8 (Times 6 (Plus _smt1_d1 _smt1_d0))) 1) 10))) (Equals (Plus (Times _smt1_d0 1) (Times _smt1_d1 10)) (Plus 8 (Times 6 (Plus _smt1_d1 _smt1_d0)))) (Le 0 _smt1_d1) (Le _smt1_d1 9) (IsInteger _smt1_d1) (Le 0 _smt1_d0) (Le _smt1_d0 9) (IsInteger _smt1_d0))",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "digits",
            "informal",
            "algebra",
            "sigmadolphin-dev"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "10; 12; 14",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1864,
        "question": "Find three consecutive even numbers such that the sum of the smallest and twice the second is 20 more than the third.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Equals (Plus 20 _smt2) (Plus (Min (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Times 2 _smt1))) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "8; 10",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1865,
        "question": "If three times the smaller of two consecutive even integers is added to the larger, the result is 4 more than three times the larger. Find the two numbers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "15",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1866,
        "question": "I think of a number. I multiply the number by 5 and minus 60. I end up with the number i started with.What is my number?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "9",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1867,
        "question": "find a number whose product with 6 is the same as its sum with 45.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "5",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1868,
        "question": "Frida is thinking of number. She adds 15 to her number and finds that the result is 4 times her number. What is her number?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "3",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1869,
        "question": "Six more than a number is 3 times the number. What is the number?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 _smt0) (Equals (Times 3 _smt0) (Plus 6 _smt0)))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-632; -125",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1870,
        "question": "If a and b are the roots of x^2+8x-5=0, find the values of a^3+b^3 and a^3*b^3.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "10100",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1871,
        "question": "what is the sum of the first 100 even numbers",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "1683",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1872,
        "question": "Find the sum of all the multiples of three between 1 and 100.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 (Sum _x1)) (LessThan 0 _x2) (IsInteger _x2) (IsInteger 3) (Equals (Mod _x2 3) 0) (LessThan 1 _x2) (LessThan _x2 100))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "13 or -13",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1873,
        "question": "If a^2 + b^2 + c^2 = 99, and ab + bc + ac = 35, find the value of a + b + c.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 99 (Plus (Plus (Pow a 2) (Pow b 2)) (Pow c 2))) (Equals 35 (Plus (Plus (Times a b) (Times b c)) (Times a c))) (Equals ?_x0 (Plus (Plus a b) c)))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "15",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1874,
        "question": "If a-b=b-3=6, what is the value of a?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "456",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1875,
        "question": "a three-digit number satisfies the following conditions: the digits are consecutive whole numbers; the sum of the digits is greater than 10 and less than 20; and the tens digit is an odd number. What is the number?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "digits",
            "informal",
            "algebra",
            "sigmadolphin-dev"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "4",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1876,
        "question": "Given that a + b = 10 and a^2 - b^2 = 40, find the value of a - b.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus a b) 10) (Equals 40 (Minus (Pow a 2) (Pow b 2))) (Equals ?_x0 (Minus a b)))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-84",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1877,
        "question": "The quotient of a number and -7, decreased by 2, is 10. Find the number.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Minus (Div _smt0 (Minus 0 7)) 2) 10) (Equals ?_x1 _smt0))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "81",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1878,
        "question": "Nine less than the quotient of a number and 3 is 18. Find the number.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Minus (Div _smt0 3) 9) 18) (Equals ?_x1 _smt0))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "25/2 | 12.5",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1879,
        "question": "The sum of a number plus half of itself is 18.75. Find the number.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 _smt0) (Equals 18.75 (Plus _smt0 (Times 0.5 _smt0))))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "19/18 | 1.056",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1880,
        "question": "The sum of 1/9, 2/3, and 5/18 is?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "34",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1881,
        "question": "What number is 17% of 200.",
        "semantics": "(Equals (Times 17 200) (Times 100 ?_x0))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "9",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1882,
        "question": "Find the number that is 27 greater than twice the opposite of itself.",
        "semantics": "(Equals ?_x0 (Plus 27 (Times 2 (Minus 0 ?_x0))))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "59",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1883,
        "question": "If A denotes the sum of even integers from 2 to 118 inclusive, and B denotes the sum of odd integers from 3 to 119 inclusive, what is the value of B-A?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{5; -6}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1884,
        "question": "Find two integers such that their sum is -1 and the sum of their squares is 61.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus _smt0 _smt1) (Minus 0 1)) (Equals (Plus (Pow _smt0 2) (Pow _smt1 2)) 61) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "49",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1885,
        "question": "the sum of the digits of a two digit number is 13. The number is 4 more than 5 times the unit digit. find the number.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus _smt1_d1 _smt1_d0) 13) (Equals (Plus (Times _smt1_d0 1) (Times _smt1_d1 10)) (Plus 4 (Times 5 (Mod (Div (Plus (Times _smt1_d0 1) (Times _smt1_d1 10)) 1) 10)))) (Equals ?_x1 (Plus (Times _smt1_d0 1) (Times _smt1_d1 10))) (Le (Plus (Times _smt1_d0 1) (Times _smt1_d1 10)) (Minus (Pow 10 2) 1)) (Le (Pow 10 (Minus 2 1)) (Plus (Times _smt1_d0 1) (Times _smt1_d1 10))) (Le 0 _smt1_d1) (Le _smt1_d1 9) (IsInteger _smt1_d1) (Le 0 _smt1_d0) (Le _smt1_d0 9) (IsInteger _smt1_d0))",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "digits",
            "informal",
            "algebra",
            "sigmadolphin-dev"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "125/324 | 0.386",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1886,
        "question": "If y varies inversely as the square of x and y=5 when x=2.5, what is the value of y when x=9?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-1; 0; 1",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1887,
        "question": "Find three consecutive integers such that five times the third integer equals twice the first integer plus seven more than the second integer.",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Equals (Plus (Times 2 _smt0) (Plus 7 _smt1)) (Times 5 _smt2)) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "7",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1888,
        "question": "If log 28 = log 4 + log x, what is the value of x?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "30",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1889,
        "question": "a number when increased by 40% becomes 42. what is the number?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "4900/13 | 376.923",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1890,
        "question": "what number increased by 30 % equals 490?",
        "semantics": "(Equals 490 (Plus ?_x0 (Div (Times 30 ?_x0) 100)))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "120",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1891,
        "question": "what is the sum of the first 15 counting numbers?",
        "semantics": "(And (LessThan 0 _x0) (IsInteger _x0) (Equals ?_x1 (Sum (Take _x2))))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-17/3 | -5.667",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1892,
        "question": "the sum of 6 times a number (N) and (4) is -30. what is the number?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 _smt0) (Equals (Minus 0 30) (Plus (Times 6 _smt0) 4)))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "9",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1893,
        "question": "If x + 3y = 12 and 2/3x - y = 5, what is the value of X?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Minus (Div (Times 2 x) 3) y) 5) (Equals 12 (Plus x (Times 3 y))) (Equals ?_x0 x))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "12",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1896,
        "question": "Six times the reciprocal of a number equals 2 times the reciprocal of 4. find the number?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 _smt0) (Not (Equals _smt0 0)) (Equals (Times _smt0 (Times 2 1)) (Times 4 (Times 6 1))))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "2442",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1897,
        "question": "What is the sum of the arithmetic sequence 174, 168, 162, ..., if there are 37 terms?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "14",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1898,
        "question": "If the sum of four consecutive terms in an arithmetic progression is 28 and the sum of the square of each term is 216, find the sum of the 1st and 4th terms.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "436",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1899,
        "question": "I am a number between 400 and 500. My ones digit is 3 more than my tens digit. The sum of my digits is 13. What number am I?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 (Sum (Elements (Times _smt0_d0 1) (Times _smt0_d1 10) (Times _smt0_d2 100)))) (LessThan 400 (Sum (Elements (Times _smt0_d0 1) (Times _smt0_d1 10) (Times _smt0_d2 100)))) (LessThan (Sum (Elements (Times _smt0_d0 1) (Times _smt0_d1 10) (Times _smt0_d2 100))) 500) (Equals (Plus 3 (Mod (Div (Sum (Elements (Times _smt0_d0 1) (Times _smt0_d1 10) (Times _smt0_d2 100))) 10) 10)) (Mod (Div (Sum (Elements (Times _smt0_d0 1) (Times _smt0_d1 10) (Times _smt0_d2 100))) 1) 10)) (Equals 13 (Sum (Elements _smt0_d2 _smt0_d1 _smt0_d0))) (Le 0 _smt0_d2) (Le _smt0_d2 9) (IsInteger _smt0_d2) (Le 0 _smt0_d1) (Le _smt0_d1 9) (IsInteger _smt0_d1) (Le 0 _smt0_d0) (Le _smt0_d0 9) (IsInteger _smt0_d0))",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "digits",
            "informal",
            "algebra",
            "sigmadolphin-dev"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "12",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1900,
        "question": "if 7 is added to a quarter of a certain number, the answer is 10. what is the number?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 10 (Plus 7 (Div (Times 1 _smt0) 4))) (Equals _smt0 ?_x1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "64",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1901,
        "question": "The sum of the digits of a 2-digit is 10. If the digits are reversed the new is 18 less than the original. What is the answer?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "digits",
            "informal",
            "algebra",
            "sigmadolphin-dev"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "6",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1902,
        "question": "One half the sum of a number and 2 is equal to one third of the difference of three times the number and six.  What is the number?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 _smt0) (Equals (Times 1 (Difference (Elements (Times 3 _smt0) 6))) (Times 3 (Times 0.5 (Plus _smt0 2)))))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "88; 89; 90",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1903,
        "question": "Find the 3 consecutive integers with the sum of 267.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 267 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-3; -1; 1; 3",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1905,
        "question": "Find four consecutive odd integers so that the sum of smallest integer and the largest integer is the same as the sum of the four integers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (IsInteger _smt3) (Equals (Plus _smt0 _smt3) (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3))) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Le _smt2 _smt3) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_3 _smt3))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "20/9; 20 or 0; 0 | 2.222; 20 or 0; 0",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1906,
        "question": "Find two numbers so that twice their sum equals their product and one number is 9 times the other number. Enter the smaller number first.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "264/5 | 52.8",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1907,
        "question": "What is the product of 3+2/3 and 14+2/5?",
        "semantics": "(Equals ?_x0 (Times (Plus 3 (Div 2 3)) (Plus 14 (Div 2 5))))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "2/3 | 0.667",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1908,
        "question": "When the product of 1/3 and 1/2 is subtracted from the sum of 1/3 and 1/2, what is the difference?",
        "semantics": "(Equals ?_x0 (Minus (Plus (Div 1 3) 0.5) (Times (Div 1 3) 0.5)))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "6",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1909,
        "question": "What is the number x in 2+x/7 = 20/7?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-156",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1910,
        "question": "The sum of two consecutive integers is -313. Find the larger integer?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus _smt0 _smt1) (Minus 0 313)) (Equals ?_x1 _smt1) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "3; 12; 48",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1911,
        "question": "The first and second terms of a geometric sequence have a sum of 15, while the second and third terms have a sum of 60.  Use an algebraic method to find the first three terms.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "25 | 25 or -25",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1912,
        "question": "if the sum of lcm and gcd of 2 consecutive numbers is 157, what is the sum of these numbers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-5",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1913,
        "question": "If x + y = 4, and x + z = 9, what is the value of ( y - z)?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus x y) 4) (Equals (Plus x z) 9) (Equals ?_x0 (Minus y z)))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "728",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1914,
        "question": "How many positive integers less than 1,000 do not have 7 as any digit?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "digits",
            "informal",
            "algebra",
            "sigmadolphin-dev"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "6/65 | 0.0923",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1916,
        "question": "The sum of one half of a number, one third of that number, and one fourth of the same number is one tenth. What is the number?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 _smt0) (Equals 1 (Times 10 (Sum (Elements (Times 0.5 _smt0) (Div (Times 1 _smt0) 3) (Div (Times 1 _smt0) 4))))))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "9/16",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1917,
        "question": "If the numerator of a fraction is increased by 3, the fraction becomes 3/4. If the denominator is decreased by 7, the fraction becomes 1. Determine the original fraction.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "5; 6",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1918,
        "question": "Which two consecutive whole numbers is square root of 29 between?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-9 or 8",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1919,
        "question": "The difference of the reciprocals of two consecutive integers is 1/72. Find the smaller of the two integers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 1 (Times 72 (Difference (Elements (Div 1 _smt0) (Div 1 _smt1))))) (Equals ?_x1 (Min (Elements _smt0 _smt1))) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "40",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1920,
        "question": "the square root of the sum of two consecutive integers is equal to 9. find the smaller integer",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 _smt0) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals (Plus _smt0 _smt1) (Times 9 9)) (Le 0 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "765",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1921,
        "question": "Finding the sum of series. 3+6+12+24+...+384?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "6",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1923,
        "question": "The number A = 200420052006....2040 is formed by putting the consecutive integers from 2004 to 2040 together.What is the remainder when A is divided by 9?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "567",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1924,
        "question": "The digits of a three digit number are consecutive integers.  When the digits are reversed the resulting number is 198 larger that the original number. If the original number is an integral multiple of 7, what is the original number?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "closed",
            "digits",
            "informal",
            "algebra",
            "sigmadolphin-dev"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "9/14",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1925,
        "question": "The numerator of a fraction is 5 less than the denominator. If 1 is added to both the numerator and the denominator the fraction would become 2/3. Find the fraction.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "3; 5",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1926,
        "question": "The sum of the reciprocals of two consecutive odd integers is 8/15. Find the integers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Equals 8 (Times 15 (Plus (Div 1 _smt0) (Div 1 _smt1)))) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "9; 11; 13; 15",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1927,
        "question": "The sum of 4 consecutive odd integers is 3 more than 5 times the least of the integers. Find the integers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "5",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1928,
        "question": "What number can be subtracted from both the numerator and the denominator of 17/25 to form a fraction equal to 3/5?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "8",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1930,
        "question": "if x^64 = 64 then x ^32 = ?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Pow x 64) 64) (Equals (Pow x 32) ?_x0))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-dev",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{26; 17}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1931,
        "question": "The difference of two integers is 9. Five times the smaller is 7 more than three times the larger. Find the numbers.",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Equals 9 (Minus _smt1 _smt0)) (Equals (Plus 7 (Times 3 _smt1)) (Times 5 _smt0)) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{16; 19}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1932,
        "question": "Two numbers differ by 3. Four times the lesser diminished by three times the greater is 7. Find the numbers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{44; 35}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1933,
        "question": "one number is 9 more than the other number.  The difference of seven times the smaller number and two times the larger is 157.  What are the numbers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals _smt0 (Plus 9 _smt1)) (Equals 157 (Difference (Elements (Times 7 (Min (Elements _smt0 _smt1))) (Times 2 (Max (Elements _smt0 _smt1)))))) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "9; 47",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1934,
        "question": "The difference between two numbers is -38. Two times the smaller number minus five times the larger number is -217. What are the numbers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-3; 1",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1935,
        "question": "one number is 4 less than another. the difference  of twice the smaller and 5 times the larger number is -11. What are the numbers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{11; 7}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1936,
        "question": "The sum of two numbers is 18 and their difference is 4. What are the two numbers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{13; 9}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1937,
        "question": "Two numbers have a sum of 22. Their difference is 4. what are the two numbers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{22;12}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1938,
        "question": "Two numbers have a difference of 10 and the sum of 34.  What are the numbers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 10 (Minus _smt1 _smt0)) (Equals 34 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{25;13}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1939,
        "question": "The sum of two numbers is 38. Their difference is 12. What are the two numbers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{23;16}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1940,
        "question": "The sum of two numbers is 39 and their difference is 7. What are the numbers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 39 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals 7 (Minus _smt1 _smt0)) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{12;8}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1941,
        "question": "The sum of two numbers is 20. Their difference is 4. Find the two numbers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "17;12",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1942,
        "question": "one number exceeds another by 5, and their sum is 29; find them.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{365; 256}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1943,
        "question": "The sum of two numbers is 621, and their difference is 109. Find the two numbers",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "34; 21",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1944,
        "question": "Find two numbers whose sum is 55 and whose difference is 13.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 55 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals 13 (Minus _smt1 _smt0)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "12; 7",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1945,
        "question": "a number exceeds another number by 5. the sum of the numbers is 19. find the numbers",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus _smt1 5) _smt0) (Equals 19 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "3; 9",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1946,
        "question": "One number exceeds another by -6. The sum of the numbers is 12. What are the numbers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus _smt1 (Minus 0 6)) _smt0) (Equals 12 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "25; 14",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1947,
        "question": "Two numbers have a sum of 39. Their difference is 11. What are the two numbers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{5; -3}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1948,
        "question": "The sum of two numbers is 2. If one number is subtracted from the other, the result is 8. Find the numbers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 8 (Minus _smt1 _smt0)) (Equals 2 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{53; 11}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1949,
        "question": "Find two numbers whose sum is 64 and whose difference is 42.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 64 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals 42 (Minus _smt1 _smt0)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{39; 31}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1950,
        "question": "The sum of two numbers is 70. One number is eight more than the other. What are the two numbers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{36; 39}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1951,
        "question": "the sum of 2 numbers is 75. the larger number is 3 more than the smaller number. What're the numbers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals _smt1 (Plus 3 _smt0)) (Equals 75 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "17; 25",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1952,
        "question": "the sum of two integers is 42. their difference is 8 find the integers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "14; 16",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1953,
        "question": "if a number is 2 more than a second and their sum is 30, find the numbers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals _smt0 (Plus 2 _smt1)) (Equals 30 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{30; 20}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1954,
        "question": "the sum of two numbers is 50. The difference between these numbers is 10 then find the numbers",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{26; 38}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1955,
        "question": "the sum of two numbers is 64. the smaller number is 12 less than the larger number. What are the two numbers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{25; 30}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1956,
        "question": "The sum of two numbers is 55. The smaller is 5 less than the larger. What are the numbers",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals _smt0 (Minus _smt1 5)) (Equals 55 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{14; 21}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1957,
        "question": "the sum of two numbers is 35. if the larger number is 7 greater than the smaller number, find the numbers",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals _smt1 (Plus 7 _smt0)) (Equals 35 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{8; -8}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1958,
        "question": "The sum of two integers is zero. The difference of the same two integers is 16. What are the two integers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{25; 35}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1959,
        "question": "One number is 10 less than another number. If their sum is 60, what are the numbers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals _smt0 (Minus _smt1 10)) (Equals 60 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{14; 21}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1960,
        "question": "One number is seven less than another. The sum of the numbers is 35. Find the numbers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals _smt0 (Minus _smt1 7)) (Equals 35 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "40; 13",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1961,
        "question": "find two numbers whose sum is 53 and whose difference is 27. what is the larger number? what is the smaller number?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "72; 73",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1962,
        "question": "The sum of two consecutive integers is 145. Find the two integers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{22; 12}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1964,
        "question": "What two numbers have a sum of 34 and a difference of 10?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus _smt0 _smt1) 34) (Equals (Minus _smt1 _smt0) 10) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{16; 12}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1965,
        "question": "The sum of two numbers is 28.  Their difference is 4.  What are the two numbers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{20; 11}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1966,
        "question": "The sum of two numbers is 31.  Their difference is 9.  What are the two numbers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "13; 9",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1967,
        "question": "A+B = 22 and A - B = 4, so what is the value of A and B?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "702; 703",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1968,
        "question": "1405 is the sum of 2 consecutive numbers. What are they?",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals 1405 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{54; 36}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1969,
        "question": "the sum of two numbers is 90. their difference is 18. find the numbers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 90 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals 18 (Minus _smt1 _smt0)) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{36; 28}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1970,
        "question": "Find two numbers whose sum is 64 and whose difference is 8 .",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 64 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals 8 (Minus _smt1 _smt0)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{36; 12}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1971,
        "question": "The sum of two numbers is 48, and their difference is 24. What are the numbers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 48 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals 24 (Minus _smt1 _smt0)) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{55/2; 37/2} | {27.5; 18.5}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1972,
        "question": "The difference between two number is 9. Find the numbers, if their sum is 46.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{4; 7}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1973,
        "question": "One number is three less than another. Their sum is eleven. Find the numbers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals _smt0 (Minus _smt1 3)) (Equals 11 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "7; 8",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1974,
        "question": "Find two consecutive integers such that the sum of 2 times the first integer and 4 times the second integer is 46.",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals 46 (Plus (Times 2 _smt0) (Times 4 _smt1))) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "21; 22; 23",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1976,
        "question": "The product of three consecutive integers is 22 less than the cube of the middle integer. Find the integers.",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Equals (Product (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Minus (Pow _smt1 3) 22)) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "2; 4; 6",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1977,
        "question": "Find 3 consecutive even integers such that three times the second equals 4 more than the sum of the first and the third",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals (Plus 4 (Plus _smt0 _smt2)) (Times 3 _smt1)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "4; 6; 8",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1978,
        "question": "find three consecutive even integers such that the sum of the first and the third is 12 less than four times the second",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals (Minus (Times 4 _smt1) 12) (Plus _smt0 _smt2)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "20; 22; 24",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1979,
        "question": "Find three consecutive even numbers so that the sum of the first and third numbers is 22 less than three times the second number.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-2; -1",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1980,
        "question": "Four times the sum of two consecutive integers is equal to 2 more than 14 times the larger integer. Find the integers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-29; -27; -25",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1981,
        "question": "find 3 consecutive odd integers whose sum is -81",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Minus 0 81) (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-29; -27; -25",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1982,
        "question": "Find three consecutive odd integers whose sum is -81.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Minus 0 81) (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{3+sqrt(2); 3-sqrt(2)} | {(-1) * 2 ^ (1/2) + 3; 2 ^ (1/2) + 3} | {3 - 2 ^ (1/2); 3 + 2 ^ (1/2)} | 1.586; 4.414 or 4.414; 1.586 | {1.586; 4.414}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1984,
        "question": "FIND TWO NUMBERS SUCH THAT THEIR SUM IS 6 AND THEIR PRODUCT IS 7.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{17;59}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1986,
        "question": "The sum of two numbers is 76.  The second is 8 more than 3 times the first.  What are the two numbers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "18; 7",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1987,
        "question": "one number is 4 more than twice the second number. Their total is 25. Find the numbers",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{13; 65}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1988,
        "question": "The sum of two numbers is 78. If four times the smaller number is subtracted from the larger number, the result is 13. What are the two numbers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{10; 3}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1989,
        "question": "The sum of two numbers is 13.  The larger number is 1 more than 3 times the smaller number.  What are the numbers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 13 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals _smt1 (Plus 1 (Times 3 _smt0))) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{20/3; 76/3} | {6.667; 25.333}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1990,
        "question": "The sum of two numbers is 32; the larger number is 12 greater than twice the smaller.  What are the 2 numbers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "19; 8",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1991,
        "question": "One number is 3 more than twice a second number. Their sum is 27. Find the numbers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals _smt0 (Plus 3 (Times 2 _smt1))) (Equals 27 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "25; 10",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1992,
        "question": "One number is 5 more than twice another number. The sum of the numbers is 35. Find the numbers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals _smt0 (Plus 5 (Times 2 _smt1))) (Equals 35 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "14; 64",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1994,
        "question": "The sum of two numbers is 78.  The second is 8 more than 4 times the first.  What are the two numbers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "22; 72",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1995,
        "question": "The sum of two numbers is 94.  The second is 6 more than 3 times the first.  What are the two numbers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{23; 7}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1996,
        "question": "one number is 2 more than three times a second number. the sum of the two numbers is 30. find the two numbers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{725; 90}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1997,
        "question": "the sum of two numbers is 825.  Dividing the larger number by the smaller number yields 8 with a remainder of 15. What are the 2 numbers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "22",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 1999,
        "question": "The difference between a number and fifteen is seven. Find the number.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "23",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2000,
        "question": "A number subtracted from 17 gives the quotient of 48 and -8. Find the number.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "2",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2001,
        "question": "What is the sum of 1 and 1?",
        "semantics": "(Equals ?_x0 (Plus 1 1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "3",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2002,
        "question": "Twenty-one is three times the difference between four times a number and five. Find the number.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 _smt0) (Equals (Plus 20 1) (Times 3 (Difference (Elements (Times 4 _smt0) 5)))))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{12; 9}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2003,
        "question": "Three times the larger of two numbers is equal to four times the smaller. The sum of the numbers is 21. Find the numbers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Times 3 (Max (Elements _smt0 _smt1))) (Times 4 _smt0)) (Equals 21 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{12;10}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2004,
        "question": "The sum of two numbers is 22.  Five times one number is equal to 6 times the second number.  Find the numbers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 22 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals (Times 5 _smt0) (Times 6 _smt1)) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "2; 4; 6 | 2; 4; 6 or -12; -10; -8",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2005,
        "question": "Find three consecutive even integers such that if three is added to the second consecutive even integer, the square of the result is 49.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "7; 5",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2006,
        "question": "The difference of two positive numbers is 2 and the sum of their squares is 74. Find the numbers",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus (Pow _smt0 2) (Pow _smt1 2)) 74) (LessThan 0 _smt0) (LessThan 0 _smt1) (Equals 2 (Minus _smt1 _smt0)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "13; 7 or -7; -13",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2007,
        "question": "Two numbers differ by 6. The sum of the squares of the numbers is 218. Find the numbers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus (Pow _smt0 2) (Pow _smt1 2)) 218) (Equals 6 (Minus _smt1 _smt0)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "11;5 or -5;-11",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2008,
        "question": "two numbers differ by 6. if the numbers are squared and then added, the result is 146. what are the two numbers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "6; 7",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2009,
        "question": "Find two consecutive positive integers such that the sum of their squares is 85.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus (Pow _smt0 2) (Pow _smt1 2)) 85) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (LessThan 0 _smt0) (LessThan 0 _smt1) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "16; 4",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2010,
        "question": "the sum of the squares of two positive integers is 272. The difference of the two integers is 12. Find the two integers",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "8; 9 or -9; -8",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2011,
        "question": "The sum of the squares of the two consecutive numbers is 145. What are those two numbers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{10; 2}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2012,
        "question": "One positive number is 8 more than another. The sum of their squares is 104. find both numbers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals _smt0 (Plus 8 _smt1)) (Equals (Plus (Pow _smt0 2) (Pow _smt1 2)) 104) (LessThan 0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "11; 12; 13",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2013,
        "question": "Find three consecutive integers such that the sum of the twice the first, six times the second and three times the third is 133.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "9; 10; 11",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2014,
        "question": "5 times the sum of three consecutive integers is 150. What are the integers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "7; 8; 9",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2015,
        "question": "Three times the sum of three consecutive integers is 72. What are the integers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "31",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2016,
        "question": "Three consecutive odd counting numbers have the property that the sum of the largest and twice the smallest is 91. What is the middle number?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "7",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2018,
        "question": "If 3 is subtracted from four times a number, the result is 10 less than five times the number. Find the number.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Minus (Times 4 _smt0) 3) (Minus (Times 5 _smt0) 10)) (Equals ?_x1 _smt0))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "5",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2019,
        "question": "which value is a solution to 60+2x=12x+10?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "50",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2020,
        "question": "Phil found that the sum of twice a number and -21 is 129 greater than the opposite of the number, What is the number?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "9; 10 or -10; -9",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2021,
        "question": "Two consecutive integers are added together. The square of their sum is 361. What are the integers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "9; 10 or -10; -9",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2022,
        "question": "Two consecutive integers are added. The square of their sum is 361. What are the integers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "3; 4 or -4; -3",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2023,
        "question": "The Square of the sum of 2 consecutive integers is 49. Find the integers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "14; 16 or -16; -14",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2024,
        "question": "find the two consecutive even integers whose sum squared is 900",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "82",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2025,
        "question": "A number consists of two digits . THe digit at ten's place is 4 times the digit at unit's place. On changing the place of digits, the new number formed is 54 less than the original number. Find the number?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "3; 4 or -6; -5",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2026,
        "question": "Find two consecutive integers such that the sum of the first and the square of the second is 19",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals 19 (Plus _smt0 (Pow _smt1 2))) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "7; 8; 9 or -2; -1; 0",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2027,
        "question": "Find 3 consecutive integers such that the square of the first, decreased by 5 times the second is 9.",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Equals 9 (Minus (Pow _smt0 2) (Times 5 _smt1))) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "45",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2029,
        "question": "The sum of the digits of a two-digit number is nine. If the original number is doubled, the result is eighteen less than twice the original number reversed. What is the original number?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{49; 33}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2030,
        "question": "The sum of two numbers is 82. The larger number is 17 less than twice the smaller number. What are the two numbers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "37/5; 123/5 | 7.4; 24.6",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2031,
        "question": "Two numbers have sum of 32. If the second is five less than four times the first, what are the two numbers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{6; 10}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2032,
        "question": "The sum of two numbers is 16. Twice the smaller # is 2 more than the larger number.Find them.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{12;100}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2033,
        "question": "The sum of two numbers is 112. The greater of the two is 32 less than 11 times the lesser number. Find the numbers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 112 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals (Max (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Minus (Times 11 _smt0) 32)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{17; 11}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2034,
        "question": "The larger of two numbers is 5 less than twice the smaller number.  The sum of the two numbers is 28.  What are the numbers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Max (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Minus (Times 2 _smt0) 5)) (Equals 28 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{20; 28}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2035,
        "question": "The sum of two numbers is 48. Three times the smaller number is the same as 32 more than the larger. Find the two numbers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{21; 7}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2036,
        "question": "The larger of two numbers is 7 less than 4 times the smaller. Find the numbers given that their sum is 28.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Max (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Minus (Times 4 _smt0) 7)) (Equals 28 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "31; 58",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2037,
        "question": "Separate 89 into two parts so that the second part is 4 less than twice the first part?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{18; 82}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2038,
        "question": "The sum of two numbers is 100. Five times the smaller number is eight more than the larger. Find the numbers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 100 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals (Plus 8 _smt1) (Times 5 _smt0)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{5; 9}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2039,
        "question": "The sum of two numbers is fourteen.  The difference between two times the smaller and the larger is one.  Find the two numbers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{148/7; 27/7} | {21.143; 3.857}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2040,
        "question": "Grant is thinking of two numbers. He says that one of the numbers is six times the other number decreased by 2 and the sum of the numbers is 25. What are the numbers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{158; 82}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2041,
        "question": "The sum of two numbers is 240. The larger number is 6 less than twice the smaller number. Find the numbers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 240 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals _smt1 (Minus (Times 2 _smt0) 6)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{31/4; 17/4} | {7.75; 4.25}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2042,
        "question": "The sum of two numbers is 12. When one number is subtracted from three times the other, the result is 5. Find the numbers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 5 (Minus (Times 3 _smt1) _smt0)) (Equals 12 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "37; 20",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2043,
        "question": "Separate the number 57 into two parts so that the first number is three less than twice the second number.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{40; 22}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2044,
        "question": "The sum of two numbers is 62. Two times the lesser number is 4 more than the greater number. What are the numbers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 62 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals (Plus 4 _smt1) (Times 2 _smt0)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "17; 19",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2045,
        "question": "twice the greater of two consecutive odd integers is thirteen less than three times the lesser number?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "17; 19",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2046,
        "question": "twice the greater of two consecutive odd integers is 13 less than three times the lesser number",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "9; 11",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2047,
        "question": "Find two consecutive odd integers such that 5 times the first integer is 12 more than 3 times the second.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Equals (Plus 12 (Times 3 _smt1)) (Times 5 _smt0)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "17; 19",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2048,
        "question": "Twice the greater of two consecutive odd integers is 13 less than three times the lesser.  Find the integers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Equals (Times 2 (Max (Elements _smt0 _smt1))) (Minus (Times 3 _smt0) 13)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "9; 11",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2049,
        "question": "Find two consecutive odd integers such that six times the first equals ten more than four times the second.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Equals (Plus 10 (Times 4 _smt1)) (Times 6 _smt0)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{11; 13}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2050,
        "question": "Three times the greater of two consecutive odd integers is five less than four times the smaller. Find the two numbers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "15; 17",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2051,
        "question": "Four times an integer is 9 more than three times the next consecutive odd integer. What are two odd integers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "5;1 or 1;5",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2052,
        "question": "The sum of two numbers is six. The sum of the squares of the two numbers is twenty-six. Find the two numbers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{8; 10} | 10; 8 or 8; 10",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2053,
        "question": "The sum of two numbers is 18 and the sum of their squares is 164. Find the numbers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus (Pow _smt0 2) (Pow _smt1 2)) 164) (Equals 18 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{3; 9} | 3; 9 or 9; 3",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2054,
        "question": "Find two numbers that total 12 and whose squares total 90.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 12 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals 90 (Plus (Pow _smt0 2) (Pow _smt1 2))) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{12; 13}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2055,
        "question": "The sum of two numbers is 25 and the sum of their squares is 313. Find the numbers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus (Pow _smt0 2) (Pow _smt1 2)) 313) (Equals 25 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{7; 5}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2056,
        "question": "The sum of the two numbers is 12 and the sum of their squares is 74. What is the numbers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus (Pow _smt0 2) (Pow _smt1 2)) 74) (Equals 12 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{2; 4}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2057,
        "question": "The sum of two numbers is six. The sum of the squares of the two numbers is twenty. Find the two numbers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{8; 9}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2058,
        "question": "The sum of two numbers is 17 and the sum of their squares is 145. Find the numbers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus (Pow _smt0 2) (Pow _smt1 2)) 145) (Equals 17 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "8; 10; 12",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2059,
        "question": "Five times the first of 3 consecutive even integers is 4 less than the twice of the sum of 2nd and 3rd . find the three even numbers .",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{7;16}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2060,
        "question": "The sum of two numbers is 23.  Twice the larger number is 4 more than 4 times the smaller.  What are the numbers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 23 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals (Plus 4 (Times 4 _smt0)) (Times 2 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{4; 11}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2061,
        "question": "The sum of two integers is fifteen. Eight times the smaller is 1 less than three times the larger. Find the numbers.",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Equals 15 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals (Minus (Times 3 _smt1) 1) (Times 8 _smt0)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{6; 14}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2062,
        "question": "The sum of two integers is twenty. Five times the smaller integer is two more than twice the larger integer. Find the two integers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{41; 47}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2063,
        "question": "The sum of two numbers is 88. Three times the smaller equals twice the larger number, plus 29. Find the numbers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 88 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals (Plus (Times 2 _smt1) 29) (Times 3 _smt0)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{7; 11}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2064,
        "question": "The sum of two numbers is 18. Find the numbers, if three times the smaller is one less than twice the larger.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 18 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals (Minus (Times 2 _smt1) 1) (Times 3 _smt0)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{3; 7}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2065,
        "question": "The sum of two integers is ten. Three times the larger integer is three less than eight times the smaller integer. Find the integers",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Equals 10 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals (Minus (Times 8 _smt0) 3) (Times 3 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{18; 15}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2066,
        "question": "The sum of 2 numbers is 33. Three times one number is six less than four times the other. What are the two numbers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{3; 7}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2067,
        "question": "the sum of two integers is ten, three times the larger integer is three less than eight times the smaller integer. Find the integers.",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Equals 10 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals (Minus (Times 8 _smt0) 3) (Times 3 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{10;11}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2068,
        "question": "The sum of two integers is twenty-one. Six times the smaller integer is twenty-seven more than three times the larger integer. Find the integers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{7; 3}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2069,
        "question": "The sum of two integers is 10.  Three times the larger integer is three less than 8 times the smaller integer. Find the integers.",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Equals 10 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals (Minus (Times 8 _smt0) 3) (Times 3 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "1; 1/2",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2070,
        "question": "One number is two times another. Eight times the smaller is two more than twice the larger number. What are the two numbers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "52;53",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2071,
        "question": "The sum of two consecutive integers is 105. Find the integers.",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals 105 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "118; 119",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2072,
        "question": "The sum of two consecutive integers is 237. Find the two integers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "224; 225",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2073,
        "question": "the left and right page numbers of an open book are two consecutive integers whose sum is 449. find the page numbers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "17; 18",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2074,
        "question": "Find two consecutive integers whose sum is 35",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 35 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "9; 10",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2075,
        "question": "the sum of two consecutive integers is 19. what are the integers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "41; 42",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2076,
        "question": "Find two consecutive integers whose sum is 83.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 83 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "145; 146",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2077,
        "question": "Find two consecutive whole numbers whose sum is 291",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 291 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "273; 274",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2078,
        "question": "the sum of the numbers on two consecutive post office boxes is 547. what are the numbers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "47; 48",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2079,
        "question": "the sum of 2 consecutive numbers is 95. what are the numbers",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals 95 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "37; 38",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2080,
        "question": "two consecutive integers whose sum is 75.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 75 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "191; 192",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2081,
        "question": "find two consecutive integers whose sum is 383",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 383 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "11; 12",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2082,
        "question": "what are two consecutive numbers whose sum is 23",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 23 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "11; 12",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2083,
        "question": "two consecutive integers whose sum is 23",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 23 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "13; 14",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2084,
        "question": "Find two consecutive integers whose sum is 27",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 27 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "ans_no_result",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2085,
        "question": "the sum of two consecutive integers is 138. find the integers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "62; 64",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2086,
        "question": "find two consecutive even integers whose sum is 126",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 126 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "35;36",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2087,
        "question": "find two consecutive numbers whose sum is 71",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 71 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "1/2; -1 | 0.5; -1",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2088,
        "question": "Find two numbers a and b such that the sum, product, and quotient of the two numbers are all equal.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "5; 7; 9",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2089,
        "question": "Find three consecutive odd numbers if the square of the smallest is four more than the sum of all three?",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Equals (Plus 4 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Pow _smt0 2)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "56",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2090,
        "question": "Forty-two more than a number divided by four is equal to fifty-two more than the same number divided by fourteen. What is the number?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 _smt0) (Equals (Plus (Plus 50 2) (Div _smt0 14)) (Plus (Plus 40 2) (Div _smt0 4))))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-18; -16",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2091,
        "question": "The greater of two consecutive even integers is 20 more than twice the smaller.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "0; 2",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2092,
        "question": "the larger of two consecutive even integers is 2 more than twice the smaller. find the numbers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "87; 89",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2093,
        "question": "Find two consecutive odd integers whose sum is 176.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 176 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "27; 29",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2094,
        "question": "Find two consecutive odd integers whose sum is 56.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 56 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "27; 29",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2095,
        "question": "What are two consecutive odd integers whose sum is 56?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 56 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "41; 43",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2096,
        "question": "Find two consecutive odd integers whose sum equals to 84. list from least to greatest.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "27; 29",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2097,
        "question": "find 2 consecutive odd integers whose sum is 56",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 56 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "81; 83",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2098,
        "question": "two consecutive odd integers whose sum is 164",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 164 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "27; 29",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2099,
        "question": "The sum of two consecutive odd integers is 56. Find the two odd integers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "13; 15",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2100,
        "question": "Find two consecutive odd integers whose sum is 28",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 28 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "87; 89",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2101,
        "question": "Please find two consecutive odd integers whose sum is 176",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 176 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "43; 45",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2102,
        "question": "What two consecutive odd integers have a sum of 88?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus _smt0 _smt1) 88) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "11; 13",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2103,
        "question": "The sum of two consecutive odd integers is 24. Find the integers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Equals 24 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "37; 39",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2104,
        "question": "if the sum of two consecutive odd integer is 76 find the number",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "11; 13",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2105,
        "question": "the sum of two consecutive odd integers is 24.  find the two integers",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "1; 2; 3",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2106,
        "question": "For three consecutive integers, the sum of 3 times the first integer and 2 times the second integer is 5 less than 4 times the third integer. What are the three consecutive integers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "8; 9",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2107,
        "question": "Find two consecutive integers such that the sum of 8 times the first integer and 7 times the second integer is 127",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals 127 (Plus (Times 8 _smt0) (Times 7 _smt1))) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "7; 8",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2108,
        "question": "If five times the smaller of two consecutive integers is added to three times the larger, the result is 59. Find the integers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "8; 9",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2109,
        "question": "Find two consecutive integers such that the sum of five times the smaller and three times the larger is 67",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "16; 17",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2110,
        "question": "Find two consecutive integers such that twice the first added to three times the second is equal to 83",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals 83 (Plus (Times 2 _smt0) (Times 3 _smt1))) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "5; 6",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2111,
        "question": "find two consecutive integers such that the sum of twice the first integer and three times the second integer is 28",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals 28 (Plus (Times 2 _smt0) (Times 3 _smt1))) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "5 or -4",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2112,
        "question": "The sum of the squares of two consecutive integers is 41. What is the larger integer?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 _smt1) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals 41 (Plus (Pow _smt0 2) (Pow _smt1 2))) (Le _smt0 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "8; 10",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2113,
        "question": "the greater of two consecutive even integers is six less than twice the smaller.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "4; 6",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2114,
        "question": "the greater of two consecutive even integers is six less than three times the lesser",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "12; 14",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2115,
        "question": "FIND TWO CONSECUTIVE EVEN INTEGERS SUCH THAT TWICE THE SMALLER IS 10 MORE THAN THE LARGER",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Equals (Plus 10 _smt1) (Times 2 _smt0)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "4; 6",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2116,
        "question": "The larger of two consecutive even integers is 6 less than 3 times the smaller. Find the integers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Equals (Max (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Minus (Times 3 _smt0) 6)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "8; 10",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2117,
        "question": "The greater of two consecutive even integers is six less than twice the smaller. Find the two numbers",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "22; 24",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2118,
        "question": "find two consecutive even integers that twice the smaller diminished by twenty is equal to the larger",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "30; 32",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2119,
        "question": "the greater of two consecutive even integers is 58 less than three times the smaller. find the integers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Equals (Max (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Minus (Times 3 _smt0) 58)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "4; 6",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2120,
        "question": "The greater of two consecutive even integers is 6 less than three times the less: Find the integers",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "18; 20",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2121,
        "question": "An even integer is doubled. The result is 16 more than the next consecutive even integer. Find the two integers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "22;24",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2122,
        "question": "Find two consecutive even integers such that twice the smaller diminished by twenty is equal to the larger.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "4; 6",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2123,
        "question": "Find 2 consecutive even integers such that the greater is 6 less than 3 times the lesser.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Equals _smt1 (Minus (Times 3 _smt0) 6)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "41; 42; 43",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2124,
        "question": "find three consecutive numbers whose sum is 126",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 126 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "28; 29; 30",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2125,
        "question": "The sum of three consecutive integers is 87. What are the integers?",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Equals 87 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "15; 16; 17",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2126,
        "question": "find three consecutive numbers whose sum is 48",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 48 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "31; 32; 33",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2127,
        "question": "find three consecutive integers whose sum is 96",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 96 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "1; 2; 3",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2128,
        "question": "Find three of the consecutive integer whose sum is equal to six. List answers from least to greatest?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "82; 83; 84",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2129,
        "question": "Find three consecutive integers whose sum is 249",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 249 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "29; 30; 31",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2130,
        "question": "find three consecutive numbers whose sum is 90",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 90 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "29; 30; 31",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2131,
        "question": "the sum of three consecutive integers is 90 find the three numbers by letting x represent the first integer and find the three numbers by letting x represent the second integer",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "111; 112; 113",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2132,
        "question": "find three consecutive integers whose sum is 336",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 336 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "56; 57; 58",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2133,
        "question": "Find three consecutive integers whose sum is 171",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 171 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "37; 38; 39",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2134,
        "question": "what are the three consecutive integers whose sum is 114.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 114 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "9; 10; 11",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2135,
        "question": "the sum of three consecutive integers is thirty. What are the numbers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "15; 16; 17",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2136,
        "question": "the sum of three consecutive integers is 48. what is the set of three consecutive integers that fits this situation",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "36; 37; 38",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2137,
        "question": "The sum of three consecutive numbers is 111. What are the three numbers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "104; 105; 106",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2138,
        "question": "Find three consecutive integers whose sum is 315",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 315 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "13; 14; 15",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2139,
        "question": "The sum of three consecutive integers is 42. Find the integers",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Equals 42 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "28; 29; 30",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2140,
        "question": "The sum of three consecutive integers is 87. Find the integers.",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Equals 87 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "13; 14; 15",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2141,
        "question": "The sum of which three consecutive integers is 42",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) 42) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "8; 9; 10",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2142,
        "question": "Find 3 consecutive integers whose sum is 27?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "20; 21; 22",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2143,
        "question": "Find three consecutive integers whose sum is 63.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 63 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "51; 53; 55; 57",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2144,
        "question": "The sum of four consecutive odd integers is 216. Find the four integers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "27; 29; 31; 33",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2145,
        "question": "Four consecutive odd integers have a sum of 120. What are the integers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (IsInteger _smt3) (Equals 120 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3))) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Le _smt2 _smt3) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_3 _smt3))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "51; 53; 55; 57",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2146,
        "question": "The sum of 4 consecutive odd integers is 216. Find the four integers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "101; 103; 105; 107",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2147,
        "question": "find four consecutive odd integers whose sum is 416",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 416 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3))) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (IsInteger _smt3) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Le _smt2 _smt3) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_3 _smt3))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "33; 35; 37; 39",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2148,
        "question": "find four consecutive odd integers whose sum is 144",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 144 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3))) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (IsInteger _smt3) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Le _smt2 _smt3) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_3 _smt3))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "81; 83; 85; 87",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2149,
        "question": "Find four Consecutive odd integers whose sum is 336.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 336 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3))) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (IsInteger _smt3) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Le _smt2 _smt3) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_3 _smt3))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "87; 89; 91; 93",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2150,
        "question": "Find four consecutive odd integers whose sum is 360",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 360 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3))) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (IsInteger _smt3) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Le _smt2 _smt3) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_3 _smt3))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "22; 23; 24; 25",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2151,
        "question": "Find four consecutive integers whose sum is 94.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 94 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3))) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (IsInteger _smt3) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Le _smt2 _smt3) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_3 _smt3))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "14; 15; 16; 17",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2152,
        "question": "find four consecutive integers whose sum is 62",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 62 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3))) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (IsInteger _smt3) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Le _smt2 _smt3) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_3 _smt3))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "107; 108; 109; 110",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2153,
        "question": "what are 4 consecutive numbers when totaled equal 434",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "27; 28; 29; 30",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2154,
        "question": "the sum of 4 consecutive integers of 114",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "4; 6",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2155,
        "question": "The greater of two consecutive even integers is 6 less than three times the lesser.  Find the integers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Equals (Max (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Minus (Times 3 _smt0) 6)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "27; 28",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2156,
        "question": "find two consecutive integers such that twice the first is 26 more than the second",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals (Plus 26 _smt1) (Times 2 _smt0)) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "17; 18",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2157,
        "question": "Find two consecutive integers such that twice the smaller is 16 more than the larger",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals (Plus 16 _smt1) (Times 2 _smt0)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "3; 4; 5; 6",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2158,
        "question": "Find a set of four consecutive positive integers such that the greatest integer in the set is twice the least integer in the set.",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (IsInteger _smt3) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3)) (LessThan 0 _smt0) (LessThan 0 _smt1) (LessThan 0 _smt2) (LessThan 0 _smt3) (IsInteger _x2) (Equals (Times 2 (Min _x4)) (Max _x3)) (IsInteger _x5) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Le _smt2 _smt3) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_2 _smt2) (Equals ?_x1_3 _smt3))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "15; 16; 17",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2159,
        "question": "The sum of three consecutive integers is 33 more than the least of the integers.  Find the integers.",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Equals (Plus 33 (Min (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "15; 16; 17",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2160,
        "question": "the sum of 3 consecutive integers is 33 more than the least of the integers. find the integers",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Equals (Plus 33 (Min (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "36",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2161,
        "question": "if one third of a number is 6 less than half of the number, what is the number?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Times 1 _smt0) (Times 3 (Minus (Times 0.5 _smt0) 6))) (Equals ?_x1 _smt0))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "36",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2162,
        "question": "find a number such that 6 more than  one-half the number is two-thirds the number",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 _smt0) (Equals (Times 2 _smt0) (Times 3 (Plus 6 (Times 0.5 _smt0)))))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "1584",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2163,
        "question": "A number when multiplied by 7/18 instead of 7/8 and got the result770 less than the actual result , find the original number?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "36",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2164,
        "question": "If one- third of a number is subtracted from three-fourths of that number, the difference is 15. What is the number?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 15 (Minus (Div (Times 3 _smt0) 4) (Div (Times 1 _smt0) 3))) (Equals ?_x1 _smt0))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "30",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2165,
        "question": "One Third of a number is 5 less than half of the same number. What is the number?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Times 1 _smt0) (Times 3 (Minus (Times 0.5 _smt0) 5))) (Equals ?_x1 _smt0))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-5; -3 or 13; 15",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2166,
        "question": "two consecutive odd integers such that 55 more than 5 times their sum is equal to their product.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "5;7 or -3; -1",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2167,
        "question": "find 2 consecutive odd integers, such that their product is 11 more than 2 times their sum.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Equals (Times _smt0 _smt1) (Plus 11 (Times 2 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)))) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "70; 71; 72",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2168,
        "question": "find three consecutive integers such that when twice the second is subtracted from three times the third, results in 74 ?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-10",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2169,
        "question": "Five times a number subtracted from 3 times the number equals 20. Find the number.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Minus (Times 3 _smt0) (Times 5 _smt0)) 20) (Equals ?_x1 _smt0))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "55",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2170,
        "question": "twice a number is 220 less than six times a number",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Times 2 _smt0) (Minus (Times 6 _smt0) 220)) (Equals _smt0 ?_x2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-1.5 | -3/2",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2171,
        "question": "twice a number is 12 less than 6 times the opposite of the number. What is the number?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 _smt0) (Equals (Times 2 _smt0) (Minus (Times 6 (Minus 0 _smt0)) 12)))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "5",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2172,
        "question": "three times a number is 10 less than five times the number. find the number",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Times 3 _smt0) (Minus (Times 5 _smt0) 10)) (Equals ?_x1 _smt0))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "11/4 | 2.75",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2173,
        "question": "eight times what number is 11 more than four times the number?",
        "semantics": "(Equals (Plus 11 (Times 4 ?_x0)) (Times 8 ?_x0))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "7",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2174,
        "question": "3 times a number is 7 more than twice the number? What is the number?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Times 3 _smt0) (Plus 7 (Times 2 _smt0))) (Equals ?_x1 _smt0))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "6",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2175,
        "question": "four times a number is 36 greater than the product of the number and -2. What is the number?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Times 4 _smt0) (Plus 36 (Times _smt0 (Minus 0 2)))) (Equals ?_x1 _smt0))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "9",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2176,
        "question": "Five times a number subtracted from seven times the number is a result of 18?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "8",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2177,
        "question": "six times a number equals 3 times the number , increased by 24. find the number",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Times 6 _smt0) (Plus (Times 3 _smt0) 24)) (Equals ?_x1 _smt0))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "137; 139; 141",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2178,
        "question": "Three consecutive odd integers whose sum is 417.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 417 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "11; 13; 15",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2179,
        "question": "The sum of 3 consecutive odd numbers is 39. what are the numbers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Equals 39 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "39;41;43",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2180,
        "question": "The sum of three consecutive odd integers is 123. Find the integers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals 123 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "35; 37; 39",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2181,
        "question": "find three consecutive odd numbers whose sum is 111",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 111 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "9; 11; 13",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2182,
        "question": "find three consecutive odd integers whose sum is 33",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 33 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "59; 61; 63",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2183,
        "question": "3 consecutive odd integers whose sum is one hundred eighty three",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus (Times 1 100) (Plus 80 3)) (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "77;79;81",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2184,
        "question": "if the sum of three consecutive odd integers is 237 then what are the integers",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals 237 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "33;35;37",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2185,
        "question": "find three consecutive odd integers whose sum is 105",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 105 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "11; 13; 15",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2186,
        "question": "The sum of 3 consecutive odd numbers is 39.Find the numbers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Equals 39 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "21; 23; 25",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2187,
        "question": "the sum of three consecutive odd integers is 69. Find the integers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals 69 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "11; 13; 15",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2188,
        "question": "the sum of what three consecutive odd numbers is 39?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) 39) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "77; 79; 81",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2189,
        "question": "If the sum of three consecutive odd integers is 237, then what are the integers",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals 237 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "ans_no_result",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2190,
        "question": "What are the three consecutive odd integers whose sum is 521?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "11; 13; 15",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2191,
        "question": "The sum of three consecutive odd integers is equal to 39. Write the equation that describes this situation and determine the three integers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "55; 57; 59",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2192,
        "question": "the sum of three consecutive odd integers is 171. what are the integers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals 171 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "89; 91; 93",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2193,
        "question": "find three consecutive odd integers whose sum is 273",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 273 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "39; 41; 43",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2194,
        "question": "Find three consecutive odd integers whose sum is 123",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 123 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "89; 91; 93",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2195,
        "question": "the sum of three consecutive odd numbers is 273. what are the numbers",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Equals 273 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "81; 83; 85",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2196,
        "question": "The sum of three consecutive odd integers is 249. Find the numbers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals 249 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "23; 25; 27",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2197,
        "question": "are there three consecutive odd integers whose sum is 75? if so, find them.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "65; 67; 69",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2198,
        "question": "The sum of three consecutive odd integers is 201.  Find the integers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals 201 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "31; 33; 35",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2199,
        "question": "what is three odd consecutive integers of 99?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "19; 21; 23",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2200,
        "question": "the sum of three consecutive odd integers is 63. Find the numbers",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals 63 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "23; 25; 27",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2201,
        "question": "find three consecutive odd integers whose sum is 75",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 75 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "82; 84; 86; 88",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2202,
        "question": "Consecutive even integers.  Find four consecutive even integers whose sum is 340.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "82; 84; 86; 88",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2203,
        "question": "Find four consecutive even integers whose sum is 340",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 340 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3))) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (IsInteger _smt3) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Le _smt2 _smt3) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_3 _smt3))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "28; 30; 32; 34",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2204,
        "question": "The sum of four consecutive even numbers is 124. What are the numbers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3)) (Equals 124 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3))) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Le _smt2 _smt3) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_3 _smt3))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "14; 16; 18; 20",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2205,
        "question": "find four consecutive even integers with the sum of 68",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 68 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3))) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (IsInteger _smt3) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Le _smt2 _smt3) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_3 _smt3))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "6; 7",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2206,
        "question": "Find two consecutive positive integers such that the sum of their square is 85.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus (Pow _smt0 2) (Pow _smt1 2)) 85) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (LessThan 0 _smt0) (LessThan 0 _smt1) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "6; 7",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2207,
        "question": "The sum of the squares of two consecutive, positive integers is 85. Find the integers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "ans_no_result",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2208,
        "question": "The sum of the  squares of two consecutive positive integers is 164. find the integers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "7; 9",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2209,
        "question": "The sum of the squares of two consecutive positive odd integers is 130. Find the two integers",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "4; 6 or -6; -4",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2210,
        "question": "the sum of the squares of two consecutive even integers is 52. Find the integers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus (Pow _smt0 2) (Pow _smt1 2)) 52) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "12;13",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2211,
        "question": "Find two consecutive whole numbers such that the sum of their squares is 313.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus (Pow _smt0 2) (Pow _smt1 2)) 313) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "13; 15",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2212,
        "question": "the sum of the squares of two consecutive odd positive integers is 394. find the integers",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus (Pow _smt0 2) (Pow _smt1 2)) 394) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (LessThan 0 _smt0) (LessThan 0 _smt1) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "6; 7; 8 or -7; -6; -5",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2213,
        "question": "Find three consecutive integers such that the product of the first integer and the second integer is 42.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Times _smt0 _smt1) 42) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "15; 16; 17",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2214,
        "question": "Find 3 consecutive integers such that 4 times the middle integer plus the largest integer is 9 less than 6 times the smallest.",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger (Max (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Equals (Minus (Times 6 (Min (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) 9) (Plus (Times 4 _smt1) (Max (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)))) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "12; 13",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2215,
        "question": "For two consecutive integers the sum of the smaller and twice the larger is 38. what are the integers.",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals 38 (Plus _smt0 (Times 2 _smt1))) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "13;14",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2216,
        "question": "Find two consecutive integers such that the sum of the first and 3 times the second is 55.",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals 55 (Plus _smt0 (Times 3 _smt1))) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "49",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2217,
        "question": "When the smaller of two consecutive integers is added to three times the larger the result is 199. Find the smaller integer.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 199 (Plus (Min (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Times 3 _smt1))) (Equals ?_x2 _smt0) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "15; 16",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2218,
        "question": "The sum of the smaller of two consecutive integers and twice the larger integer is 47. What are the integers?",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals 47 (Plus (Min (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Times 2 _smt1))) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "10; 11",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2219,
        "question": "when the smaller of two consecutive integers is added to three times the larger, the result is 43. Find the two integers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "67; 68",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2220,
        "question": "Find two consecutive integers such that the sum of the first and twice the second is 203",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals 203 (Plus _smt0 (Times 2 _smt1))) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "10; 11",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2221,
        "question": "Find two consecutive integers such that the sum of the smaller and twice the greater is 32",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "23;24",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2222,
        "question": "find two consecutive integers such that the sum of the first and four times the second is 119",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals 119 (Plus _smt0 (Times 4 _smt1))) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "19;20",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2223,
        "question": "For 2 consecutive integers, the result of adding the smaller integer and triple the larger integer is 79. What are the 2 integers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "9; 10",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2224,
        "question": "When the smaller of two consecutive integers is added to three times the larger, the result is 39. Find the integers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "10; 12; 14",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2225,
        "question": "find three consecutive even integers such that the sum of the smallest and twice the second is 20 more than the third",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals (Plus 20 _smt2) (Plus (Min (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Times 2 _smt1))) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "10; 12; 14",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2226,
        "question": "find three consecutive even integers so that the sum of the smallest integer and twice the second integer is 20 more than the third",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (IsInteger (Min (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Equals (Plus 20 _smt2) (Plus (Min (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Times 2 _smt1))) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "76; 78; 80",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2227,
        "question": "three consecutive even numbers add up to 234. find the three numbers",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "72; 74; 76",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2228,
        "question": "The sum of 3 consecutive even integers is 222. Find the numbers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals 222 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "22; 24; 26",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2229,
        "question": "The sum of three consecutive even integers is 72. Find the three integers",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "36; 38; 40",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2230,
        "question": "find three consecutive even numbers whose sum is 114",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 114 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "74; 76; 78",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2231,
        "question": "The sum of three consecutive even integers is 228. Find the integers",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals 228 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "8; 10; 12",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2232,
        "question": "The sum of three consecutive even integers is 30. Find the integers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "62; 64; 66",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2233,
        "question": "Find three consecutive even integers whose sum is 192.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 192 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "16; 18; 20",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2234,
        "question": "The sum of three consecutive even integers is 54. Find all three integers",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "11; 13; 15; 17",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2235,
        "question": "find four consecutive odd integers such that the sum of the first three exceeds twice the fourth by 5.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Plus (Times 2 _smt3) 5)) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (IsInteger _smt3) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_3 _smt3))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "ans_no_result",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2236,
        "question": "Find three consecutive even integers such that the sum of the twice the first, six times the second and three times the third is 133.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "6; 8 or -8; -6",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2237,
        "question": "Find 2 consecutive even integers whose product is 48.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 48 (Times _smt0 _smt1)) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "7; 9 or -9; -7",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2238,
        "question": "The product of two consecutive odd integers is 63. Find the integers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Equals 63 (Times _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "93; 95 or -95; -93",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2239,
        "question": "The product of two consecutive odd integers is eight thousand, eight hundred thirty-five. What are the integers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "14;15 or -15;-14",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2240,
        "question": "The product of two consecutive numbers is 210. Find the numbers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals 210 (Times _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{23; 25} or {-25; -23}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2241,
        "question": "The product of two consecutive odd integers is 575. what are the integers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Equals 575 (Times _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "8; 10 or -10; -8",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2242,
        "question": "Find two consecutive even integers whose product is 80",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 80 (Times _smt0 _smt1)) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "8; 10",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2243,
        "question": "The product of two consecutive positive even integers is 80.  Find the integers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (LessThan 0 _smt0) (LessThan 0 _smt1) (Equals 80 (Times _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "11; 13 or -13; -11",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2244,
        "question": "The product of two consecutive odd numbers is 143. What are the two numbers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "11; 13",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2245,
        "question": "Find 2 consecutive positive odd integers whose product is 143.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 143 (Times _smt0 _smt1)) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (LessThan 0 _smt0) (LessThan 0 _smt1) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "15; 17 or -17; -15",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2246,
        "question": "find two consecutive odd integers whose product is 255",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 255 (Times _smt0 _smt1)) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-7; -6",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2247,
        "question": "Find two consecutive negative integers such that the product is 42",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-10; -9",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2248,
        "question": "Find 2 consecutive negative numbers that have a product of 90",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 90 (Times _smt0 _smt1)) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (LessThan _smt0 0) (LessThan _smt1 0) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "3; 4 or -4; -3",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2249,
        "question": "product of two consecutive integers is 12. find the integers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-1",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2250,
        "question": "find the value of y in the following to make it an arithmetic sequencey+8, 4y+6, 3y",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "7; 3 or -6; -7/2 | 7; 3 or -6; -3.5",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2251,
        "question": "one number is 1 more than twice another number. the product of the two numbers is 21. What are the numbers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals _smt0 (Plus 1 (Times 2 _smt1))) (Equals 21 (Times _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{13; 4}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2252,
        "question": "the larger of two positive integers is five more than twice the smaller integer. The product of the integers is 52. What are the integers?",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (LessThan 0 _smt0) (LessThan 0 _smt1) (Equals (Max (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Plus 5 (Times 2 _smt0))) (Equals 52 (Times _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{4; 13}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2253,
        "question": "The larger of two positive integers is five more than twice the smaller integer. The product of the integers is 52. What are the two integers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{12; 5} or {-10; -6}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2254,
        "question": "A number is 2 more than twice another. Their product is 60. What are the numbers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals _smt0 (Plus 2 (Times 2 _smt1))) (Equals 60 (Times _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "15; 17; 19",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2255,
        "question": "Find three consecutive odd integers such that six times the sum of the first and second is 2 more than 10 times the third.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals (Plus 2 (Times 10 _smt2)) (Times 6 (Plus _smt0 _smt1))) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "9; 11; 13",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2256,
        "question": "find the consecutive odd numbers such that twice the sum of the first and second is one more than three times the third.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Equals (Plus 1 (Times 3 _smt2)) (Times 2 (Plus _smt0 _smt1))) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "5; 7; 9",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2257,
        "question": "three consecutive odd integers such that seven times the sum of the first two integers is three more than nine times the third integer.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "29; 31; 33",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2258,
        "question": "find three consecutive odd integers such that if six times the first is subtracted from the sum of twice the second plus five times the third, the result is 53",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 53 (Minus (Plus (Times 2 _smt1) (Times 5 _smt2)) (Times 6 _smt0))) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-29; -27",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2259,
        "question": "what two consecutive odd integers have a sum of -56",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus _smt0 _smt1) (Minus 0 56)) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-21; -19",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2260,
        "question": "The sum of two consecutive odd integers is -40. Find the integers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus _smt0 _smt1) (Minus 0 40)) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "58; 60",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2261,
        "question": "what are two consecutive even integers such that the sum of the larger and 3 times the smaller is 234?",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Equals 234 (Plus _smt1 (Times 3 _smt0))) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "12;14",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2262,
        "question": "find two consecutive even integers such that the larger, added to eight times the smaller, equals 110",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Equals 110 (Plus _smt1 (Times 8 _smt0))) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "30; 32; 34; 36",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2263,
        "question": "Find four consecutive even integers such that twice the least increased by the greatest is 96.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (IsInteger _smt3) (Equals 96 (Plus (Times 2 _smt0) _smt3)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Le _smt2 _smt3) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_3 _smt3))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "26; 28; 30",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2264,
        "question": "Three times the greatest of 3 consecutive even integers exceeds twice the least by 38.  Find the integers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals (Plus (Times 2 _smt0) 38) (Times 3 (Max (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)))) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "26; 28; 30",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2265,
        "question": "Three times the greatest of three consecutive even integers exceeds twice the least by 38. What are the integers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals (Plus (Times 2 _smt0) 38) (Times 3 (Max (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)))) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "40",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2266,
        "question": "The product of two positive consecutive odd integers is 399. The sum of these two integers is?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Times _smt0 _smt1) 399) (Equals (Plus _smt0 _smt1) ?_x1) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (LessThan 0 _smt0) (LessThan 0 _smt1) (Le _smt0 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "9",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2267,
        "question": "The sum of an integer and its reciprocal is 82/9. Find the integer.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 _smt0) (IsInteger _smt0) (Equals 82 (Times 9 (Plus _smt0 (Div 1 _smt0)))))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "3/2 or 2/3",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2268,
        "question": "What fraction when added to its reciprocal is equal to 13/6?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "19; 21; 23",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2270,
        "question": "Find three consecutive odd integers such that the sum of the first and the third is 7 greater than the second decreased by -14.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals (Minus (Plus 7 _smt1) (Minus 0 14)) (Plus _smt0 _smt2)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{32; 18}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2271,
        "question": "The difference between two numbers is 14 and half of their sum is 25. What are the numbers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 14 (Minus _smt1 _smt0)) (Equals 25 (Times 0.5 (Plus _smt0 _smt1))) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{16; 12}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2272,
        "question": "find 2 numbers with the mean of 14 and a difference of 4",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "3; 4",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2273,
        "question": "the sum of two consecutive integers is two less than three times the smaller number. Find the integers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "12; 14",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2274,
        "question": "the product of two consecutive even integers decreased by seven times the greater integer is 70.  find the two integers",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "19; 20 or -5; -4",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2275,
        "question": "The product of two consecutive integer is 80 more than 15 times the larger integer. find the two numbers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "4; 5 or -2; -1",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2276,
        "question": "The product of two consecutive integers is 5 more than three times the larger.  Find the integers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "4; 6; 8; 10",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2277,
        "question": "Find four consecutive even integers such that the sum of the first three exceeds the fourth by 8.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Plus _smt3 8)) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (IsInteger _smt3) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_3 _smt3))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "83",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2278,
        "question": "The sum of three consecutive positive integers is 246.  Find the largest integer.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) 246) (Equals ?_x1 _smt2) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (LessThan 0 _smt0) (LessThan 0 _smt1) (LessThan 0 _smt2) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "19",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2279,
        "question": "The sum of 3 consecutive integers is 54. What is the greatest of the three integers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) 54) (Equals ?_x1 (Max (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "15; 17; 19 or -19; -17; -15",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2280,
        "question": "The sum of the squares of three consecutive ODD integers is 875. Find the integers",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Sum (Elements (Pow _smt0 2) (Pow _smt1 2) (Pow _smt2 2))) 875) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "7; 8; 9 or -9; -8; -7",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2281,
        "question": "If the sum of squares of three consecutive integers is 194, find the integers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Sum (Elements (Pow _smt0 2) (Pow _smt1 2) (Pow _smt2 2))) 194) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "5; 7",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2282,
        "question": "two positive numbers are consecutive odd integers. the square of the smaller is 10 less than 5 times the larger. Find the integers.",
        "semantics": "(And (LessThan 0 _smt0) (LessThan 0 _smt1) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Equals (Minus (Times 5 _smt1) 10) (Pow _smt0 2)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "5;7",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2283,
        "question": "2 positive numbers are consecutive odd integers. The square of the smaller is 10 less than 5 times the larger. Find the integers",
        "semantics": "(And (LessThan 0 _smt0) (LessThan 0 _smt1) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Equals (Minus (Times 5 _smt1) 10) (Pow _smt0 2)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "15; 17; 19",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2284,
        "question": "The sum of the third and twice the first of three consecutive odd integers is 49. Find all three consecutive odd integers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "7; 9; 11",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2285,
        "question": "Find three consecutive odd integers suck that the sum of the greatest and twice the least is 25.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "8; 10; 12; 14; 16",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2286,
        "question": "the sum of one half of the first even integer, one third of the third even integer and one fourth of the fifth even integer is equal to 12. What are the 5 consecutive even integers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "20; 25; 30 or -10; -5; 0",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2287,
        "question": "find three consecutive multiples of 5 such that the sum of the squares of the first two is 125 greater than the square of the third.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "5; 6 or 0; 1",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2288,
        "question": "the product of two consecutive integers is 3 less than 3 times their sum. Find the integers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "7; 9 or -1; 1",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2289,
        "question": "The product of two consecutive odd integer is 1 less than 4 times their sum. Find the two integers",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "6; 8 or 14; 16",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2290,
        "question": "The product of two consecutive even integers is 106 less than 11 times their sum. Find the two integers",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "0; 1 or 7; 8",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2291,
        "question": "The product of two consecutive integers is 4 less than four times their sum. Find the integers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "7; 9 or -1; 1",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2292,
        "question": "The product of two consecutive odd integers is 1 less than four times their sum. Find the two integers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "5; 7",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2293,
        "question": "The product of two consecutive positive odd integers is one less than three times their sum. Find the integers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (LessThan 0 _smt0) (LessThan 0 _smt1) (Equals (Times _smt0 _smt1) (Minus (Times 3 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) 1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "11; 13 or -1; 1",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2294,
        "question": "the product of two consecutive odd integers is one less than six times their sum. Find the integers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Equals (Times _smt0 _smt1) (Minus (Times 6 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) 1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "3; 5 or -1; 1",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2295,
        "question": "The Product of two consecutive odd integers is 1 less than twice their sum.Find the integers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Equals (Times _smt0 _smt1) (Minus (Times 2 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) 1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "2; 3",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2296,
        "question": "The Product of two consecutive  positive integers is 1 more than their sum. Find the integers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Times _smt0 _smt1) (Plus 1 (Plus _smt0 _smt1))) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (LessThan 0 _smt0) (LessThan 0 _smt1) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "6; 8 or -6; -4",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2297,
        "question": "If the product of two consecutive even integers is 34 larger than their sum then what are the two integers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "4; 6",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2298,
        "question": "The product of two consecutive positive even  integers is 14 more than their sum. Find the integers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Times _smt0 _smt1) (Plus 14 (Plus _smt0 _smt1))) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (LessThan 0 _smt0) (LessThan 0 _smt1) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "5; 7 or -5; -3",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2299,
        "question": "What are two consecutive odd integers whose product is 23 more than their sum.",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Equals (Times _smt0 _smt1) (Plus 23 (Plus _smt0 _smt1))) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "8; 9",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2300,
        "question": "The product of two consecutive positive integers is 55 more than their sum. Find the integers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Times _smt0 _smt1) (Plus 55 (Plus _smt0 _smt1))) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (LessThan 0 _smt0) (LessThan 0 _smt1) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "7; 8 or -6; -5",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2301,
        "question": "The product of two consecutive integers is 41 more than their sum. Find the integers",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "5; 6 or -4; -3",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2302,
        "question": "The product of two consecutive integers is 19 more than their sum. Find the numbers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "3; 4 or -2; -1",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2303,
        "question": "The product of two consecutive integers is 5 more than their sum. Find the integers",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "10; 11 or -9; -8",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2304,
        "question": "Product of two consecutive integers is 89 more than their sum. Find integers",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "7; 8",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2305,
        "question": "The product of two positive consecutive integers is 41 more than their sum. Find the integers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Times _smt0 _smt1) (Plus 41 (Plus _smt0 _smt1))) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (LessThan 0 _smt0) (LessThan 0 _smt1) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "5; 7 or -5; -3",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2306,
        "question": "Find two consecutive odd integers whose product is 23 more than their sum.",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Equals (Times _smt0 _smt1) (Plus 23 (Plus _smt0 _smt1))) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "5; 6",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2307,
        "question": "the product of two consecutive positive integers is 19 more than their sum. what are the integers",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Times _smt0 _smt1) (Plus 19 (Plus _smt0 _smt1))) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (LessThan 0 _smt0) (LessThan 0 _smt1) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "6; 8 or -6; -4",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2308,
        "question": "if the product of two consecutive even integers is 34 large than their sum, then what are the integers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{155;31}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2309,
        "question": "One positive number is 5 times another number. The difference between the two numbers is 124, find the numbers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals _smt0 (Times 5 _smt1)) (LessThan 0 _smt0) (Equals 124 (Difference (Elements _smt0 _smt1))) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{63; 21}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2310,
        "question": "The difference between two positive integers is 42. One integer is three times as great as the other. Find the integers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals _smt0 (Times 3 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (LessThan 0 _smt0) (LessThan 0 _smt1) (Equals 42 (Difference (Elements _smt0 _smt1))) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "15; 5",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2311,
        "question": "one number equals three times another number. the difference between the numbers is 10. find the numbers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals _smt0 (Times 3 _smt1)) (Equals 10 (Difference (Elements _smt0 _smt1))) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "32; 4 or -32; -4 | 32; 4",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2312,
        "question": "One number is 8 times another; their difference is 28. What are the numbers",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "19; 57 | 57; 19",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2313,
        "question": "the difference between two integers is 38. one integer is three times as great as the other. Find the integers",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals _smt0 (Times 3 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Equals 38 (Difference (Elements _smt0 _smt1))) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "1905; 381",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2314,
        "question": "One positive number is 5 times another number. The difference between the two numbers is 1524, find the numbers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals _smt0 (Times 5 _smt1)) (LessThan 0 _smt0) (Equals 1524 (Difference (Elements _smt0 _smt1))) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-64; -32 | 64; 32",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2315,
        "question": "One number is twice another number. The larger number is also 32 more than the smaller number. Find the numbers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals _smt0 (Times 2 _smt1)) (Equals (Max (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Plus 32 (Min (Elements _smt0 _smt1)))) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{48; 24} or {-48; -24}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2316,
        "question": "One number is twice another number. The larger number is also 24 more than the smaller number. Find the numbers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals _smt0 (Times 2 _smt1)) (Equals (Max (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Plus 24 (Min (Elements _smt0 _smt1)))) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{-12; -4}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2317,
        "question": "the smaller of two numbers is thrice the larger. the larger number is 8 more than the smaller one. find the numbers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "2; 4; 6",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2318,
        "question": "find three consecutive even integers such that the largest is three times the smallest.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "11;13;15",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2319,
        "question": "Twice the smallest of three consecutive odd integers is seven more than the largest. Find the integers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "7; 9; 11",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2320,
        "question": "Twice the smallest of three consecutive odd integers is three more than the largest. Find the integers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "11;13;15",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2321,
        "question": "twice the smallest of three consecutive odd integers is seven more than the largest. determine the integers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "11; 13; 15",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2322,
        "question": "Find three consecutive odd integers such that twice the first is 7 more than the third",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals (Plus 7 _smt2) (Times 2 _smt0)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "225",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2323,
        "question": "one number is 5 times another number. the sum of the two numbers is 270. what is the number",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus (Times 5 _smt1) _smt1) 270) (Equals ?_x1 (Times 5 _smt1)))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "39",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2324,
        "question": "The sum of two numbers is 52.  The larger number is three times the smaller number.  Find the larger number",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus _smt0 (Times 3 _smt0)) 52) (Equals ?_x1 (Times 3 _smt0)) (Le _smt0 (Times 3 _smt0)))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "45",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2325,
        "question": "the larger of two numbers is 5 times the smaller number the sum of the numbers is 54 find the larger number",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "13",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2326,
        "question": "One integer is four times another. The sum of the integers is 65. What is the value of the lesser integer?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus (Times 4 _smt1) _smt1) 65) (IsInteger (Times 4 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger (Min (Elements (Times 4 _smt1) _smt1))) (Equals ?_x2 (Min (Elements (Times 4 _smt1) _smt1))))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "8; 10; 12; 14",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2327,
        "question": "Find four consecutive even integers so that the sum of the first three is 2 more than twice the fourth.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (IsInteger _smt3) (Equals (Plus 2 (Times 2 _smt3)) (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_3 _smt3))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "28; 29; 30",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2328,
        "question": "What are consecutive numbers where the 1st and 3rd equal 58?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "19; 20; 21",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2329,
        "question": "Find three consecutive integers such that the sum of the smallest and the largest is 40.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus _smt0 _smt2) 40) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "19; 20; 21",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2330,
        "question": "find three consecutive integers such that the sum of the first and the third is 40.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus _smt0 _smt2) 40) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "16; 18; 20",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2331,
        "question": "find three consecutive even integers such that the sum of the smallest and the largest is 36",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus _smt0 _smt2) 36) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "41; 42; 43",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2332,
        "question": "Find three consecutive integers such that the sum of the first and third is 84",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus _smt0 _smt2) 84) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "37; 38; 39",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2333,
        "question": "find three consecutive integers such  that the sum of the first and third is 76",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus _smt0 _smt2) 76) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "21; 22; 23",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2334,
        "question": "Find three consecutive integers such that the sum of the first and last is 44",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "20; 21; 22",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2335,
        "question": "Find three consecutive integers such that the sum of the first and third is forty two.",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Equals (Plus 40 2) (Plus _smt0 _smt2)) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "22; 24",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2336,
        "question": "The lesser of two consecutive even integers is 10 more than one-half the greater. Find the integers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Min (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Plus 10 (Times 0.5 _smt1))) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "12; 14",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2337,
        "question": "The smaller of two consecutive even integers is five more than one half of the greater.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "6",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2338,
        "question": "the smaller of two consecutive even integer is five more than one half of the greater.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "11; 13; 15 or -3; -1; 1",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2339,
        "question": "Find three consecutive odd integers such that the product of the first and second integer is 7 less than 10 times the third integer.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals (Minus (Times 10 _smt2) 7) (Times _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "26; 28; 30",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2340,
        "question": "Three times the greatest of three consecutive even integers exceeds twice the least by the 38. Write an equation and Find the integers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "22; 24; 26",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2341,
        "question": "Four times the smallest of three consecutive even integers is ten more than three times the largest integer. Find the integers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals (Times 4 (Min (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Plus 10 (Times 3 _smt2))) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "81; 82; 83; 84",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2342,
        "question": "Find four consecutive integers such that twice the sum of the two greater integers exceeds three times the first by 91.",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (IsInteger _smt3) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3)) (Equals (Plus (Times 3 _smt0) 91) (Times 2 (Plus _smt2 _smt3))) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_2 _smt2) (Equals ?_x1_3 _smt3))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "63; 65; 67",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2343,
        "question": "three consecutive odd integers are such that the square of the third is 264 more than the square of the second. Find the three integers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "45;47;49",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2344,
        "question": "Given three consecutive odd numbers such that the square of the second number is 192 less than the square of the third. Find those numbers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "5;7",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2345,
        "question": "Find two consecutive odd integers such that seven times the first equals five times the second.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Equals (Times 5 _smt1) (Times 7 _smt0)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "3; 5",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2346,
        "question": "Five times the first of two consecutive odd integers is three times the second. Find the integers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Equals (Times 3 _smt1) (Times 5 _smt0)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "5; 7",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2347,
        "question": "Seven times the first of two consecutive odd integers is equal to five times the second. Find each integer.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-150; -148",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2348,
        "question": "the sum of two consecutive even integers is -298. what are the integers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus _smt0 _smt1) (Minus 0 298)) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-40; -38",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2349,
        "question": "the sum of two consecutive even integers is -78. find the two integers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "28",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2350,
        "question": "The larger of 2 integers is one more than three times the smaller. If the sum of the two integers is 37, find the larger integer.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Max (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Plus 1 (Times 3 _smt0))) (Equals (Plus _smt0 _smt1) 37) (Equals ?_x2 _smt1) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Le _smt0 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "22",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2351,
        "question": "The sum of two numbers is 70. The larger number is 4 more than twice the smaller number. What is the smaller number?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus _smt0 (Plus 4 (Times 2 _smt0))) 70) (Equals ?_x1 _smt0) (Le _smt0 (Plus 4 (Times 2 _smt0))))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "11",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2352,
        "question": "one integer is 3 more than twice another integer. If sum of the two integers is 36, what is the smaller integer?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus (Plus 3 (Times 2 _smt1)) _smt1) 36) (Equals ?_x1 (Min (Elements (Plus 3 (Times 2 _smt1)) _smt1))) (IsInteger (Plus 3 (Times 2 _smt1))) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger (Min (Elements (Plus 3 (Times 2 _smt1)) _smt1))))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "17",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2353,
        "question": "the sum of two integers is fifty seven. Twice the smaller integer is six less than the larger integer.  Find the smaller integer",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus _smt0 _smt1) (Plus 50 7)) (Equals ?_x1 _smt0) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Equals (Minus _smt1 6) (Times 2 _smt0)) (Le _smt0 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "7; 8",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2354,
        "question": "Find two consecutive positive integers such that the square of the first decreased by 25 equals three times  the second.",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (LessThan 0 _smt0) (LessThan 0 _smt1) (Equals (Times 3 _smt1) (Minus (Pow _smt0 2) 25)) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "16; 18",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2355,
        "question": "Find two consecutive even integers such that 3 times the smaller is 12 more than 2 times the larger.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Equals (Plus 12 (Times 2 _smt1)) (Times 3 _smt0)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "44; 46",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2356,
        "question": "find two consecutive even integers so that three times the smaller is 40 more than two times the larger",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Equals (Plus 40 (Times 2 _smt1)) (Times 3 _smt0)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "12; 14",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2357,
        "question": "Find two consecutive even integers such that three times the lesser integer is eight more than twice the greater integer.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "8; 10; 12",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2358,
        "question": "Find three consecutive even integers such that two times the sum of the first and the second is equal to three times the third.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals (Times 3 _smt2) (Times 2 (Plus _smt0 _smt1))) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "6; 8",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2359,
        "question": "the sum of two integers is greater than 12, one integer is ten less than twice the other. what are the least values of the integers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "9; 10; 11; 12",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2360,
        "question": "find 4 consecutive integers such that the sum of the first three exceeds the 4th by 18.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Plus _smt3 18)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (IsInteger _smt3) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_3 _smt3))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "5; 6",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2361,
        "question": "Find two consecutive integers so that twice the square of the larger is 57 more than three times the smaller.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "4; 5; 6 or -1; 0; 1",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2362,
        "question": "find three consecutive integers such that four times the sum of all three is two times the product of the larger two",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "19;20",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2363,
        "question": "Find two consecutive integers such that 4 times the larger exceeds 3 times the smaller by 23.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Times 4 _smt1) (Plus (Times 3 _smt0) 23)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "19;20",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2364,
        "question": "find two consecutive integers such that 4 times the largest exceeds 3 times the smaller by 23",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Times 4 _smt1) (Plus (Times 3 _smt0) 23)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "19; 20",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2365,
        "question": "Find two consecutive integers such that four times the the larger exceeds three times the smaller by 23.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "3; 4",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2366,
        "question": "Four times the greater of two consecutive integers is 1 more than five times the lesser number.  Find the integers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "23; 24",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2367,
        "question": "find 2 consecutive integers where twice the smaller increased by 26 is equal to three times the larger.",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals (Times 3 _smt1) (Plus (Times 2 _smt0) 26)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "18; 19",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2368,
        "question": "3 times an integer is 41 less than 5 times the next consecutive integer. Find the two consecutive integers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-4; -2; 0",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2369,
        "question": "of three consecutive even integers, the sum of the smallest two integers is equal to 6 less than the largest. find the integers",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "103",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2370,
        "question": "There are 3 consecutive odd integers whose sum is 303. What is the value of the 3rd odd integer?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "25",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2371,
        "question": "The sum of three consecutive odd integers is 69. what is the largest of the integers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "9",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2372,
        "question": "The sum of three consecutive odd integers is 27. What is the middle integer?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) 27) (Equals ?_x1 _smt1) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "141",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2373,
        "question": "the sum of three consecutive odd integers is 417. what is the largest of the three consecutive integers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "13",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2374,
        "question": "3 consecutive odd numbers add up to 33. Which is the highest?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 33 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Equals ?_x1 _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "9;11;13",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2375,
        "question": "find three consecutive odd integers such that three times the second minus the third is 11 more than the first",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals (Plus 11 _smt0) (Minus (Times 3 _smt1) _smt2)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "5; 7; 9",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2376,
        "question": "find three consecutive odd integers such that three times the middle integer is seven more than the sum of the first and third integer.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals (Plus 7 (Plus _smt0 _smt2)) (Times 3 _smt1)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "9; 11; 13",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2377,
        "question": "Find three consecutive odd integers such that five times the middle integer equals 33 more than the sum of the first and the last.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "39; 41; 43",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2378,
        "question": "there are three consecutive odd integers and sum of smaller is 49 less than 3 times largest integer find the three odd integer",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "5; 7; 9",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2379,
        "question": "Find 3 consecutive odd integers such that the sum of the first and third integer is the sum of the second integer and 7",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals (Plus _smt1 7) (Plus _smt0 _smt2)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "41; 43; 45",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2380,
        "question": "find three consecutive odd integers such that the sum of the first and third equals the sum of the second and 43.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals (Plus _smt1 43) (Plus _smt0 _smt2)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "29; 31; 33",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2381,
        "question": "Find the three consecutive odd integers such that the sum of the first and third equals the sum of the second and 31",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals (Plus _smt1 31) (Plus _smt0 _smt2)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "11",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2382,
        "question": "The sum of an integer and three times the next consecutive integer is 47. What is the original integer.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 _smt0) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger (Next (Elements _smt0))) (Equals 47 (Plus _smt0 (Times 3 (Next (Elements _smt0))))))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "121; 123; 125",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2383,
        "question": "four times the smallest of three consecutive odd integers is 236 more than the sum of the other two integers. Find the integers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "11; 13; 15",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2384,
        "question": "Find 3 consecutive odd integers such that 3 times the smallest, is 5 more than the sum of the 2nd and 3rd.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals (Plus 5 (Plus _smt1 _smt2)) (Times 3 (Min (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)))) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-24; -22; -20",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2385,
        "question": "Find three consecutive even integers such that two times the sum of the first and the third integer is twenty-two less than the product of three and the second number",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals (Minus (Times 3 _smt1) (Plus 20 2)) (Times 2 (Plus _smt0 _smt2))) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "25; 27",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2386,
        "question": "find two consecutive odd number such that when smaller number is subtracted from 3 time bigger number, the result is 56.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "13; 15",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2387,
        "question": "Find two consecutive odd integers such that twice the larger is 17 more than the smaller",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Equals (Plus 17 _smt0) (Times 2 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "55",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2388,
        "question": "The sum of two consecutive integers 111. Three times the larger integer less two times the smaller integer is 58. Find the value of the smaller integer",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "3; 5",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2389,
        "question": "Find two consecutive odd integers such that the square of the first added to 3 times the second is 24.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Equals 24 (Plus (Pow _smt0 2) (Times 3 _smt1))) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "6;7",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2390,
        "question": "Find two consecutive positive integers such that the square of the smaller increased by 4 times the larger is 64.",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (LessThan 0 _smt0) (LessThan 0 _smt1) (Equals 64 (Plus (Pow _smt0 2) (Times 4 _smt1))) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "11",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2391,
        "question": "Find the largest of three consecutive odd integers such that the sum of the first two integers is five more than the third integer",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 (Max (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals (Plus 5 _smt2) (Plus _smt0 _smt1)))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "6; 7; 8",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2392,
        "question": "3 times the first of three consecutive numbers is 4 more than 2 times the second. what are the three numbers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "55; 57",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2393,
        "question": "Twice the lesser of two consecutive odd integers decreased by the greater integer is 53.  What are the integers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Minus (Times 2 (Min (Elements _smt0 _smt1))) _smt1) 53) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "13; 15",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2394,
        "question": "Find 2 consecutive odd integers such that three times the first minus the second equals 24",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Equals 24 (Minus (Times 3 _smt0) _smt1)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "13; 15",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2395,
        "question": "Find two consecutive odd integers such that three times the first minus the second equals 24",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Equals 24 (Minus (Times 3 _smt0) _smt1)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "9; 11",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2396,
        "question": "If the lesser of two consecutive odd integers is doubled, the result is 7 more than the greater of the two integers. Find the two integers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "3; 5",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2397,
        "question": "The greater of two consecutive odd integers is one less than twice the smaller.  Find the integers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "7; 9",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2398,
        "question": "3 times an odd integer is 12 more than the next consecutive odd integer",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "12; -15",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2399,
        "question": "the sum of two numbers is -3. if the second number is subtracted from the first, the difference is 27. find the numbers",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus _smt0 _smt1) (Minus 0 3)) (Equals 27 (Minus _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-7; 4",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2400,
        "question": "Two integers have a difference of -11 and a sum of -3. What are the integers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{-2; -7}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2401,
        "question": "two integers have a sum of -9 and a difference of 5. What are the integers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus _smt0 _smt1) (Minus 0 9)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Equals 5 (Minus _smt1 _smt0)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-41; -11",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2402,
        "question": "The sum of two numbers is -52. The first number minus the second is -30 . find the numbers",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus _smt0 _smt1) (Minus 0 52)) (Equals (Minus 0 30) (Minus _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{-4; -12}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2403,
        "question": "The sum of two numbers is -16.  The difference of the same numbers is 8. Find the numbers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus _smt0 _smt1) (Minus 0 16)) (Equals 8 (Minus _smt1 _smt0)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "1; 2 or 8; 9",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2404,
        "question": "the product of two consecutive integers is 8 less than 10 times the smaller of the two integers. Find the integers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "25; 26; 27",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2405,
        "question": "Find 3 consecutive numbers such that twice the smallest is 23 more than the largest.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Equals (Plus 23 _smt2) (Times 2 _smt0)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "8; 9; 10",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2406,
        "question": "Find three consecutive integers such that three times the smallest is 14 more than the largest.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "50",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2407,
        "question": "The sum of the positive odd integers less than 100 is subtracted from the sum of the positive even integers less than or equal to 100. What is the resulting difference?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "12",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2408,
        "question": "The sum of two numbers A and B is 3. The sum of their cubes is 36, What is the sum of their squares decreased by the product of the two numbers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus (Pow _smt0 3) (Pow _smt1 3)) 36) (Equals 3 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals ?_x0 (Minus (Plus (Pow _smt0 2) (Pow _smt1 2)) (Times _smt0 _smt1))) (Le _smt0 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "40",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2409,
        "question": "The sum of two integers is 120. One half the smaller number plus three-fourths the larger number is 80. What is the smaller number?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus _smt0 _smt1) 120) (Equals (Plus (Times 0.5 _smt0) (Div (Times 3 _smt1) 4)) 80) (Equals ?_x1 _smt0) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Le _smt0 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "14",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2410,
        "question": "if the sum of five consecutive integers is 60, find the value of the largest integer.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3 _smt4)) 60) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (IsInteger _smt3) (IsInteger _smt4) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3 _smt4)) (Equals ?_x2 _smt4) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Le _smt2 _smt3) (Le _smt3 _smt4))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "202",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2411,
        "question": "The sum of 5 consecutive integers is 1,000.  What is the value of the greatest of these integers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "39",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2412,
        "question": "What is the greatest of 5 consecutive integers if the sum of these integers equals 185?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 (Max (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3 _smt4))) (Equals (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3 _smt4)) 185) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (IsInteger _smt3) (IsInteger _smt4) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3 _smt4)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Le _smt2 _smt3) (Le _smt3 _smt4))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "403",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2413,
        "question": "if the sum of five consecutive positive integers is 2005, then what is the largest of these numbers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3 _smt4)) 2005) (Equals ?_x1 (Max (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3 _smt4))) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (IsInteger _smt3) (IsInteger _smt4) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3 _smt4)) (LessThan 0 _smt0) (LessThan 0 _smt1) (LessThan 0 _smt2) (LessThan 0 _smt3) (LessThan 0 _smt4) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Le _smt2 _smt3) (Le _smt3 _smt4))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-9;-8",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2414,
        "question": "The greatest of two consecutive integers is ten greater than twice the lesser. find the integers",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-19; -18",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2415,
        "question": "the greater of two consecutive integers is 20 more than twice the smaller. find the integers",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals (Max (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Plus 20 (Times 2 _smt0))) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-14; -13",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2416,
        "question": "the greater of 2 consecutive integers is 15 more than twice the smaller",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-6; -5",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2417,
        "question": "the larger of two consecutive integers is 7 greater than twice the smaller. find the integers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-5; -3",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2418,
        "question": "the greater of two consecutive odd integers is 7 greater than twice the lesser. Find the integers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-6; -5",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2419,
        "question": "the larger of the two consecutive integers is 7 greater than twice the smaller. Find the integers",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-19; -18",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2420,
        "question": "Find two consecutive integers such that the greater of the two is 20 more than twice the smaller.",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals (Max (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Plus 20 (Times 2 _smt0))) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "6; 8; 10",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2421,
        "question": "Find 3 consecutive even numbers where the product of the smaller two numbers is 52 less than the square of the largest number.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Equals (Minus (Pow _smt2 2) 52) (Times _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "11; 13; 15",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2422,
        "question": "Find three consecutive odd integers such that 4 times the sum of the last two is 2 greater than 10 times the first.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals (Plus 2 (Times 10 _smt0)) (Times 4 (Plus _smt1 _smt2))) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-12; -10; -8; -6",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2423,
        "question": "find four consecutive even integers whose sum is -36",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Minus 0 36) (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3))) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (IsInteger _smt3) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Le _smt2 _smt3) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_3 _smt3))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "5; 7",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2424,
        "question": "The product of two consecutive odd integers is 10 more than the square of the smaller integer. Find the integers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "9;10",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2425,
        "question": "The product of two consecutive integers is 9 more than the square of the smaller one. Find the integers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "87",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2427,
        "question": "The sum of 4 consecutive odd integers is 336. Find the largest integer.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3)) 336) (Equals ?_x1 _smt3) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (IsInteger _smt3) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Le _smt2 _smt3))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "15",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2428,
        "question": "The sum of four consecutive integers is 54. What is the LARGEST of these integers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "64",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2429,
        "question": "the sum of four consecutive integers is 250, what is the greatest of these integers",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "104; 106; 108; 110; 112",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2430,
        "question": "find 5 consecutive even integers such that the greatest minus twice the least is -96",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3 _smt4)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (IsInteger _smt3) (IsInteger _smt4) (Equals (Minus 0 96) (Minus _smt4 (Times 2 _smt0))) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Le _smt2 _smt3) (Le _smt3 _smt4) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_3 _smt3) (Equals ?_x0_4 _smt4))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "4",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2431,
        "question": "If five is added to the sum of twice a number and three times the number, the result is 25. Find the number",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 25 (Plus 5 (Plus (Times 2 _smt0) (Times 3 _smt0)))) (Equals ?_x1 _smt0))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "24",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2432,
        "question": "Eleven more than five times a number is equal to the difference between 227 and four times the number. Find the number.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 _smt0) (Equals (Plus 11 (Times 5 _smt0)) (Difference (Elements 227 (Times 4 _smt0)))))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "9",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2433,
        "question": "4 times a number and 5 times the same number added to 75 gives 156. Find the number?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "77",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2434,
        "question": "The Sum of three consecutive integers is 234. The smallest integer among the three integers is?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "5",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2435,
        "question": "what is the least of three consecutive integers whose sum is 18",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 (Min (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Equals 18 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "9; 11; 13",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2436,
        "question": "Find three consecutive odd integers such that the sum of the smallest and 4 times the largest is 61",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals 61 (Plus _smt0 (Times 4 _smt2))) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "9; 11; 13",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2437,
        "question": "find three consecutive odd integers such that the sum of the smallest and 4 times the largest 61",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "5; 7; 9",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2438,
        "question": "FIND THREE CONSECUTIVE ODD INTEGERS SUCH THAT THE SUM OF THE SMALLEST AND 7 TIMES THE LARGEST IS 68",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals 68 (Plus _smt0 (Times 7 _smt2))) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "18; 19; 20",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2439,
        "question": "Product of three consecutive positive integers is 120 times their sum. Find the numbers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Product (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Times 120 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)))) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (LessThan 0 _smt0) (LessThan 0 _smt1) (LessThan 0 _smt2) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-23; -21",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2440,
        "question": "find 2 consecutive odd integers such that 4 times the smaller is 29 less than 3 times the larger",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Equals (Minus (Times 3 _smt1) 29) (Times 4 _smt0)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-1; 1",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2441,
        "question": "Find two consecutive odd integers such that when twice the second is subtracted from four times the first, the result is -6",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Minus (Times 4 _smt0) (Times 2 _smt1)) (Minus 0 6)) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "21; 23",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2442,
        "question": "Find two consecutive odd integers such that 4 times the larger is 29 more than 3 times the smaller",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Equals (Plus 29 (Times 3 _smt0)) (Times 4 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-7; -5",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2443,
        "question": "find two consecutive odd integers such that five times the first integer is 25 less than twice the greater integer",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Equals (Minus (Times 2 (Max (Elements _smt0 _smt1))) 25) (Times 5 _smt0)) (IsInteger (Max (Elements _smt0 _smt1))) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-4; -2",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2444,
        "question": "Four times the lesser of two consecutive even integers is 12 less than twice the greater number. Find the integers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "20; 22",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2445,
        "question": "find two consecutive even integers  such that twice the smaller is 26 less than three times the larger",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Equals (Minus (Times 3 _smt1) 26) (Times 2 _smt0)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-27; -25; -23",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2446,
        "question": "Two times the least of three consecutive odd integers exceeds three times the greatest by 15. What are the integers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals (Plus (Times 3 _smt2) 15) (Times 2 (Min (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)))) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "ans_no_result",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2447,
        "question": "fiND FOUR CONSECUTIVE INTEGERS WHOSE SUM IS 244",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "29;30;31;32",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2448,
        "question": "The sum of four consecutive integers is 122. What are the integers?",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (IsInteger _smt3) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3)) (Equals 122 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3))) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Le _smt2 _smt3) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_2 _smt2) (Equals ?_x1_3 _smt3))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "11; 12; 13; 14",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2449,
        "question": "The total number of medals won by athletes in each of the countries A, B, C, and D are four consecutive integers whose sum is 50. Find the number of metals for each country",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "57; 58; 59; 60",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2450,
        "question": "what are four consecutive integers whose sum is 234?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 234 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3))) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (IsInteger _smt3) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Le _smt2 _smt3) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_3 _smt3))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-143",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2451,
        "question": "The sum of two consecutive integers is -287. Find the larger integer.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus _smt0 _smt1) (Minus 0 287)) (Equals ?_x1 _smt1) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-138",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2452,
        "question": "the sum of two consecutive integers is -277. what is the larger integer",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus _smt0 _smt1) (Minus 0 277)) (Equals ?_x1 _smt1) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-111",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2453,
        "question": "the sum of two consecutive integers is -223.  Find the larger integer",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus _smt0 _smt1) (Minus 0 223)) (Equals ?_x1 _smt1) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "6; 8; 10; 12",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2454,
        "question": "find four consecutive even integers where the sum of the first three is twice the fourth",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (IsInteger _smt3) (Equals (Times 2 _smt3) (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_3 _smt3))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "6; 8; 10; 12",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2455,
        "question": "FIND FOUR CONSECUTIVE EVEN INTEGERS SO THAT THE sum OF THE FIRST THREE IS TO MORE THAN THAT twice THE FOURTH",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "40",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2456,
        "question": "the sum of a number and 2/5 of itself is 56. what is the number?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 _smt0) (Equals 56 (Plus _smt0 (Div (Times 2 _smt0) 5))))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "120",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2457,
        "question": "When 60% of a number is added to the number, the result is 192. What is the number?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 192 (Plus (Div (Times 60 _smt0) 100) _smt0)) (Equals ?_x1 _smt0))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "ans_no_result",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2458,
        "question": "Find three consecutive odd integers whose sum is 10 less than 4 times the least integer.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-11; -9; -7",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2459,
        "question": "the sum of three consecutive odd integers is five less than twice the smallest of these integers",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "24; 25",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2460,
        "question": "Find two consecutive integers whose sum is the square of 7.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Pow 7 2) (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "58",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2461,
        "question": "Find the 2-digit number whose tens digit is 3 less than the units digit and the original number is 6 more than 4 times the sum of the digits.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 (Plus 6 (Times 4 (Plus _smt0_d1 _smt0_d0)))) (Equals (Mod (Div ?_x0 10) 10) (Minus (Mod (Div ?_x0 1) 10) 3)) (Le ?_x0 (Minus (Pow 10 2) 1)) (Le (Pow 10 (Minus 2 1)) ?_x0) (Equals (Plus (Times _smt0_d0 1) (Times _smt0_d1 10)) ?_x0) (Le 0 _smt0_d1) (Le _smt0_d1 9) (IsInteger _smt0_d1) (Le 0 _smt0_d0) (Le _smt0_d0 9) (IsInteger _smt0_d0))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "4; 6",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2462,
        "question": "Find two consecutive even integers such that the square of the smaller is 10 more than the larger.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Equals (Plus 10 _smt1) (Pow _smt0 2)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "28; 30; 32; 34",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2463,
        "question": "Find four consecutive even integers such that twice the sum of the first and fourth is 124",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (IsInteger _smt3) (Equals 124 (Times 2 (Plus _smt0 _smt3))) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_3 _smt3))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-63; -62; -61",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2464,
        "question": "What three consecutive integers have a sum of -186?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Minus 0 186)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-50; -49; -48",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2465,
        "question": "Find three consecutive integers whose sum is -147",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Minus 0 147) (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-20; -15; -10; -5",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2466,
        "question": "Find four consecutive multiples of five such that twice the sum of the two biggest exceeds twice the smallest by ten.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "5; 6; 7",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2467,
        "question": "find 3 consecutive numbers such that 4 times the first is equal to 7 more than the sum of the other two.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "2; 4; 6",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2469,
        "question": "find three consecutive even integers so that the largest is 2 times more than the smallest",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "6; 8",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2470,
        "question": "find two consecutive even integers if one-third of the smaller one is equal to one-fourth of the larger one",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "13; 15; 17; 19; 21",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2471,
        "question": "five consecutive odd integers whose sum is 85",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 85 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3 _smt4))) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3 _smt4)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (IsInteger _smt3) (IsInteger _smt4) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Le _smt2 _smt3) (Le _smt3 _smt4) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_3 _smt3) (Equals ?_x0_4 _smt4))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "9; 11; 13; 15; 17",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2472,
        "question": "Find five consecutive odd numbers that have a sum of 65.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 65 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3 _smt4))) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3 _smt4)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Le _smt2 _smt3) (Le _smt3 _smt4) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_3 _smt3) (Equals ?_x0_4 _smt4))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "39",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2473,
        "question": "Find the largest of four consecutive odd integers such that the sum of the first and the fourth is 27 less than three times the first integer.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 (Max (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3))) (Equals (Plus _smt0 _smt3) (Minus (Times 3 _smt0) 27)) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (IsInteger _smt3))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "7 or -8",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2474,
        "question": "if a number is added to its square, the result is 56. Find the number",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 56 (Plus _smt0 (Pow _smt0 2))) (Equals ?_x1 _smt0))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "5 or -6",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2475,
        "question": "The sum of an integer and its square is 30. Find the number?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 _smt0) (IsInteger _smt0) (Equals 30 (Plus _smt0 (Pow _smt0 2))))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "10000",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2476,
        "question": "find the sum of the first 100 odd numbers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "7225",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2477,
        "question": "What is the sum of the first 85 consecutive odd numbers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{-3; -15}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2478,
        "question": "find 2 integers whose sum is -18 and whose product is 45",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Minus 0 18) (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals 45 (Times _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{-7; -6}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2479,
        "question": "two negative integers have a sum of -13 and a product of 42. what are the integers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus _smt0 _smt1) (Minus 0 13)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (LessThan _smt0 0) (LessThan _smt1 0) (Equals 42 (Times _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "6",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2480,
        "question": "The sum of five consecutive integers is 40. What is the smallest of the integers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-11; -10; -9; -8",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2481,
        "question": "Find four consecutive integers whose sum is -38.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "3; 5; 7",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2482,
        "question": "Find three consecutive odd integers such that the product of the first and second exceeds the third by 8.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Times _smt0 _smt1) (Plus _smt2 8)) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "5; 6; 7",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2483,
        "question": "find three consecutive positive integers such that the product of the first and the third is 29 more than the second.",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (LessThan 0 _smt0) (LessThan 0 _smt1) (LessThan 0 _smt2) (Equals (Plus 29 _smt1) (Times _smt0 _smt2)) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "6; 8; 10",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2484,
        "question": "Find three consecutive positive even integers such that the product of the second and third integers is twenty more than ten times the first integer.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "9; 10; 11",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2485,
        "question": "find three consecutive positive integers such that the product of the second and third integers is twenty more than ten times the first integer",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "4; 5; 6; 7 or -7; -6; -5; -4",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2486,
        "question": "I am thinking of four consecutive integers. The sum of the squares of the second and third numbers is 61. Find all four of the integers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "5; 6; 7",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2487,
        "question": "find three consecutive integers such that the sum of twice the first and 4 times the second is equal to 20 more than twice the third",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Equals (Plus 20 (Times 2 _smt2)) (Plus (Times 2 _smt0) (Times 4 _smt1))) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "57",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2488,
        "question": "The tens digits of a two-digit number is 2 less than the units digit. The sum of the digits is 12. Identify what the number is.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "15; 16; 17",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2489,
        "question": "The smallest of three consecutive integers is 18 less than the sum of the two larger integers. Find the integers",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Equals (Min (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Minus (Plus _smt1 _smt2) 18)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "ans_no_result",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2490,
        "question": "The square of the first of three consecutive odd integers is 9 more than 6 times the sum of the second and the first. Find the numbers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "51; 52; 53",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2491,
        "question": "find three consecutive integers such that the sum of the second and the third is eighty-eight more than one-third the smallest",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Equals (Plus (Plus 80 8) (Div (Times 1 (Min (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) 3)) (Plus _smt1 _smt2)) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "25; 26; 27",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2492,
        "question": "find three consecutive integers such that the sum of the second and third is forty eight more than one-fifth the smallest.",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Equals (Plus (Plus 40 8) (Div (Times 1 (Min (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) 5)) (Plus _smt1 _smt2)) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "5; 6",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2493,
        "question": "Find two consecutive integers whose product is 6 less than the square of the larger number.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "3; 5",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2494,
        "question": "two consecutive odd integers, the sum of three times the smaller and the larger is fourteen",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "13; 15",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2495,
        "question": "Find two consecutive odd integers such that the larger, added to eight times the smaller, equals 119.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Equals 119 (Plus _smt1 (Times 8 _smt0))) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "10",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2496,
        "question": "If f(x) = x + 2, find the value of x if f(x) = 12.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Times f x) (Plus x 2)) (Equals (Times f x) 12) (Equals ?_x0 x))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "8; 10",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2497,
        "question": "find two consecutive even integers such that 5 times the first integer is equal to 4 times the second",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Equals (Times 5 _smt0) (Times 4 _smt1)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "4; 6",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2498,
        "question": "find two consecutive even integers such that three times the first equals twice the second",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Equals (Times 2 _smt1) (Times 3 _smt0)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "14; 16",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2499,
        "question": "Find two consecutive even integers such that eight times the first equals seven times the second.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Equals (Times 7 _smt1) (Times 8 _smt0)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-8; -6",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2500,
        "question": "Find two consecutive even integers such that nine times the smaller is equal to twelve times the larger.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "27",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2501,
        "question": "the sum of three consecutive odd number is 87.find the first number",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "7",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2502,
        "question": "The sum of 3 consecutive odd integers is 27. find the smallest of these integers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "23",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2503,
        "question": "the sum of three consecutive odd numbers is 75 what are the smallest of these numbers",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "17",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2504,
        "question": "If x is an odd number and the sum of x and two consecutive odd numbers after x is 57, find the value of x.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "8",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2505,
        "question": "The product of three-fourths and a number is six. find the number.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 _smt0) (Equals 6 (Times (Div 3 4) _smt0)))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "600",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2506,
        "question": "If .4% of a quantity is 2.4, find the total quantity.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "2.680% | 2.680",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2507,
        "question": "What percentage of 306,000 equals 8,200?",
        "semantics": "(Equals (Times ?_x0 306000) (Times 100 8200))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "850",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2508,
        "question": "4% of what number is 34?",
        "semantics": "(Equals (Times 4 ?_x0) (Times 100 34))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "40",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2509,
        "question": "30 is 75% of what number?",
        "semantics": "(Equals (Times 75 ?_x0) (Times 100 30))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "250% | 250",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2510,
        "question": "what percent of 54 is 135?",
        "semantics": "(Equals (Times ?_x0 54) (Times 100 135))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "224/3 | 74.667",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2511,
        "question": "56 is 75% of what number?",
        "semantics": "(Equals (Times 75 ?_x0) (Times 100 56))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "300",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2512,
        "question": "if 18% of a number Z is 54 Find the value of Z.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Times 18 _smt0) (Times 100 54)) (Equals ?_x2 _smt0))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "200",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2513,
        "question": "35% of what number is 70?",
        "semantics": "(Equals (Times 35 ?_x0) (Times 100 70))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "12.5% | 12.5",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2514,
        "question": "I have the number 640 and the number 80. I need to figure out what percentage 80 is of 640.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "350",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2517,
        "question": "what is the sum of 5 consecutive integers if the median number is 70",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "29",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2519,
        "question": "If the first and third of three consecutive odd integers are added, the result is 81 less than five times the second integer. Find the third integers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "19; 9",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2520,
        "question": "One number is 1 more than another doubled. If their difference is 10, find the numbers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals _smt0 (Plus 1 (Times _smt1 2))) (Equals 10 (Difference (Elements _smt0 _smt1))) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{49; 15}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2521,
        "question": "the difference between 2 numbers is 34. the larger number is 4 more than 3 times the smaller number. What're the numbers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 34 (Minus _smt1 _smt0)) (Equals _smt1 (Plus 4 (Times 3 _smt0))) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "37; 18",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2522,
        "question": "The difference between two numbers is 19. The first number is one more than twice the second number. Find the two numbers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "30",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2523,
        "question": "one number is 15 more than another. the sum of twice the larger number and 3 times the smaller number is 180. what's the smaller number ?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus (Times 2 (Max (Elements (Plus 15 _smt1) _smt1))) (Times 3 (Min (Elements (Plus 15 _smt1) _smt1)))) 180) (Equals ?_x1 (Min (Elements (Plus 15 _smt1) _smt1))))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{7; 3}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2524,
        "question": "One positive integer is 5 less than 4 times another.  Their product is 21.  Find the integers",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (LessThan 0 _smt0) (Equals _smt0 (Minus (Times 4 _smt1) 5)) (Equals 21 (Times _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "49; 50",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2525,
        "question": "A fifth of the larger of two consecutive integer exceeds a seventh of the smaller by 3. Find the integers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "2; 4; 6; 8",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2527,
        "question": "Find four consecutive even integers such that the sum of the squares of the first and the second is 12 more than the last.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-1; 0; 1 or 9; 10; 11",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2528,
        "question": "Three times the sum of three consecutive integers is equal to the product of the two smallest integers. What are the integers?",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Equals (Times 3 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Times _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "24;26",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2529,
        "question": "If you begin with an even integer and count by two, you are counting consecutive even integers.  Write and solve an equation to find two consecutive even integers whose sum is 50.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "96; 98",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2530,
        "question": "the sum of two even integers is 194. what are they?",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger 2) (Equals (Mod _smt0 2) 0) (Equals (Mod _smt1 2) 0) (Equals 194 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "44; 46",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2531,
        "question": "find two consecutive even integers whose sum is 90.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 90 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "108; 110",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2532,
        "question": "Two consecutive even integers that total 218",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 218 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "20; 22",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2533,
        "question": "find two consecutive even integers whose sum equals 42.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 42 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "22; 24",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2534,
        "question": "find two consecutive even integers whose sum is 46",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 46 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "36; 38",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2535,
        "question": "two consecutive even integers have a sum of 74",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "12;14",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2536,
        "question": "How do I find 2 consecutive even integers whose sum is 26?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "14;16",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2537,
        "question": "the sum of two consecutive even numbers is 30. what are the numbers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals 30 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "24; 26",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2538,
        "question": "The sum of two consecutive even integers is 50. What are the integers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Equals 50 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "44",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2539,
        "question": "The sum of two consecutive even integers is 86. Find the larger number.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus _smt0 _smt1) 86) (Equals ?_x1 _smt1) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Le _smt0 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "18",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2540,
        "question": "if three times the smaller of two consecutive integers is added to four times the larger, the result is 130. find the smaller integer.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 130 (Plus (Times 3 (Min (Elements _smt0 _smt1))) (Times 4 _smt1))) (Equals ?_x2 _smt0) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "19",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2541,
        "question": "If three times the smaller of two consecutive integers is added to four times the larger the result is 137. Find the smaller integer",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 137 (Plus (Times 3 (Min (Elements _smt0 _smt1))) (Times 4 _smt1))) (Equals ?_x2 _smt0) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "9",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2542,
        "question": "three times the smaller of two consecutive integers is added to four times the larger, the result is 67. find the smaller integer.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 67 (Plus (Times 3 (Min (Elements _smt0 _smt1))) (Times 4 _smt1))) (Equals ?_x2 _smt0) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "19",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2543,
        "question": "If three times the smaller of two consecutive integers is added to four times the larger, the result is  137. Find the smaller integer",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 137 (Plus (Times 3 (Min (Elements _smt0 _smt1))) (Times 4 _smt1))) (Equals ?_x2 _smt0) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "4",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2544,
        "question": "Find the smallest of three consecutive even integers so that four times the smallest increased by two times the largest is 32",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 (Min (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Equals (Plus (Times 4 _smt0) (Times 2 _smt2)) 32) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "18; 20",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2545,
        "question": "The product of 2 consecutive positive even integers is 360.  Find the integers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (LessThan 0 _smt0) (LessThan 0 _smt1) (Equals 360 (Times _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "12;14 or -14;-12",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2546,
        "question": "find two consecutive even integers whose product is 168.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 168 (Times _smt0 _smt1)) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "16;18 or -18;-16",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2547,
        "question": "find two consecutive even numbers whose product is 288",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 288 (Times _smt0 _smt1)) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "12; 14",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2548,
        "question": "The product of two consecutive positive even integers is one hundred sixty-eight.  Find the two integers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "24; 26 or -26; -24",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2549,
        "question": "Find two consecutive even integers whose product is 624.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 624 (Times _smt0 _smt1)) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "12; 14",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2550,
        "question": "find two consecutive even positive numbers whose product is 168",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 168 (Times _smt0 _smt1)) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (LessThan 0 _smt0) (LessThan 0 _smt1) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "250; 252 or -252; -250",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2551,
        "question": "The product of two consecutive even integers is sixty-three thousand. What are the numbers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Equals (Times (Plus 60 3) 1000) (Times _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "4;6 or -6;-4",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2552,
        "question": "if the product of two consecutive positive even integers is 24. find the numbers",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-7; -5",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2553,
        "question": "five times the sum of two consecutive odd integers is twelve times the larger of the two. find the two odd integers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "17; 19 or -19; -17",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2554,
        "question": "The product of two consecutive odd integers is 323. Find the numbers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Equals 323 (Times _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "13; 15 or -15; -13",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2555,
        "question": "Find two consecutive odd numbers whose product is 195.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 195 (Times _smt0 _smt1)) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "11; 13",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2556,
        "question": "The product of two consecutive positive odd integers is 143. Find the pair of integers that satisfies this condition.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "13; 15 or -15; -13",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2557,
        "question": "Find two consecutive odd integers whose product is 195.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 195 (Times _smt0 _smt1)) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "6;8 or -8;-6",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2558,
        "question": "The sum of the squares of two consecutive even integers is 100. Find the two integers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "4; 6 or -6; -4",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2559,
        "question": "the sum of the squares of two consecutive even integers is 52. what are the integers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus (Pow _smt0 2) (Pow _smt1 2)) 52) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "12; 14",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2560,
        "question": "find the two consecutive positive even numbers the sum of whose squares 340",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-8; -6",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2561,
        "question": "The sum of the squares of two consecutive negative even integers is 100. Find the integers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus (Pow _smt0 2) (Pow _smt1 2)) 100) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (LessThan _smt0 0) (LessThan _smt1 0) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "96",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2562,
        "question": "The sum of two numbers is 110. The larger number is 2 less than 7 times the smaller. Find the larger number",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus _smt0 (Minus (Times 7 _smt0) 2)) 110) (Equals ?_x1 (Minus (Times 7 _smt0) 2)) (Le _smt0 (Minus (Times 7 _smt0) 2)))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "1680",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2563,
        "question": "The sum of 4 consecutive integers is 26. What is the product of the 4 numbers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3)) 26) (Equals ?_x1 (Product (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3))) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (IsInteger _smt3) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Le _smt2 _smt3))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "60",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2564,
        "question": "One-fifth of a number, subtracted from 20, is the same as one-fourth of 32.What is the number?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 _smt0) (Equals (Times 1 32) (Times 4 (Minus 20 (Div (Times 1 _smt0) 5)))))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "18",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2565,
        "question": "What is the value of x?here's the equation: 3/5(x+2)=12.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "4; 6",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2566,
        "question": "find two consecutive even numbers such that three times the square of the smaller one added to the square of the greater is equal to 84",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals 84 (Plus (Times 3 (Pow _smt0 2)) (Pow _smt1 2))) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "19; 20; 21",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2568,
        "question": "there are three consecutive integers. The sum of twice the second and third is 61. Find the three integers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "9; 10; 11",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2569,
        "question": "Three consecutive integers are such that the square of the first is 29 less than the product of the other two",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "240",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2570,
        "question": "If the largest of 87 consecutive integers is 326, what is the smallest?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Max (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3 _smt4 _smt5 _smt6 _smt7 _smt8 _smt9 _smt10 _smt11 _smt12 _smt13 _smt14 _smt15 _smt16 _smt17 _smt18 _smt19 _smt20 _smt21 _smt22 _smt23 _smt24 _smt25 _smt26 _smt27 _smt28 _smt29 _smt30 _smt31 _smt32 _smt33 _smt34 _smt35 _smt36 _smt37 _smt38 _smt39 _smt40 _smt41 _smt42 _smt43 _smt44 _smt45 _smt46 _smt47 _smt48 _smt49 _smt50 _smt51 _smt52 _smt53 _smt54 _smt55 _smt56 _smt57 _smt58 _smt59 _smt60 _smt61 _smt62 _smt63 _smt64 _smt65 _smt66 _smt67 _smt68 _smt69 _smt70 _smt71 _smt72 _smt73 _smt74 _smt75 _smt76 _smt77 _smt78 _smt79 _smt80 _smt81 _smt82 _smt83 _smt84 _smt85 _smt86)) 326) (Equals ?_x1 _smt0) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (IsInteger _smt3) (IsInteger _smt4) (IsInteger _smt5) (IsInteger _smt6) (IsInteger _smt7) (IsInteger _smt8) (IsInteger _smt9) (IsInteger _smt10) (IsInteger _smt11) (IsInteger _smt12) (IsInteger _smt13) (IsInteger _smt14) (IsInteger _smt15) (IsInteger _smt16) (IsInteger _smt17) (IsInteger _smt18) (IsInteger _smt19) (IsInteger _smt20) (IsInteger _smt21) (IsInteger _smt22) (IsInteger _smt23) (IsInteger _smt24) (IsInteger _smt25) (IsInteger _smt26) (IsInteger _smt27) (IsInteger _smt28) (IsInteger _smt29) (IsInteger _smt30) (IsInteger _smt31) (IsInteger _smt32) (IsInteger _smt33) (IsInteger _smt34) (IsInteger _smt35) (IsInteger _smt36) (IsInteger _smt37) (IsInteger _smt38) (IsInteger _smt39) (IsInteger _smt40) (IsInteger _smt41) (IsInteger _smt42) (IsInteger _smt43) (IsInteger _smt44) (IsInteger _smt45) (IsInteger _smt46) (IsInteger _smt47) (IsInteger _smt48) (IsInteger _smt49) (IsInteger _smt50) (IsInteger _smt51) (IsInteger _smt52) (IsInteger _smt53) (IsInteger _smt54) (IsInteger _smt55) (IsInteger _smt56) (IsInteger _smt57) (IsInteger _smt58) (IsInteger _smt59) (IsInteger _smt60) (IsInteger _smt61) (IsInteger _smt62) (IsInteger _smt63) (IsInteger _smt64) (IsInteger _smt65) (IsInteger _smt66) (IsInteger _smt67) (IsInteger _smt68) (IsInteger _smt69) (IsInteger _smt70) (IsInteger _smt71) (IsInteger _smt72) (IsInteger _smt73) (IsInteger _smt74) (IsInteger _smt75) (IsInteger _smt76) (IsInteger _smt77) (IsInteger _smt78) (IsInteger _smt79) (IsInteger _smt80) (IsInteger _smt81) (IsInteger _smt82) (IsInteger _smt83) (IsInteger _smt84) (IsInteger _smt85) (IsInteger _smt86) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3 _smt4 _smt5 _smt6 _smt7 _smt8 _smt9 _smt10 _smt11 _smt12 _smt13 _smt14 _smt15 _smt16 _smt17 _smt18 _smt19 _smt20 _smt21 _smt22 _smt23 _smt24 _smt25 _smt26 _smt27 _smt28 _smt29 _smt30 _smt31 _smt32 _smt33 _smt34 _smt35 _smt36 _smt37 _smt38 _smt39 _smt40 _smt41 _smt42 _smt43 _smt44 _smt45 _smt46 _smt47 _smt48 _smt49 _smt50 _smt51 _smt52 _smt53 _smt54 _smt55 _smt56 _smt57 _smt58 _smt59 _smt60 _smt61 _smt62 _smt63 _smt64 _smt65 _smt66 _smt67 _smt68 _smt69 _smt70 _smt71 _smt72 _smt73 _smt74 _smt75 _smt76 _smt77 _smt78 _smt79 _smt80 _smt81 _smt82 _smt83 _smt84 _smt85 _smt86)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Le _smt2 _smt3) (Le _smt3 _smt4) (Le _smt4 _smt5) (Le _smt5 _smt6) (Le _smt6 _smt7) (Le _smt7 _smt8) (Le _smt8 _smt9) (Le _smt9 _smt10) (Le _smt10 _smt11) (Le _smt11 _smt12) (Le _smt12 _smt13) (Le _smt13 _smt14) (Le _smt14 _smt15) (Le _smt15 _smt16) (Le _smt16 _smt17) (Le _smt17 _smt18) (Le _smt18 _smt19) (Le _smt19 _smt20) (Le _smt20 _smt21) (Le _smt21 _smt22) (Le _smt22 _smt23) (Le _smt23 _smt24) (Le _smt24 _smt25) (Le _smt25 _smt26) (Le _smt26 _smt27) (Le _smt27 _smt28) (Le _smt28 _smt29) (Le _smt29 _smt30) (Le _smt30 _smt31) (Le _smt31 _smt32) (Le _smt32 _smt33) (Le _smt33 _smt34) (Le _smt34 _smt35) (Le _smt35 _smt36) (Le _smt36 _smt37) (Le _smt37 _smt38) (Le _smt38 _smt39) (Le _smt39 _smt40) (Le _smt40 _smt41) (Le _smt41 _smt42) (Le _smt42 _smt43) (Le _smt43 _smt44) (Le _smt44 _smt45) (Le _smt45 _smt46) (Le _smt46 _smt47) (Le _smt47 _smt48) (Le _smt48 _smt49) (Le _smt49 _smt50) (Le _smt50 _smt51) (Le _smt51 _smt52) (Le _smt52 _smt53) (Le _smt53 _smt54) (Le _smt54 _smt55) (Le _smt55 _smt56) (Le _smt56 _smt57) (Le _smt57 _smt58) (Le _smt58 _smt59) (Le _smt59 _smt60) (Le _smt60 _smt61) (Le _smt61 _smt62) (Le _smt62 _smt63) (Le _smt63 _smt64) (Le _smt64 _smt65) (Le _smt65 _smt66) (Le _smt66 _smt67) (Le _smt67 _smt68) (Le _smt68 _smt69) (Le _smt69 _smt70) (Le _smt70 _smt71) (Le _smt71 _smt72) (Le _smt72 _smt73) (Le _smt73 _smt74) (Le _smt74 _smt75) (Le _smt75 _smt76) (Le _smt76 _smt77) (Le _smt77 _smt78) (Le _smt78 _smt79) (Le _smt79 _smt80) (Le _smt80 _smt81) (Le _smt81 _smt82) (Le _smt82 _smt83) (Le _smt83 _smt84) (Le _smt84 _smt85) (Le _smt85 _smt86))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "6; 8; 10 or -2; 0; 2",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2571,
        "question": "find three consecutive even integers such that the product of the second and third integers is twenty more than ten times the first integer",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "25",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2572,
        "question": "If the sum of the consecutive integers from -22 to x, inclusive, is 72, find the value of x?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Sum _x0) 72) (IsInteger _x1) (Le (Minus 0 22) _x1) (Le _x1 x) (Consecutive _x0) (Equals ?_x2 x))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "26",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2573,
        "question": "twice a number decreased by 7, gives 45. find the number",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "15",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2574,
        "question": "If the product of a number and 4 is decreased by 10, the result is 50. Find the number",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 50 (Minus (Times _smt0 4) 10)) (Equals ?_x1 _smt0))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "115",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2575,
        "question": "420 is subtracted from the product of a number and 12. This difference is equal to 960. What is the number?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 960 (Minus (Times _smt0 12) 420)) (Equals ?_x1 _smt0))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "x = 7 | 7",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2576,
        "question": "four less than twice a number x is equal to ten",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "25",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2577,
        "question": "how do you write find a number such that seven less than twice the number is 43 as an equation??",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "3",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2578,
        "question": "if 5 is decreased by 3 times a number, the result is -4",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "30",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2579,
        "question": "If a number is doubled and the result decreased by 35, the result is 25. What is the Number?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "5",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2580,
        "question": "The difference of the squares of two consecutive positive even integers is 20. What is the average of the two numbers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 (Times (Plus _smt0 _smt1) 0.5)) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (LessThan 0 _smt0) (LessThan 0 _smt1) (Equals 20 (Difference (Elements (Pow _smt0 2) (Pow _smt1 2)))) (Le _smt0 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "2/3",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2581,
        "question": "The sum of two integers is 15 and their product is 54. What is the quotient, in simplest form, when the smaller integer is divided by the larger one?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "11; 12; 13 or -2; -1; 0",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2582,
        "question": "find three consecutive integers such that the product of the two smaller integers is 2 more than 10 times the largest integer.",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Equals (Plus 2 (Times 10 _smt2)) (Times _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "225",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2583,
        "question": "Ten consecutive integers are arranged in order from least to greatest. If the sum of the first five integers is 200, what is the sum of the last five integers ?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{4; 6}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2584,
        "question": "The sum of two integers is 10, and their product is 24.  Find the two integers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{9; 16}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2585,
        "question": "the sum of two numbers is 25; their product is 144. Find the numbers",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{19; 36}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2586,
        "question": "Find two numbers whose sum is 55 and whose product is 684.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 55 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals 684 (Times _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "11; 13; 15",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2589,
        "question": "Three numbers are positive consecutive odd integers. If the larger two numbers have a product of 195, find all three integers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "21; 23; 25",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2590,
        "question": "What three consecutive odd numbers have a product of 12075?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Product (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) 12075) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "4",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2591,
        "question": "If 18 is decreased by the sum of a number and 6, the result is 4 less than 3 times the number.  Find the number",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Minus 18 (Plus _smt0 6)) (Minus (Times 3 _smt0) 4)) (Equals ?_x1 _smt0))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "52900",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2592,
        "question": "M is a perfect square of an integer. The next larger perfect square is M + 461. What is M?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "117",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2593,
        "question": "The sum of two consecutive odd integers is 236. What is the smaller integer?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus _smt0 _smt1) 236) (Equals ?_x1 _smt0) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Le _smt0 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "7; 9",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2594,
        "question": "find two consecutive odd positive odd numbers which are such that the square of their sum exceeds the sum of their square by 126",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "4; 7",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2595,
        "question": "The sum of two times one number and three times another is 29. The difference between twice the first and the second is 1. Solve algebraically to find the numbers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "8; 19",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2597,
        "question": "The sum of twice a first number and five times a second number is 111.  If the second number is subtracted from five times the first number the result is 21. Find the numbers",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 21 (Minus (Times 5 _smt0) _smt1)) (Equals 111 (Plus (Times 2 _smt0) (Times 5 _smt1))) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "9; 10",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2598,
        "question": "The smaller of two consecutive integers is four more than half of the greater.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "16; 18",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2599,
        "question": "There are two consecutive even integers. The square of the larger one is three hundred eight more than the smaller one.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "4; 6 or -2; 0",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2600,
        "question": "If the difference between the squares of two consecutive even integers is the same as four less than the product of the integers, what is one of the integers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "7",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2601,
        "question": "find the ratio of 28 days to 4 weeks.",
        "semantics": "(Equals 28 (Times 4 ?_x0))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "5/4 | 1.25",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2602,
        "question": "what is the reciprocal of 0.8.",
        "semantics": "(Equals 1 (Times 0.8 ?_x0))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "15/4",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2603,
        "question": "what is the answer to 30 divided by 8 as a fraction?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "7; 9",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2604,
        "question": "the sum of the squares of two consecutive odd positive integers is 130. find the integers",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus (Pow _smt0 2) (Pow _smt1 2)) 130) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (LessThan 0 _smt0) (LessThan 0 _smt1) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-13; -11",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2605,
        "question": "The sum of the squares of two consecutive negative odd integers is 290. Find the integers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus (Pow _smt0 2) (Pow _smt1 2)) 290) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (LessThan _smt0 0) (LessThan _smt1 0) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "7;9",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2606,
        "question": "The sum of the squares of two consecutive positive odd integers is equal to one hundred thirty. Find the two integers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "25",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2607,
        "question": "The sum of the positive odd integers less than 50 is subtracted from the sum of the positive even integers less than or equal to 50. What is the resulting difference?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "7 or 1",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2608,
        "question": "Twice the square of an odd integer is 1 more than the square of the next consecutive odd integer.  What is the greater integer?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-3; -1; 1; 3",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2609,
        "question": "find four consecutive odd integers so that the sum of the smallest integer and the largest integer is the same as the sum of all four integers",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (IsInteger _smt3) (IsInteger _smt4) (IsInteger _smt5) (IsInteger _smt6) (IsInteger _smt7) (Equals (Plus _smt0 _smt3) (Sum (Elements _smt4 _smt5 _smt6 _smt7))) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Le _smt2 _smt3) (Le _smt4 _smt5) (Le _smt5 _smt6) (Le _smt6 _smt7) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_3 _smt3))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "6; 7; 8",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2610,
        "question": "Find three consecutive integers such that the sum of the squares of the second and third exceeds twice the square of the first by 41.",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Equals (Plus (Times 2 (Pow _smt0 2)) 41) (Plus (Pow _smt1 2) (Pow _smt2 2))) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "15; 17; 19; 21",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2611,
        "question": "Find four consecutive odd integers such that the product of the second and third exceeds the square of the first by 98.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Times _smt1 _smt2) (Plus (Pow _smt0 2) 98)) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (IsInteger _smt3) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_3 _smt3))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "11.403",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2612,
        "question": "when the sum of 16 and 10 times a positive number is subtracted from the square of the number, 0 results",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-9; -7; -5; -3; -1",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2613,
        "question": "Find the integers. Five consecutive odd integers such that the sum of the first and fifth are one less than three times the fourth integer.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "18; 20",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2614,
        "question": "the greater of two consecutive even integers is 10 more than half the greater. Find the integers",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Max (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Plus 10 (Times 0.5 _smt1))) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "17; 18; 19",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2615,
        "question": "there are 3 consecutive integers. the sum of the first two integers is 16 more than the third. Find integers",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "8; 9; 10",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2616,
        "question": "find three consecutive integers such that the sum of the first and second is 7  more than the third.",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Equals (Plus 7 _smt2) (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "79; 81; 83",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2617,
        "question": "find three consecutive odd numbers such that the sum of the last two bigger numbers is 85 more  than the first.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "79; 81; 83",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2618,
        "question": "Find Three consecutive odd integers such that the sum of the last two is 85 more than the first.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals (Plus 85 _smt0) (Plus _smt1 _smt2)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-6",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2619,
        "question": "The sum of three consecutive even integers is -24.  Find the LARGEST integer",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Minus 0 24)) (Equals ?_x1 _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "29; 31; 33; 35",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2620,
        "question": "find four consecutive odd integers, if the sum of the third and fourth is 68",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus _smt2 _smt3) 68) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (IsInteger _smt3) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_3 _smt3))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "13; 14; 15",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2621,
        "question": "find 3 consecutive integers where four times the smallest is seven more than 3 times the largest",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Equals (Plus 7 (Times 3 _smt2)) (Times 4 _smt0)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "13; 14; 15; 16",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2622,
        "question": "the sum of 4 consecutive integers is 58 and twice the smallest is ten more than the largest. find the four numbers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-10; -8; -6; -4",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2623,
        "question": "The sum of four consecutive even integers equals seven times the greatest of the integers.  Find the integers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-10; -8; -6; -4",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2624,
        "question": "The sum of 4 consecutive even integer equals 7 times the greatest of the integers. Find the integers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "65",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2625,
        "question": "if the sum of 7 consecutive integers is 434,then the greatest of the 7 integers is?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{31/3; 4/3} | {10.333; 1.333}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2626,
        "question": "the greater of two numbers is 9 more than the smaller. if the smaller is added to twice the greater the result is 22. find both numbers",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Max (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Plus 9 _smt0)) (Equals 22 (Plus _smt0 (Times 2 _smt1))) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{12; 15}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2627,
        "question": "One number plus twice another number gives a sum of 42.  The difference of these same two numbers equals \ufffdC3.Find the two numbers",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "18; 9/4 | 18; 2.25",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2628,
        "question": "Find two positive numbers so that twice their sum equals their product and one number is 8 times the other number.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals _smt0 (Times 8 _smt1)) (LessThan 0 _smt0) (LessThan 0 _smt1) (Equals (Times _smt0 _smt1) (Times 2 (Plus _smt0 _smt1))) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{12; 13}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2629,
        "question": "The sum of 2 numbers is 25. 12 less than 4 times one of the numbers is 16 more than twice the other number. Find both numbers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{13; 12}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2630,
        "question": "the sum of two numbers is 25. 12 less than four times one of the numbers is 16 more than twice the other number",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "3; 5; 7",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2631,
        "question": "find three consecutive odd integers such that 3 times their sum is 5 more than 8 times the middle one",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals (Plus 5 (Times 8 _smt1)) (Times 3 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)))) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "17; 19; 21",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2632,
        "question": "The sum of three consecutive odd integers is 40 more than the smallest.  What are the integers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Plus 40 _smt0)) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "13; 15; 17",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2633,
        "question": "find three consecutive odd integers such that the sum of the first, twice the second, and three times the third is 94",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals 94 (Sum (Elements _smt0 (Times 2 _smt1) (Times 3 _smt2)))) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "4; 6; 8; 10",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2634,
        "question": "find four consecutive even numbers such that three-fourths of the sum of the second and fourth numbers equals the sum of the first and the third numbers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-23; -21; -19; -17",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2635,
        "question": "What would be the four consecutive odd integers if the sum is -80.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "33.5; 34.5; 35.5",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2636,
        "question": "there are three consecutive integers. half the sum of the second and third number is 35. what are the integers",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "7;35",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2638,
        "question": "The second of two numbers is 5 times the first. Their sum is 42. Find the Numbers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals _smt1 (Times 5 _smt0)) (Equals 42 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "90; 10",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2639,
        "question": "One number is 9 times another. Their sum is 100. Find the numbers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals _smt0 (Times 9 _smt1)) (Equals 100 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "66; 22",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2640,
        "question": "the first of two numbers is 3 times the second. Their sum is 88. Find the numbers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals _smt0 (Times 3 _smt1)) (Equals 88 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "63; 21",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2641,
        "question": "One number is three times another number. Their sum is 84. Find both numbers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals _smt0 (Times 3 _smt1)) (Equals 84 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "60; 30",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2642,
        "question": "One number is two times another number. The sum of the numbers is 90. What are the two numbers",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "76; 38",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2643,
        "question": "One number is twice as large as a second number.  If the sum of the two numbers is 114, what are the two numbers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "24; 8",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2644,
        "question": "Find two numbers whose sum is 32 and such that one is 3 times as large as the other?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{1/50; 9/500} | {0.02; 0.018}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2645,
        "question": "one number is 0.9 of another number. their sum is 0.038. find each number.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{36; 12}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2646,
        "question": "Find two numbers whose sum is 48 and such that one is 3 times as large as the other?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "22; 11",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2647,
        "question": "Find two numbers whose sum is 33 and one of the numbers is two times as large as the other?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{18; 9}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2648,
        "question": "Find two numbers whose sum is 27 and such that one is 2 times as large as the other.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "15",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2649,
        "question": "Three times the first of three consecutive odd integers is 3 more than twice the third. What is the third integer?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Times 3 _smt0) (Plus 3 (Times 2 _smt2))) (Equals ?_x1 _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "6; 7; 8; 9",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2650,
        "question": "Find four consecutive integers such that four times the second diminished by twice the fourth is 10.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "21; 23; 25; 27",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2651,
        "question": "The sum of the first and last of four consecutive odd integers is 48, what are the four integers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "91",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2652,
        "question": "The sum of three consecutive odd integers is 85 less than four times the first. What is the first integer",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Minus (Times 4 _smt0) 85)) (Equals ?_x1 _smt0) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "91",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2653,
        "question": "the sum of 3 consecutive odd integers is 85 less than 4 times the first.  what is the first integer?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Minus (Times 4 _smt0) 85)) (Equals ?_x1 _smt0) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{7; 15}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2655,
        "question": "what are the numbers to be found in this word problem? :the greater number is 1 more than twice the smaller. Three times the greater exceeds 5 times the smaller by 10",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "73; 15",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2656,
        "question": "one number is twenty-eight more than three times another number. If each number were multiplied by four, their difference would be 232. what are the numbers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "30",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2657,
        "question": "two-thirds of a number is decreased by 3 is 2 more than half the number. Find the number.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "34; 35; 36",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2658,
        "question": "The sum of the least and greatest of three consecutive integers is equal to 35 plus the middle integer, what are the integers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "6",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2659,
        "question": "four times the certain number, minus 5, is equal to 7 more than twice the number. What is the number?",
        "semantics": "(Equals (Minus (Times 4 ?_x0) 5) (Plus 7 (Times 2 ?_x0)))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-7",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2660,
        "question": "the sum of four times a number and three is the same as the difference of twice the number and eleven. Find the number.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-2.5 | -5/2",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2661,
        "question": "if 2 is subtracted from four times a number, the result is 3 more than six times the number.  find the number",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Minus (Times 4 _smt0) 2) (Plus 3 (Times 6 _smt0))) (Equals ?_x1 _smt0))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-7",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2662,
        "question": "ten more than 6 times a number is 4 less than 4 times the number. Determine the number.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 _smt0) (Equals (Minus (Times 4 _smt0) 4) (Plus 10 (Times 6 _smt0))))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "47",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2663,
        "question": "Three times a number, increased by 32, has the same value as four times the number, decreased by 15. Find the number.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 _smt0) (Equals (Minus (Times 4 _smt0) 15) (Plus (Times 3 _smt0) 32)))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "14",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2664,
        "question": "5 less than triple a number is nine more than twice a number. Find the number?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 _smt0) (Equals (Plus 9 (Times 2 _smt0)) (Minus (Times 3 _smt0) 5)))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "6; 7; 8 or -6; -5; -4",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2665,
        "question": "Find three consecutive integers such that the square of the sum of the smaller two is 105 more than the square of the largest.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{81; 77}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2666,
        "question": "The difference between two positive integers is 4. If the smaller is added to the square root of the larger, the sum is 86. find the integers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{2.9; 2.8} or {-2.8; -2.9}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2667,
        "question": "The product of two decimal numbers is 8.12. The difference of the two numbers is 0.1. What are the two numbers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{12; 8}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2668,
        "question": "Find two positive integers whose difference is 4 and whose product is 96",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 4 (Minus _smt1 _smt0)) (Equals 96 (Times _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (LessThan 0 _smt0) (LessThan 0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{12; 13} or {-13; -12}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2669,
        "question": "The product of two consecutive integers x and y is 156. Find the two integers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{12; 7} or {-7; -12}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2671,
        "question": "One integer is 5 more than another. Their product is 84. Find the integers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals _smt0 (Plus 5 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Equals 84 (Times _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{17; 8} or {-8; -17}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2672,
        "question": "one integer is 9 more than another. their product is 136. Find the integers",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals _smt0 (Plus 9 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Equals 136 (Times _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "38",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2673,
        "question": "There are four consecutive even integers.  Half the sum of the second and third is 35. What is the last integer?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "19; 21; 23",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2674,
        "question": "find the three consecutive odd integers such that the sum of the first and third is 42",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus _smt0 _smt2) 42) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "32; 34; 36",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2675,
        "question": "The sum of the largest and smallest of three consecutive even numbers is 68. What are the three numbers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "21; 23; 25",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2676,
        "question": "find 3 consecutive odd integers so that the sum of the least integer and middle integer is 44",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus (Min (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) _smt1) 44) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (IsInteger (Min (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "35; 21; 735 | 21; 35; 735",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2677,
        "question": "The difference between two numbers is 14. The sum of the two numbers is 56. What are the two numbers and their product?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "20; 22; 24; 26",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2678,
        "question": "the greatest of four consecutive even integers is 14 less than twice the smallest integer. what are the integers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (IsInteger _smt3) (Equals (Max (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3)) (Minus (Times 2 _smt0) 14)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Le _smt2 _smt3) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_3 _smt3))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "14; 16; 18; 20",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2679,
        "question": "find four consecutive even integers such that the sum of twice the first, five times the second, and four times the third divided by three times the fourth equals three",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "0; 1; 2; 3",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2681,
        "question": "four consecutive integers such that the sum of the first three integers equal to the fourth. what are the integers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "0; 1; 2; 3",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2682,
        "question": "find the four consecutive such that the sum of the first three integers is equal to the fourth",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "23;60;51",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2683,
        "question": "The sum of three numbers is 134. The second number is 9 less than 3 times the first number. The third number is 5 more than 2 times the first number. Find the three numbers",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "21;33;69",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2684,
        "question": "The sum of three numbers is 123. The second number is 9 less than two times the first number. The third number is 6 more than three times the first number. Find the three numbers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "23; 50; 64",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2685,
        "question": "The sum of three numbers is 137. The second number is 4 more than two times the first number. The third number is 5 less than three times the first number. Find the three numbers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "50; 51; 52; 53",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2686,
        "question": "Find four consecutive integers such that the square of the 3rd number is 154 more than the product of the first two numbers",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (IsInteger _smt3) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3)) (Equals (Plus 154 (Times _smt0 _smt1)) (Pow _smt2 2)) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_2 _smt2) (Equals ?_x1_3 _smt3))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "31; 33; 35; 37",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2687,
        "question": "Of four consecutive odd numbers the product of the second and the fourth exceeds the product of the first and the third by 136. Find the numbers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "2",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2688,
        "question": "Find a number such that three times the sum of four and the number is 18",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 _smt0) (Equals (Times 3 (Plus 4 _smt0)) 18))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "11",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2689,
        "question": "Three times the sum of five and a number is 48. Find the number.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Times 3 (Plus 5 _smt0)) 48) (Equals ?_x1 _smt0))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-6/5 | -1.2",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2690,
        "question": "five times the sum of a number and nine is thirty nine",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "8",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2691,
        "question": "add 3 to a number then double the result. if the total is 22 find the number",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "10",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2692,
        "question": "The product of 8 and the sum of 4 and a number is 112. What is the number?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Times 8 (Plus 4 _smt0)) 112) (Equals ?_x1 _smt0))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "2",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2693,
        "question": "Three times the sum of a number and five gives a result of 21. Find the number?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "99",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2694,
        "question": "How many times larger is the 5 in the number 5263 than the 5 in the number 456",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-3",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2695,
        "question": "Five times the sum of a number and eight is twenty-five. Find the number.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 _smt0) (Equals (Plus 20 5) (Times 5 (Plus _smt0 8))))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "13; 14; 15",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2696,
        "question": "find 3 consecutive integers such that the sum of twice the second and three times the third is 5 less than six times the first",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Equals (Minus (Times 6 _smt0) 5) (Plus (Times 2 _smt1) (Times 3 _smt2))) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "13; 14; 15",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2697,
        "question": "Find three consecutive integers such that the sum of twice the second and three times the third is five less than six times the first.",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Equals (Minus (Times 6 _smt0) 5) (Plus (Times 2 _smt1) (Times 3 _smt2))) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{3; 1/3} or {-3; -1/3} | {3; 0.333} or {-3; -0.333}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2701,
        "question": "Two numbers are reciprocals of each other. One number is 9 times as large as the other. Find the two numbers",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-3",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2702,
        "question": "when 23 is added to 4 times a certain number the answer is 11. Find this number",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 11 (Plus 23 (Times 4 _smt0))) (Equals _smt0 ?_x1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "9",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2703,
        "question": "if 25 is added to three times of a number 52 is obtained. find the number.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "2",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2704,
        "question": "two more than the product of 5 and x is 12",
        "semantics": "(Equals 12 (Plus 2 (Times 5 x)))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "8",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2705,
        "question": "if 6 times a number is added to 8, the result is 56. What is the number",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 56 (Plus (Times 6 _smt0) 8)) (Equals ?_x1 _smt0))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-11/6 | -1.833",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2706,
        "question": "The difference of 10 and the product of 6 and n is 21.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "3",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2707,
        "question": "three more than the product of a number and 4 is 15. Find the number.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus 3 (Times _smt0 4)) 15) (Equals ?_x1 _smt0))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-2",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2708,
        "question": "three less than twice what number is -7?",
        "semantics": "(Equals (Minus (Times 2 ?_x0) 3) (Minus 0 7))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-4",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2709,
        "question": "the sum of 3 times a number and 17 is 5. what is the number?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus (Times 3 _smt0) 17) 5) (Equals ?_x1 _smt0))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "24",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2710,
        "question": "If you double a number and then add 32,the result is 80. What is the number?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "8",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2711,
        "question": "Two less than the product of a number and -5 is -42? What is the number?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 _smt0) (Equals (Minus 0 42) (Minus (Times _smt0 (Minus 0 5)) 2)))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "6; 7; 8",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2712,
        "question": "Find three consecutive integers such that the sum of the first and second is 9 more than half of the third.",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Equals (Plus 9 (Times 0.5 _smt2)) (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "31; 33; 35",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2713,
        "question": "The sum of three consecutive odd integers is 41 less than four times the largest. Find the numbers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Minus (Times 4 _smt2) 41)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{24; 12} or {-24; -12}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2714,
        "question": "one is twice another number. When the larger number is diminished by 10, the result is two greater than the smaller. Find the numbers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{5; 15}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2715,
        "question": "The difference between two numbers is 10 and their sum is equal to 4 times the smaller number. What are the numbers ?.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 10 (Minus _smt1 _smt0)) (Equals (Plus _smt0 _smt1) (Times 4 _smt0)) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "61; 62; 63; 64",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2716,
        "question": "Find four consecutive integers such that the sum of the second and the fourth is fifty-seven less than thrice the first.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-2.5",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2717,
        "question": "Five times some number is 10 less than the number.  What is the number?",
        "semantics": "(Equals (Minus ?_x0 10) (Times 5 ?_x0))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-2",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2718,
        "question": "Two more than twice a number is equal to the number itself. Find the number.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "970",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2719,
        "question": "The sum of two numbers is 1457. Four times the first number minus twice the second number is 8. Find the larger number.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus _smt0 _smt1) 1457) (Equals (Minus (Times 4 _smt0) (Times 2 _smt1)) 8) (Equals ?_x1 (Max (Elements _smt0 _smt1))))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "9",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2720,
        "question": "The sum of two numbers is 3 and twice the larger number is 36 more than three times the smaller number.What is the larger number?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus _smt0 _smt1) 3) (Equals (Times 2 _smt1) (Plus 36 (Times 3 _smt0))) (Equals ?_x1 _smt1) (Le _smt0 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "2; 4; 6",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2721,
        "question": "Find three consecutive even integers such that twice the sum of the first and third is four more than three times the second.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals (Plus 4 (Times 3 _smt1)) (Times 2 (Plus _smt0 _smt2))) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "4; 5; 6",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2722,
        "question": "For three consecutive integers, when four times the third is subtracted from five times the first, the result is -4. Find the integers",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "40;42;44",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2723,
        "question": "twice the first of three consecutive even integers minus the third equals 36. Find the three integers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "70",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2724,
        "question": "If the sum of six consecutive even integers is 450, what is the smallest of the six integers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3 _smt4 _smt5)) 450) (Equals ?_x1 (Min (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3 _smt4 _smt5))) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3 _smt4 _smt5)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (IsInteger _smt3) (IsInteger _smt4) (IsInteger _smt5) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Le _smt2 _smt3) (Le _smt3 _smt4) (Le _smt4 _smt5))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "5;7;9",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2725,
        "question": "three times the largest of three consecutive odd integers is three less than twice the sum of the other two integers. find the integers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "7; 9; 11",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2726,
        "question": "What are three consecutive odd integers so that five times the middle integer is nine more than twice the sum of the first and third integers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "25; 27; 29",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2727,
        "question": "find three consecutive odd integers such that five times the sum of the first and second is 1 less than 9 times the third",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals (Minus (Times 9 _smt2) 1) (Times 5 (Plus _smt0 _smt1))) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "40",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2728,
        "question": "5 less than the product of 15 and 3",
        "semantics": "(Equals ?_x0 (Minus (Times 15 3) 5))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "5; 7; 9",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2729,
        "question": "Find three consecutive odd integers such that three times the first integer is one less than the sum of the second and third integers",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "5; 7; 9",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2730,
        "question": "find three consecutive odd integers such that three times the smallest equals the sum of the other two integers decreased by 1?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "8",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2731,
        "question": "the difference of 67 and an integer is 3 more than the product of 8 and 7. what is the integer?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 _smt0) (IsInteger _smt0) (Equals (Plus 3 (Times 8 7)) (Difference (Elements 67 _smt0))))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-4; -2; 0",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2732,
        "question": "The smallest of three consecutive even integers is 4 less than 5 times the largest.   Find the integers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals (Min (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Minus (Times 5 _smt2) 4)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "2; 4; 6 or -18; -16; -14 | 2; 4; 6 | -18; -16; -14",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2733,
        "question": "Three consecutive even integers are such that the difference of the smallest integer and twice the largest integer is 10. Find the three integers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "18; 20; 22",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2734,
        "question": "Find three consecutive even integers such as that twice the sum of the first and second is 10 more than three times the third.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "31; 32; 33; 34",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2735,
        "question": "find four consecutive integers if the sum of the first and second is 63",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus _smt0 _smt1) 63) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (IsInteger _smt3) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_3 _smt3))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-32",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2736,
        "question": "the sum of four consecutive odd integers is -64. what is the sum of the smallest and largest of the four integers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3)) (Minus 0 64)) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (IsInteger _smt3) (Equals ?_x4 (Plus _smt0 (Max (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3)))) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Le _smt2 _smt3))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-5; -3",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2737,
        "question": "the larger of two consecutive odd integers is 7 greater than twice the smaller. Find the integers",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-3; -1",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2738,
        "question": "The greater of two consecutive odd integers is eight more than three times the lesser",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-22; -20",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2739,
        "question": "Three times the smaller of two consecutive even integers is equal to -146 minus four times the larger of the two integers. What are the two even integers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-20; -16",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2740,
        "question": "the sum of 3 consecutive even integers is fourteen less than twice the smallest of these integers. Find the smallest and greatest integer",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Minus (Times 2 (Min (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) 14)) (Equals ?_x2_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x2_1 _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{7; 5}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2741,
        "question": "One positive integer is 3 less than twice another. Find these two integers if the difference of their squares is 24.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Difference (Elements (Pow _smt0 2) (Pow _smt1 2))) 24) (IsInteger _smt0) (LessThan 0 _smt0) (Equals _smt0 (Minus (Times 2 _smt1) 3)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-1; 0",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2742,
        "question": "three times the sum of two consecutive integers is three less than two times the larger integer. find the integers",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "14; 16; 18",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2743,
        "question": "Find three consecutive even integers such that four times the first minus the third is six more than twice the second.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals (Plus 6 (Times 2 _smt1)) (Minus (Times 4 _smt0) _smt2)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "12; 13; 14",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2744,
        "question": "Find three consecutive integers such that the sum of twice the first number and three times the third number is fourteen more than four times the second number",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Equals (Plus 14 (Times 4 _smt1)) (Plus (Times 2 _smt0) (Times 3 _smt2))) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "37; 38; 39; 40; 41",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2745,
        "question": "five consecutive integers whose sum is 195",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 195 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3 _smt4))) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (IsInteger _smt3) (IsInteger _smt4) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3 _smt4)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Le _smt2 _smt3) (Le _smt3 _smt4) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_3 _smt3) (Equals ?_x0_4 _smt4))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "16; 17; 18; 19; 20",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2746,
        "question": "find five consecutive whole numbers sum 90",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-2; -1; 0; 1; 2",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2747,
        "question": "the sum of five consecutive integers is 0. find the integers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "14; 16; 18",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2748,
        "question": "find three consecutive even integers, such that the sum of the second and third number is 20 more than the first.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals (Plus 20 _smt0) (Plus _smt1 _smt2)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "24;26;28",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2749,
        "question": "Find three consecutive even integers such that the sum of the second and third integers is 30 more than the first integer.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "18; 20",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2750,
        "question": "for two consecutive even integers, the sum of the smaller and twice the larger is 58",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "6; 8",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2751,
        "question": "Find two consecutive even integers such that the smaller added to three times the larger give a sum of 30.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "6; 8",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2752,
        "question": "Find two consecutive even integers such that the smaller added to five times the larger gives a sum of 46.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "31",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2753,
        "question": "The sum of two numbers is 58 and their difference is 4. Which is the greater of the two numbers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus _smt0 _smt1) 58) (Equals (Minus _smt1 _smt0) 4) (Equals ?_x1 (Max (Elements _smt0 _smt1))))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "60",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2754,
        "question": "The Sum of two consecutive even integers in 118. What is the 2nd number?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "16",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2755,
        "question": "One number is 9 less than the other. The sum of the two numbers is 41. Find the smaller integer.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus (Minus _smt1 9) _smt1) 41) (Equals ?_x1 (Min (Elements (Minus _smt1 9) _smt1))) (IsInteger (Min (Elements (Minus _smt1 9) _smt1))))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "28",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2756,
        "question": "One number is 4 more than another, and their sum is 60. What is the smaller number?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus (Plus 4 _smt1) _smt1) 60) (Equals ?_x1 (Min (Elements (Plus 4 _smt1) _smt1))))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "79; 81; 83",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2757,
        "question": "The sum of three consecutive odd integers is equal to the sum of two times the largest integer and seventy-seven. Find the numbers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Plus (Times 2 _smt2) (Plus 70 7))) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "11; 13; 15",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2758,
        "question": "Find three consecutive odd numbers whose sum is 5 more than twice the next     consecutive number.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-210; -208; -206",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2759,
        "question": "Find three consecutive even integers whose sum is -624.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Minus 0 624) (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "5 or -5",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2760,
        "question": "Eighteen more than the square of an integer is 43. What is the integer?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus 18 (Pow _smt0 2)) 43) (Equals ?_x1 _smt0) (IsInteger _smt0))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "47; 48 | -48; -47 | 47; 48 or -48; -47",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2762,
        "question": "The squares of two consecutive integers differ by 95. What are These integers ?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Difference (Elements (Pow _smt0 2) (Pow _smt1 2))) 95) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "3; 6 or -4; -1",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2763,
        "question": "There are two numbers. the second number is 3 more than the first. the product of the two numbers is 9 more than their sum. What are the two numbers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "3; 6 or -4; -1",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2764,
        "question": "There are two numbers with the following properties.1. the second number is 3 more than the first number.2. The product of the two numbers is 9 more than their sum.Determine the two numbers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "21;23;25 or 3;5;7",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2765,
        "question": "find three consecutive odd integers such that the product of the second and third is 55 less than 30 times the first",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals (Minus (Times 30 _smt0) 55) (Times _smt1 _smt2)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "1;2;3;4",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2766,
        "question": "Find four consecutive positive integers such that the product of the first and the fourth is four less than twice the first multiplied by the fourth",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (IsInteger _smt3) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3)) (LessThan 0 _smt0) (LessThan 0 _smt1) (LessThan 0 _smt2) (LessThan 0 _smt3) (Equals (Minus (Times (Times 2 _smt0) _smt3) 4) (Times _smt0 _smt3)) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_2 _smt2) (Equals ?_x1_3 _smt3))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-13 | -26/5 | -5.2",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2767,
        "question": "3 times the sum of twice a number and 6 is 4 times 2 less than the number.  find the number.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 _smt0) (Equals (Times 4 (Minus _smt0 2)) (Times 3 (Plus (Times 2 _smt0) 6))))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{9; 11} or {-11; -9}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2768,
        "question": "Two consecutive odd integers have a product of 99. Find all sets of integers that satisfy this description.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "7; 9 or -9; -7",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2769,
        "question": "The product of two consecutive odd integers is 63.  Find the numbers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Equals 63 (Times _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "2; 3",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2770,
        "question": "the difference of 3 times the larger consecutive integer and the smaller consecutive integer is 7",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "17;19",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2771,
        "question": "The product of two consecutive positive odd integers is 38 less than the square of the greater integer. Find the integers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (LessThan 0 _smt0) (LessThan 0 _smt1) (Equals (Times _smt0 _smt1) (Minus (Pow _smt1 2) 38)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{-1; -11} | -11; -1 or -1; -11",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2772,
        "question": "Two negative integers have a sum of -12 and a product of 11. What are the integers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus _smt0 _smt1) (Minus 0 12)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (LessThan _smt0 0) (LessThan _smt1 0) (Equals 11 (Times _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "16; 18 or -18;-16",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2773,
        "question": "what are 2 consecutive even integers whose product plus two is 290",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "12",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2774,
        "question": "if three times the smaller of two consecutive even integers is added to two times the larger, the result is 64. what is the smaller of the two integers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 64 (Plus (Times 3 (Min (Elements _smt0 _smt1))) (Times 2 _smt1))) (Equals ?_x2 (Min (Elements _smt0 _smt1))) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Le _smt0 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-2; 0; 2",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2775,
        "question": "Find three consecutive even integers such that four times the middle integer is equal to the sum of the first and third integers",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "151",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2776,
        "question": "Find the larger of two consecutive integers if the larger is 149 less than twice the smaller.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 (Max (Elements _smt0 (Minus (Times 2 _smt0) 149)))) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger (Minus (Times 2 _smt0) 149)) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 (Minus (Times 2 _smt0) 149))) (Le _smt0 (Minus (Times 2 _smt0) 149)))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "ans_no_result",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2777,
        "question": "What is the greater of two consecutive even integers that is four less than three times the smaller integer?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{-8; 5; 15}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2778,
        "question": "Three integers have these characteristics: their sum is 12; the sum of the smallest and largest integers is 7; the middle integer is one third of the largest integer. What are the integers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "20; 22; 24",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2779,
        "question": "Find three consecutive even integers such that the sum of the second and third is equal to three times the first decreased by 14.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals (Plus _smt1 _smt2) (Minus (Times 3 _smt0) 14)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{27; 15}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2780,
        "question": "The sum of two numbers is 42.  One number plus 2 times the other number is 57.  What are the numbers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 42 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals 57 (Plus _smt0 (Times 2 _smt1))) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "14; 10",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2781,
        "question": "The sum of two numbers is 24 and the sum of the first number and twice the second is 34. Find the numbers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 24 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals 34 (Plus _smt0 (Times 2 _smt1))) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "22; 24; 26; 28",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2782,
        "question": "Find four consecutive even integers such that twice the sum of the second and third exceeds 3 times the first by 34",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (IsInteger _smt3) (Equals (Plus (Times 3 _smt0) 34) (Times 2 (Plus _smt1 _smt2))) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_3 _smt3))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "10",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2783,
        "question": "the sum of the squares of 3 consecutive positive numbers is 365. find the smallest of the 3",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 (Min (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (LessThan 0 _smt0) (LessThan 0 _smt1) (LessThan 0 _smt2) (Equals 365 (Sum (Elements (Pow _smt0 2) (Pow _smt1 2) (Pow _smt2 2)))) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "3;5;7",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2784,
        "question": "Determine three consecutive odd integers such that the product of the first two integers is equal to the sum of all three integers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-5; -3; -1; 1; 3",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2785,
        "question": "Find 5 consecutive odd integers with the sum of -5",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "117",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2786,
        "question": "the sum of three consecutive odd integers is 33. what is the product of the least and the greatest integer.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "11",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2787,
        "question": "the sum of four consecutive odd integers is 56 find the first",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "13 or 24 or 35 or 46 or 57 or 68 or 79",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2788,
        "question": "the ones digit of a 2 digit number is 2 greater than the tens digit, if the original number is subtracted from its interchanged form the difference is 18,find the original number",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-6; -5",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2789,
        "question": "The sum of two consecutive integers is five less than the smaller integer. Find both integers",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "9",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2790,
        "question": "If the product of 2 consecutive positive odd integers is 15 more than 3 times their sum, then the larger integer is?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Times _smt0 _smt1) (Plus 15 (Times 3 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)))) (Equals _smt1 ?_x1) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (LessThan 0 _smt0) (LessThan 0 _smt1) (Le _smt0 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "3",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2791,
        "question": "The sum of the square of a positive number and the square of 4 more than the number is 58. what is the number?",
        "semantics": "(And (LessThan 0 ?_x0) (Equals _smt0 ?_x0) (Equals 58 (Plus (Pow _smt0 2) (Pow (Plus 4 ?_x0) 2))))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "1;3;5",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2792,
        "question": "find three consecutive odd positive integers such that 5 times the sum of all three is 42 more than the product of the first and  second integer",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (LessThan 0 _smt0) (LessThan 0 _smt1) (LessThan 0 _smt2) (Equals (Plus 42 (Times _smt0 _smt1)) (Times 5 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)))) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "5 or -7",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2793,
        "question": "The square of an integer plus two times the integer is 35. Find all possible solutions.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "9",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2794,
        "question": "if the square of a positive integer is added to 6 times the integer, the result is 135. find the integer",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 135 (Plus (Pow _smt0 2) (Times 6 ?_x1))) (IsInteger ?_x1) (LessThan 0 ?_x1) (Equals _smt0 ?_x1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-10 or 0",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2795,
        "question": "When the square of an integer is added to ten times the integer, the sum is zero.  What is the integer?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 0 (Plus (Pow _smt0 2) (Times 10 _smt0))) (Equals ?_x1 _smt0) (IsInteger _smt0))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "44; 45; 46; 47",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2796,
        "question": "There are 4 consecutive integers.  Their sum is 100 decreased by twice the difference between the greatest and twice the least. Determine the integers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-3; -2; -1; 0",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2797,
        "question": "find four consecutive integers such that if the sum of the first and third is increased by 10 the result is 6 greater than 4 times the fourth",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (IsInteger _smt3) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3)) (Equals (Plus 10 (Plus _smt0 _smt2)) (Plus 6 (Times 4 _smt3))) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_2 _smt2) (Equals ?_x1_3 _smt3))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "61; 62; 63; 64",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2798,
        "question": "There are four consecutive integers.  The sum of the first and fourth of these consecutive integers is 125.  Find all four consecutive integers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "26; 27; 28",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2799,
        "question": "Find three consecutive integers such that three times the smallest integer, increased by the largest integer equals 106.",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Equals 106 (Plus (Times 3 _smt0) _smt2)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "12;13;14",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2801,
        "question": "Three consecutive integers such that the sum of the first, twice the second and three times the third is 80. What are the integers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "15; 16; 17",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2802,
        "question": "find three consecutive integers such that the sum of the first and twice the second is 98 minus three times the third",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Equals (Minus 98 (Times 3 _smt2)) (Plus _smt0 (Times 2 _smt1))) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "25; 26; 27",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2803,
        "question": "The sum of three consecutive integers is 78. Find the numbers.",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Equals 78 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "267;268;269",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2804,
        "question": "Find 3 consecutive integers whose sum is 804",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 804 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "25; 26; 27",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2805,
        "question": "find 3 consecutive integers whose sum is 78",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 78 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "43; 44; 45",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2806,
        "question": "The sum of three consecutive integers is one hundred thirty-two. Find the integers.",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Equals (Plus (Times 1 100) (Plus 30 2)) (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "155; 156; 157",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2807,
        "question": "The sum of three consecutive integers is 468. find the numbers.",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Equals 468 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "21;22;23",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2808,
        "question": "What is the three consecutive numbers if they add up to 66",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 66 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "5; 7; 9",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2809,
        "question": "find three consecutive odd integers such that the second is 20 less than 3 times the third integer",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals _smt1 (Minus (Times 3 _smt2) 20)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "14;15;16",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2811,
        "question": "Find three consecutive integers such that twice the least integer is 12 more than the greatest integer.",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Equals (Plus 12 _smt2) (Times 2 _smt0)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "14;15;16",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2812,
        "question": "find three consecutive integers. The largest integer added to twelve equals twice the smaller integer",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Equals (Times 2 _smt0) (Plus _smt2 12)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "25;26;27",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2813,
        "question": "Find three consecutive numbers such that twice the smallest number is 23 more than the largest.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Equals (Plus 23 _smt2) (Times 2 _smt0)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "25;26;27",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2814,
        "question": "Find three consecutive numbers such that twice the smallest is 23 more than the largest",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Equals (Plus 23 _smt2) (Times 2 _smt0)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "105;107;109;111",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2815,
        "question": "find four consecutive odd numbers whose sum is 432",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 432 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3))) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Le _smt2 _smt3) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_3 _smt3))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "7",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2816,
        "question": "If 5 times a integer is subtracted from twice the square of the integer, the result is 63. Find the integer",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 63 (Minus (Times 2 (Pow _smt0 2)) (Times 5 _smt0))) (Equals ?_x1 _smt0) (IsInteger _smt0))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "9",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2817,
        "question": "Three times the square of a positive number decreased by 20 times the number is 63. Find the number.",
        "semantics": "(And (LessThan 0 ?_x0) (Equals _smt0 ?_x0) (Equals 63 (Minus (Times 3 (Pow _smt0 2)) (Times 20 ?_x0))))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "12;13;14",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2818,
        "question": "find three consecutive integers whose sum is 11 more than twice the greatest of the three integers.",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Plus 11 (Times 2 (Max (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))))) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "2;3;4",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2819,
        "question": "find three consecutive integers such that three times the middle integer is equal to the sum of five times the first and three times the third integer decreased by 13",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Equals (Times 3 _smt1) (Plus (Times 5 _smt0) (Minus (Times 3 _smt2) 13))) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "4; 6; 8",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2820,
        "question": "Find three consecutive even integers such that twice the sum of the first and third is twelve more than twice the second.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals (Plus 12 (Times 2 _smt1)) (Times 2 (Plus _smt0 _smt2))) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "37; 39; 41",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2821,
        "question": "Find three consecutive odd integers such that four times the sum of the first and second is 17 more than 7 times the third",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals (Plus 17 (Times 7 _smt2)) (Times 4 (Plus _smt0 _smt1))) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "5;7;9",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2822,
        "question": "find three consecutive positive odd integers such that the product of the second and third integers is 18 more than 9 times the first integer",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "8;10;12",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2823,
        "question": "Find three consecutive positive even integers such that the sum of the squares of the first and second integers is equal to the square of the third integer plus 20.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "27",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2824,
        "question": "If four consecutive odd integers had a sum of 96, what would be the largest integer?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "6 or -6",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2825,
        "question": "Twelve more than one-half the square of a number is 30. What is the number?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus 12 (Times 0.5 (Pow _smt0 2))) 30) (Equals ?_x1 _smt0))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "220;222",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2826,
        "question": "find two consecutive even integers whose sum is 442.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 442 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "44;46;48;50",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2827,
        "question": "what are four consecutive even integers whose sum is 188",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 188 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3))) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (IsInteger _smt3) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Le _smt2 _smt3) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_3 _smt3))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "52; 54; 56; 58",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2828,
        "question": "The sum of four consecutive even integers is 220. Find all four numbers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "0;2 or 10;12",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2830,
        "question": "The product of which two consecutive even integers is 12  less than 6  times their sum?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Times _smt0 _smt1) (Minus (Times 6 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) 12)) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-35",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2831,
        "question": "The sum of two consecutive odd integers is -72 . What is the larger integer?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus _smt0 _smt1) (Minus 0 72)) (Equals ?_x1 _smt1) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Le _smt0 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "25",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2832,
        "question": "Two consecutive odd integers have a sum of 48. What is the largest of the two integers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus _smt0 _smt1) 48) (Equals ?_x1 (Max (Elements _smt0 _smt1))) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Le _smt0 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "7;9 or -3;-1",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2833,
        "question": "How do i solve two consecutive odd integers such that their product is 15 more than three times their sum?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "31",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2834,
        "question": "The sum of the larger of two consecutive numbers and five times the smaller one is 187. What is the smallest of the integers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 (Min (Elements _smt0 _smt1))) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals 187 (Plus (Max (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Times 5 _smt0))) (Le _smt0 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "13",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2835,
        "question": "An odd number when added to its squares equals to 182. find the odd number",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{25; 16}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2836,
        "question": "Divide 41 into two positive parts such that difference of their squares is 369.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{7; 5}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2837,
        "question": "Find two integers whose sum is 12 and whose squares differ by 24.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 12 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals (Difference (Elements (Pow _smt0 2) (Pow _smt1 2))) 24) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{18; 7}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2838,
        "question": "The sum of two positive integers is 25.The difference of their squares is 275.What are the two integers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "7 or -3",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2839,
        "question": "find the number such that its square is 21 more than four times the original number",
        "semantics": "(Equals (Pow ?_x0 2) (Plus 21 (Times 4 ?_x0)))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "ans_no_result",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2840,
        "question": "Nine times a certain integer is 18 less than the square of the integer. Find the integer.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-1 or 5",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2841,
        "question": "four times an integer plus 5 is equal to the square of the integer. what is the integer?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 _smt0) (IsInteger _smt0) (Equals (Plus (Times 4 _smt0) 5) (Pow _smt0 2)))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "ans_no_result",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2842,
        "question": "find three consecutive positive even integers such that the product of the second and third integers is 15",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "23;24;25;26",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2843,
        "question": "What are four consecutive integers whose sum is 98",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 98 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3))) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (IsInteger _smt3) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Le _smt2 _smt3) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_3 _smt3))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "6;8;10",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2844,
        "question": "find 3 consecutive even integers such that three times the first equals the sum of  the other two",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "6; 8; 10",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2845,
        "question": "find the 3 consecutive even integers such that 3 times the first equal the sum of the other 2.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "1",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2846,
        "question": "If the product of 3 consecutive odd integers is 15 what is the smallest of the 3 integers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Product (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) 15) (Equals ?_x1 (Min (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "16; 18; 20",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2847,
        "question": "Find three consecutive even integers such that the sum of three times the first, and twice the third is twenty less than six times the second.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals (Minus (Times 6 _smt1) 20) (Plus (Times 3 _smt0) (Times 2 _smt2))) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-6; -4; -2",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2848,
        "question": "find 3 consecutive even integers such that 4 times the sum of the first and the third is 8 less than six times the second",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals (Minus (Times 6 _smt1) 8) (Times 4 (Plus _smt0 _smt2))) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "7;8;9",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2849,
        "question": "Find three consecutive integers if the sum of the first two integers is 6 more than the third integer",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Equals (Plus 6 _smt2) (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "10; 12; 14",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2850,
        "question": "Find three consecutive even integers such that the sum of the least integer and the greatest integer is 12 more than the middle integer",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (IsInteger (Min (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (IsInteger (Max (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Equals (Plus 12 _smt1) (Plus (Min (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Max (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)))) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "7;9;11",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2851,
        "question": "find three consecutive odd integers such that three times the second number added to twice the third number is seven times the first integer.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals (Times 7 _smt0) (Plus (Times 3 _smt1) (Times 2 _smt2))) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "14;16;18;20",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2852,
        "question": "seven times the smallest of four consecutive even integers is the same as two less than five times the largest of the integers. what are the four integers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "6; 8",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2853,
        "question": "Find two positive consecutive even integers whose product is 8 more than 5 times the larger integer.",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Equals (Times _smt0 _smt1) (Plus 8 (Times 5 _smt1))) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (LessThan 0 _smt0) (LessThan 0 _smt1) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-2; 0; 2 or 2; 4; 6 or -6; -4; -2",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2854,
        "question": "What are three consecutive even integers whose product is 4 times their sum?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "2; 4; 6",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2855,
        "question": "Find three consecutive even integers such that twice the sum of the second and third is 4 less than 6 times the second",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals (Minus (Times 6 _smt1) 4) (Times 2 (Plus _smt1 _smt2))) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-15; -14; -13; -12",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2856,
        "question": "find four consecutive integers such that if the sum of the first and third is multiplied by 2, the result is 20 less than three times the fourth",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (IsInteger _smt3) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3)) (Equals (Times (Plus _smt0 _smt2) 2) (Minus (Times 3 _smt3) 20)) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_2 _smt2) (Equals ?_x1_3 _smt3))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "8; 10 or -12; -10",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2857,
        "question": "The product of two consecutive even integers plus their sum is 98. Find the numbers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus (Times _smt0 _smt1) (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) 98) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-21; -19; -17",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2858,
        "question": "Find three consecutive odd integers such that the sum of the first and second is equal to 23 less than the third",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals (Plus _smt0 _smt1) (Minus _smt2 23)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-9; -8; -7",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2859,
        "question": "Find three consecutive integers where the sum of the two smaller integers is 4 more than 3 times the largest.",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Equals (Plus 4 (Times 3 _smt2)) (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "88",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2860,
        "question": "three consecutive even integers whose sum is 264. what is the second number?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "21",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2861,
        "question": "What is the largest of the three consecutive odd integers whose sum is 57",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 (Max (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Equals 57 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "47",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2862,
        "question": "The sum of three consecutive odd numbers is 135. Find the largest odd number?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) 135) (Equals ?_x1 (Max _x2)) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _x4) (IsInteger (Plus 1 _x4)) (IsInteger 2) (Equals (Mod (Plus 1 _x4) 2) 0) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "79",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2863,
        "question": "3 Rosenberg sisters' ages are consecutive odd integers. If the sum of their ages is 231, how old is oldest sister",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "1",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2864,
        "question": "find the largest of three consecutive odd integers whose sum is -3",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 (Max (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Equals (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Minus 0 3)) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "12; 13",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2865,
        "question": "4 times an integer is 9 more than 3 times the next consecutive integer.  What are the two integers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{27; 18}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2866,
        "question": "the difference of two integers is 9. five times the smaller is 9 more than three times the larger. find the integers.",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Equals 9 (Minus _smt1 _smt0)) (Equals (Plus 9 (Times 3 _smt1)) (Times 5 _smt0)) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "8; 10",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2867,
        "question": "find two consecutive even integers such that five times the smaller integer is ten more than three times the larger integer",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Equals (Plus 10 (Times 3 _smt1)) (Times 5 _smt0)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "15; 17; 19; 21",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2868,
        "question": "Find four consecutive odd integers such that the sum of the first and fourth is 55 greater than the opposite of the third",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (IsInteger _smt3) (Equals (Plus 55 (Minus 0 _smt2)) (Plus _smt0 _smt3)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_3 _smt3))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "59; 60; 61",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2870,
        "question": "find the 3 consecutive integers such that one half of their sum is 90.",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Equals 90 (Times 0.5 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)))) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "0; 1; 2",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2871,
        "question": "suppose you have three consecutive integers. The greatest of the three integers is twice as great as the sum of the first two. What are the integers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "2; 4; 6",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2872,
        "question": "what is the 3 consecutive even integers such that the largest is 3 times the smallest",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "40; 42; 44",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2873,
        "question": "find three consecutive even integers such that their sum decreased by the third integer is 82",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Minus (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) _smt2) 82) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "30",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2874,
        "question": "Consider four consecutive integers. What is the sum of the 2nd and fourth numbers if the first number is 13.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "38",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2875,
        "question": "The sum of digits of a two digit positive integer is 11. If the digit at one's place is one less than the square of the digit at the ten's place. Find the number?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "76; 78; 80",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2876,
        "question": "find three consecutive even numbers whose sum is 234",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 234 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "9; 11; 13",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2877,
        "question": "Find three consecutive odd integers such that four times the smallest integer added to four times the largest integer equals 88",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals 88 (Plus (Times 4 _smt0) (Times 4 _smt2))) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "40; 41; 42; 43; 44",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2878,
        "question": "Find five consecutive numbers that the sum of the first and the last is 84.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "19; 21; 23; 25; 27",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2879,
        "question": "There are five consecutive odd integers. The sum of the first two numbers is thirty-five less than the sum of the last three numbers. What are the integers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3 _smt4)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (IsInteger _smt3) (IsInteger _smt4) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Le _smt2 _smt3) (Le _smt3 _smt4) (Equals (Elements _smt5 _smt6 _smt7 _smt8 _smt9) (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3 _smt4)) (Consecutive (Elements _smt5 _smt6 _smt7 _smt8 _smt9)) (IsInteger _x1) (Equals (Minus (Sum (Elements _smt7 _smt8 _smt9)) (Plus 30 5)) (Plus _smt5 _smt6)) (Le _smt5 _smt6) (Le _smt6 _smt7) (Le _smt7 _smt8) (Le _smt8 _smt9) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt5) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt6) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt7) (Equals ?_x0_3 _smt8) (Equals ?_x0_4 _smt9))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "86; 88; 90",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2881,
        "question": "The sum of the first and third of three consecutive even integers is 176. What are the three  even integers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "4; 6; 8",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2882,
        "question": "What are the three consecutive even integers so that the value three times the second integer is equal to six more than the sum of the first and third integers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "31; 32; 33; 34; 35",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2883,
        "question": "find 5 consecutive integers whose sum of the first, third, and fifth is 99",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "5; 7; 9",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2884,
        "question": "Find three consecutive odd numbers such that eight times the first plus the third is seven times the second",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Equals (Times 7 _smt1) (Plus (Times 8 _smt0) _smt2)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "15; 16",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2885,
        "question": "Find two consecutive integers such that the sum of the three fifths of the first and one-fourth of the second is 13.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-14; -13; -12",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2886,
        "question": "Find three consecutive integers whose sum is negative thirty-nine",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-12; -11; -10",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2887,
        "question": "find three consecutive integers whose sum is -33",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "8; 10 or -10; -8",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2888,
        "question": "the sum of the squares of two consecutive even integers is 84 more than the product of the two integers. Find the two integers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-59",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2889,
        "question": "The sum of two integers is -50. The greater integer is 9. What is the lesser integer?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus _smt0 9) (Minus 0 50)) (Equals ?_x1 _smt0) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger 9) (Le _smt0 9))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "5; 7",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2890,
        "question": "The product of two consecutive odd integers is equal to 30 more than the first. Find the integers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Equals (Times _smt0 _smt1) (Plus 30 _smt0)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "11; 13 or -13; -11 | 11; 13 | -13; -11",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2891,
        "question": "The difference in the square of 2 consecutive odd integers is 48. What are the integers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "7; 9; 11",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2892,
        "question": "find three consecutive odd integers such that 3 times the sum of all three is 18 more than the product of the first and second integers",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "5; 7; 9",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2893,
        "question": "Find three consecutive odd positive integers such that two times the sum of all three is seven more than the product of the first and second integers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{14; 6} or {-12; -7}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2894,
        "question": "Find two integers whose product is 84 such that one of the integers is 2 more than twice the other integer.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "26",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2895,
        "question": "i'm the middle number of three consecutive numbers. the product of the three consecutive numbers is 17550. who am i?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "10; 11; 12",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2896,
        "question": "Find three consecutive integers such that the sum of the smallest and twice the second is 20 more than the third.",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Equals (Plus 20 _smt2) (Plus (Min (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Times 2 _smt1))) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "8",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2897,
        "question": "sum of 3 consecutive even numbers is 24 . what is the middle number?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) 24) (Equals ?_x1 _smt1) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "14",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2898,
        "question": "Find the largest of three consecutive even integers when six times the first integer is equal to five times the middle integer.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 (Max (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals (Times 5 _smt1) (Times 6 _smt0)))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "6; 8; 10",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2899,
        "question": "find three consecutive even integer such that three times the first equals the sum of the other two.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "18; 20; 22; 24",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2900,
        "question": "find four consecutive even integers such that four times the greatest is 36 more than the sum of the other three",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "56",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2901,
        "question": "The sum of 4 consecutive odd integers exceeds twice the largest by 22. find the sum of the 4 numbers",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3)) (Plus (Times 2 _smt3) 22)) (Equals ?_x1 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3))) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (IsInteger _smt3) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Le _smt2 _smt3))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "39168",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2902,
        "question": "find the product of three consecutive even integers whose sum is 102",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 (Product (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Equals 102 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-12; -11; -10",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2903,
        "question": "Find three consecutive integers such that the sum of the second and the third is half the first decreased by 15.",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Equals (Minus (Times 0.5 _smt0) 15) (Plus _smt1 _smt2)) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "15; 16; 17; 18",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2905,
        "question": "The sum of the three smallest of four consecutive integers is 30 more than the largest integer.  What are the four consecutive integers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "10; 11; 12; 13",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2906,
        "question": "Find 4 consecutive integers such that twice the sum of the first and third is 11 greater than 3 times the second.",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (IsInteger _smt3) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3)) (Equals (Plus 11 (Times 3 _smt1)) (Times 2 (Plus _smt0 _smt2))) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_2 _smt2) (Equals ?_x1_3 _smt3))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "5467",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2907,
        "question": "The sum of four consecutive odd integers is 296. What is the product of the smallest and largest of the four odd integers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3)) 296) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (IsInteger _smt3) (IsInteger (Plus 1 _smt0)) (IsInteger 2) (Equals (Mod (Plus 1 _smt0) 2) 0) (IsInteger (Plus 1 _smt1)) (Equals (Mod (Plus 1 _smt1) 2) 0) (IsInteger (Plus 1 _smt2)) (Equals (Mod (Plus 1 _smt2) 2) 0) (IsInteger (Plus 1 _smt3)) (Equals (Mod (Plus 1 _smt3) 2) 0) (Equals ?_x4 (Times _smt0 (Max (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3)))) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Le _smt2 _smt3))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "93",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2908,
        "question": "The sum of four consecutive odd integers is 360. find the largest of the four odd integers",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3)) 360) (Equals ?_x1 (Max (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3))) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (IsInteger _smt3) (IsInteger (Plus 1 _smt0)) (IsInteger 2) (Equals (Mod (Plus 1 _smt0) 2) 0) (IsInteger (Plus 1 _smt1)) (Equals (Mod (Plus 1 _smt1) 2) 0) (IsInteger (Plus 1 _smt2)) (Equals (Mod (Plus 1 _smt2) 2) 0) (IsInteger (Plus 1 _smt3)) (Equals (Mod (Plus 1 _smt3) 2) 0) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Le _smt2 _smt3))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "83",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2909,
        "question": "The sum of 4 consecutive odd numbers is 336.What is the second number in this sequence?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3)) 336) (Equals ?_x1 _smt1) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3)))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-5760",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2910,
        "question": "The sum of three consecutive even integers is fourteen less than twice the smallest of these integers. Calculate the product of the integers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Minus (Times 2 (Min (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) 14)) (Equals ?_x2 (Product (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "2;3",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2911,
        "question": "Find two consecutive integers such that three times the first equals twice the second.",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals (Times 2 _smt1) (Times 3 _smt0)) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "6; 8",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2912,
        "question": "find two consecutive even integers such that four times the first equals three times the second",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Equals (Times 3 _smt1) (Times 4 _smt0)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "5; 7",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2913,
        "question": "Three more than twice an odd integer is equal to the next odd integer plus 6. Find the integers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "9; 11; 13; 15",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2914,
        "question": "What are the integers as the sum of four consecutive odd integers being three more than five times the least of the integers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-17; -15; -13",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2915,
        "question": "Find three consecutive odd integers such that the sum of the first and the third is 13 less than the first",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals (Minus _smt0 13) (Plus _smt0 _smt2)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-15; -14; -13; -12",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2916,
        "question": "Find four consecutive negative integers whose sum is -54",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Minus 0 54) (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3))) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (IsInteger _smt3) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3)) (LessThan _smt0 0) (LessThan _smt1 0) (LessThan _smt2 0) (LessThan _smt3 0) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Le _smt2 _smt3) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_3 _smt3))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "8; 10; 12 or -12; -10; -8",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2917,
        "question": "can you  find three consecutive even integers such that the product of the first and third is 96?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "7",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2918,
        "question": "In three consecutive positive integers, the product of the first and third, minus the second, is 1 more than 6 times the third. The smallest integer is?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "15",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2919,
        "question": "the sum of twice and thrice of a number is 75. find the number.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "9",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2920,
        "question": "If six times an integer is added to four times the same integer, the results is 90. What is the integer?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "10; 12; 14",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2921,
        "question": "Find three consecutive positive even integers such that the sum of the squares of the first and second integers is equal to the square of the third integer plus 48.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "55; 56; 57",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2922,
        "question": "Find 3 consecutive integers in which the sum of 1st and 3rd is 84 more than one half of the 2nd",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "80; 81",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2923,
        "question": "If one-half of a number is added to one-third of the next consecutive number, the sum is 67. What are the two numbers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "23; 24; 25 | -25; -24; -23 | 23; 24; 25 or -25; -24; -23",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2924,
        "question": "find three consecutive integers such that the difference of the squares of the least and the greatest is 96",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Equals 96 (Difference (Elements (Pow _smt0 2) (Pow _smt2 2)))) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "6",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2925,
        "question": "Find the larger of two consecutive integers whose sum is 4 less than three times the smaller integer.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 (Max (Elements _smt0 _smt1))) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Equals (Plus _smt0 _smt1) (Minus (Times 3 _smt0) 4)) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-6; -4 or 6; 8",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2926,
        "question": "the sum of two consecutive even integers is 34 less than their product. find the integers",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus _smt0 _smt1) (Minus (Times _smt0 _smt1) 34)) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "10; 11; 12 or -2; -1; 0",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2927,
        "question": "three consecutive integers where the square of the smaller number is 4 more than 8 time the largest. what are the three integers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "4;5;6",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2928,
        "question": "find three consecutive positive integers, such that the square of the smallest exceeds the largest by 10",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Pow _smt0 2) (Plus _smt2 10)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (LessThan 0 _smt0) (LessThan 0 _smt1) (LessThan 0 _smt2) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "670",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2929,
        "question": "sum of four consecutive integers is 686, then what is the sum of four previous consecutive integers ?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "5;7;9",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2930,
        "question": "Find three consecutive odd integers such that the sum of all three is 42 less than the product of the larger two.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-1/3 | -0.333",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2931,
        "question": "one-fifth of the sum of a number and -3 is twice the number. What is the value of the number?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Times 1 (Plus _smt0 (Minus 0 3))) (Times 5 (Times 2 _smt0))) (Equals ?_x2 _smt0))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-10;-9;-8",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2932,
        "question": "The sum of three consecutive integers is 7 less than twice the first. What are the integers?",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Equals (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Minus (Times 2 _smt0) 7)) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "44;46;48",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2933,
        "question": "find three consecutive even integers such that the sum of twice the smallest and three times the largest is 232",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals 232 (Plus (Times 2 _smt0) (Times 3 _smt2))) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{6; 24; 20}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2934,
        "question": "Three integers have a sum of 50. the second integer is four times as large as the first integer and the third integer is 4 less than the second integer. what are the three integers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "144",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2935,
        "question": "when a number is divided by 4 and has 12 subtracted from it, the result is 1/6 of the number. what is the number ?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "120",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2936,
        "question": "Find the number such that its third is  greater than its fifth by 16.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "30;32;34",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2937,
        "question": "Find three consecutive even integers such that the sum of the least integer and the middle integer is 28 more than the greatest integer?",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (IsInteger (Min (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Equals (Plus 28 (Max (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Plus (Min (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) _smt1)) (IsInteger (Max (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-8",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2938,
        "question": "One-fifth the sum of three consecutive even integers is -6. Find the largest integer.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Times 1 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Times 5 (Minus 0 6))) (Equals ?_x1 _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "51;53;55;57",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2939,
        "question": "Find 4 consecutive odd integers whose sum is 216",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 216 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3))) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (IsInteger _smt3) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Le _smt2 _smt3) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_3 _smt3))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "81; 83; 85; 87",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2940,
        "question": "Find 4 consecutive odd integers whose sum equals 336",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 336 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3))) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (IsInteger _smt3) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Le _smt2 _smt3) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_3 _smt3))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-195;-193;-191",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2941,
        "question": "Find three consecutive odd integers whose sum is -579",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Minus 0 579) (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "3;5;7",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2942,
        "question": "There are 3 consecutive odd integers. Three times the largest is seven times the smallest. What are the integers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals (Elements _smt3 _smt4 _smt5) (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Consecutive (Elements _smt3 _smt4 _smt5)) (IsInteger _x1) (Equals (Times 7 _smt3) (Times 3 _smt5)) (Le _smt3 _smt4) (Le _smt4 _smt5) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt3) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt4) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt5))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "3;5;7",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2943,
        "question": "There are three consecutive odd integers. Three times the largest is seven times the smallest. What are the integers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals (Elements _smt3 _smt4 _smt5) (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Consecutive (Elements _smt3 _smt4 _smt5)) (IsInteger _x1) (Equals (Times 7 _smt3) (Times 3 _smt5)) (Le _smt3 _smt4) (Le _smt4 _smt5) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt3) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt4) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt5))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "9; 11 | -15; -13",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2944,
        "question": "Difference of an odd integer and three times the next consecutive odd integer is 24. Find the integers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "36",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2945,
        "question": "What two-digit number is equal to twice the product of its digits?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "36",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2946,
        "question": "what 2 digit number is equal to twice the product of its digits?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "26",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2947,
        "question": "In an even 2-digit number, the second digit is 3 times the first. what is the number?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "19",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2948,
        "question": "The difference between six times a number and 9 is equal to five times the sum of the number and 2. find the number",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 _smt0) (Equals (Difference (Elements (Times 6 _smt0) 9)) (Times 5 (Plus _smt0 2))))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-23",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2949,
        "question": "if the sum of a number and seven is tripled, the result is two less than twice the number. find the number?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Times (Plus _smt0 7) 3) (Minus (Times 2 _smt0) 2)) (Equals ?_x1 _smt0))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "23",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2950,
        "question": "Robert thinks of a number. When he multiples his number by 5 and subtracts 16 from the result, he gets the same answer as to when he adds 10 to his number and multiples the result by 3. Find the number Robert is thinking of.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "20",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2951,
        "question": "the sum of two times a number and eight is equal to three times the difference between the number and four. What's the number?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 _smt0) (Equals (Plus (Times 2 _smt0) 8) (Times 3 (Difference (Elements _smt0 4)))))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "37",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2952,
        "question": "twice the sum of a number and sixteen is five less than three times the number?find the number?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 _smt0) (Equals (Minus (Times 3 _smt0) 5) (Times 2 (Plus _smt0 16))))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "4; 6",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2953,
        "question": "The product of two consecutive even integers is 4 more than 5 times the smaller of the two integers. Find the integers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-24;-22;-20;-18",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2954,
        "question": "Find 4 consecutive even integers such that four less than twice the smallest is equal to three times the largest, increased by two.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (IsInteger _smt3) (Equals (Plus (Times 3 _smt3) 2) (Minus (Times 2 _smt0) 4)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Le _smt2 _smt3) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_3 _smt3))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "9",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2956,
        "question": "An integer minus 3 times its reciprocal equals 26/3. What is the integer?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 _smt0) (IsInteger _smt0) (Equals 26 (Times 3 (Minus _smt0 (Div (Times 3 1) _smt0)))))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "96",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2958,
        "question": "The tens digit of a certain two-digit number is 3 more than the units digit. The sum of the squares of the two digits is 117. Find the number.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "7;9",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2959,
        "question": "Nine times the first of two consecutive odd integers equals seven times the second.  Find the integers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Equals (Times 7 _smt1) (Times 9 _smt0)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "16; 23",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2960,
        "question": "The sum of Two numbers is 39. Twice the first number and plus 3 times the second number is 101. What are the numbers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{7; 14}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2961,
        "question": "The sum of two numbers is 21. Two times the smaller number plus five times the larger number is 84. What are the two numbers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "16/3; 37/3 | 5.333; 12.333",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2962,
        "question": "a number is 7 less than another. if 4 times the smaller number plus twice the larger is 46, find the two numbers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{44; -11}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2963,
        "question": "The difference between two numbers is 55. Four times the smaller number plus five times the larger number is 176. What are the numbers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 55 (Minus _smt1 _smt0)) (Equals 176 (Plus (Times 4 _smt0) (Times 5 _smt1))) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{227/5; 152/5} | {45.4; 30.4}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2964,
        "question": "One number is 15 more than the other. The sum of twice the larger and 3 times the smaller is 182. Find the numbers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals _smt0 (Plus 15 _smt1)) (Equals 182 (Plus (Times 2 (Max (Elements _smt0 _smt1))) (Times 3 (Min (Elements _smt0 _smt1))))) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "49/9; 94/9 | 5.444; 10.444",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2965,
        "question": "The first number is 5 less than the second number. Four times the first number plus five times the second number is 74. Find the numbers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals _smt0 (Minus _smt1 5)) (Equals 74 (Plus (Times 4 _smt0) (Times 5 _smt1))) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{20; 8}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2966,
        "question": "One number is 12 more than another number. The sum of twice the larger number and three times the smaller number is 64. Find the numbers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals _smt0 (Plus 12 _smt1)) (Equals 64 (Plus (Times 2 (Max (Elements _smt0 _smt1))) (Times 3 (Min (Elements _smt0 _smt1))))) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "192837",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2967,
        "question": "find a six-digit number in which the first is two less that the fifth, the second digit is one more that the fourth, and the fifth digit is four less than the last. The sum of the third and last digits equals the second and the sum of all the digits is 30.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "a = 5.5; b = 5.1; c = 3 | a = 11/2; b = 51/10; c = 3 | 11/2; 51/10; 3 | 5.5; 5.1; 3",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2968,
        "question": "a+b=10.6a+c=8.5b+c=8.1how much are a, b, c worth?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "255",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2969,
        "question": "The sum of two consecutive odd numbers is 32.  What is the product of the two numbers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus _smt0 _smt1) 32) (Equals ?_x1 (Times _smt0 _smt1)) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{-12;-6}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2970,
        "question": "One number is 6 less than a second number. Twice the second number is 48 more than 5 times the first. Find the two numbers",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{8;11;15}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2972,
        "question": "The sum of 3 numbers is 34. The first number is 3 less than the second and the third is 4 more than the second.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "5; 7; 9 or -9; -7; -5",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2973,
        "question": "The sum of squares of three consecutive odd numbers is 155. What are the numbers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Sum (Elements (Pow _smt0 2) (Pow _smt1 2) (Pow _smt2 2))) 155) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "8; 2",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2974,
        "question": "one number is six more than another number. The sum of the larger number and twice the smaller number is 12. Find the numbers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals _smt0 (Plus 6 _smt1)) (Equals 12 (Plus (Max (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Times 2 (Min (Elements _smt0 _smt1))))) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "18; 10",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2975,
        "question": "One number is 8 more than another number.  If the sum of the smaller number and twice the larger number is 46, find the two numbers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "18; 10",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2976,
        "question": "one number is 8 more than another. if the sum of the smaller number and twice the larger number is 46, find the two numbers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "15;17;19",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2977,
        "question": "find three consecutive odd integers such that the largest decreased by three times the second is 47 less than the smallest",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals (Minus (Min (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) 47) (Minus (Max (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Times 3 _smt1))) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-1;1",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2978,
        "question": "Find two consecutive odd integers whose sum is 0",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 0 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "71; 73",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2979,
        "question": "The sum of two consecutive odd integers is 144. Find the integers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Equals 144 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "16;6 or -6;-16",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2980,
        "question": "the product of two numbers is 96. their difference is 10. what are the numbers",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 96 (Times _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals 10 (Minus _smt1 _smt0)) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "237; 238 or -238; -237",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2981,
        "question": "56406 is the product of 2 consecutive numbers. What are they?",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals 56406 (Times _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "38; 25 or -25; -38",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2982,
        "question": "Number A minus number B equals 13 and the two numbers multiplied together equals 950. What are the numbers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{28;32}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2983,
        "question": "one number is 12 more than half another number. the two numbers total 60. find the numbers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals _smt0 (Plus 12 (Times 0.5 _smt1))) (Equals 60 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "15",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2984,
        "question": "One number exceeds another by 5. One-fifth of their sum is five less than the smaller number. Find the number.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x1 (Plus _smt1 5)) (Equals (Times 1 (Plus (Plus _smt1 5) _smt1)) (Times 5 (Minus (Min (Elements (Plus _smt1 5) _smt1)) 5))))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "5/6 | 0.833",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2985,
        "question": "four fifths of a number added to one half the number is equal to the sum of one tenth of the number and 1. what is the number?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "22;24;26",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2986,
        "question": "Find three consecutive even integers such that the first plus twice the second plus four times the third equals 174",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals 174 (Plus (Plus _smt0 (Times 2 _smt1)) (Times 4 _smt2))) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "8;9;10 or -5;-4;-3",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2987,
        "question": "find three consecutive numbers such that twice the square of the first number is 38 more than the product of the other two numbers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "3",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2988,
        "question": "Three times the square of a certain positive number exceeds six times the number by nine.  Find the number:",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Times 3 (Pow _smt0 2)) (Plus (Times 6 _smt0) 9)) (Equals ?_x1 _smt0) (LessThan 0 _smt0))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "11",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2989,
        "question": "Find the whole number such that twice its square is 11 more than 21 times the original number ?",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger ?_x0) (Equals (Plus 11 (Times 21 ?_x0)) (Times 2 (Pow ?_x0 2))))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "3",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2990,
        "question": "three times the square of a certain positive number exceeds six times the number by nine.  Find the number.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Times 3 (Pow _smt0 2)) (Plus (Times 6 _smt0) 9)) (Equals ?_x1 _smt0) (LessThan 0 _smt0))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-14.5",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2991,
        "question": "the product of some negative number and 5 less than twice that number is 493. find the number?",
        "semantics": "(And (LessThan ?_x0 0) (Equals 493 (Times ?_x0 (Minus (Times 2 ?_x0) 5))))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "16",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2992,
        "question": "The sum of the digits of a two-digit number is 7. If the digits are reversed, the new number is increased by 3 equals 4 times the original number. what is the number?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{4; 7}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2995,
        "question": "find two numbers such that five times the larger plus three times the smaller is 47 and four times the larger minus twice the smaller is 20.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 47 (Plus (Times 5 _smt1) (Times 3 _smt0))) (Equals 20 (Minus (Times 4 _smt1) (Times 2 _smt0))) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{479; 139}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2996,
        "question": "Twice the sum of two numbers is 1236. Twice the difference of those same two numbers is 680. What are those two numbers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "199",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2997,
        "question": "The sum of three consecutive numbers is 600. What is the least of these three numbers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) 600) (Equals ?_x1 (Min (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "26",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 2999,
        "question": "The sum of two digits is 8. If the digits of the number are reversed, the number formed is 36 more than the number. What is the number?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "38",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3000,
        "question": "The sum of the digits of a 2-digit number is 11. If the digits are reversed, the number formed is 45 more than the original number. Find the original number.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "ans_no_result",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3001,
        "question": "the sum of the digits of a two digit number is 7. If the digits are reversed the number is increased by 37. What is the original number?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "35",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3002,
        "question": "The sum of the digits of a two-digit number is 8. If the digits are reversed. the new number is 18 more than the original number. Find the original number.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "39",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3003,
        "question": "The sum of the digits of a two-digit number is 12. The number formed by interchanging the digits is 54 more than the original number. What is the original number?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "8",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3004,
        "question": "the ratio of the number of coins mark has to the number of coins john has is 2:5. if john has 20 coins, how many coins does mark have?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "400",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3005,
        "question": "if 240:3=x:5 what's the value of x?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "28",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3006,
        "question": "Given that 7 : 2 = x : 8,find the value of x",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-7",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3010,
        "question": "twice the sum of a number and 3 is the same as 1 subtracted from the number. Find the number",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 _smt0) (Equals (Times 2 (Plus _smt0 3)) (Minus _smt0 1)))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "25",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3011,
        "question": "if n=7,what is the value of 3n+4",
        "semantics": "(Equals ?_x0 (Plus (Times 3 7) 4))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "49;51",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3013,
        "question": "Find two consecutive odd numbers such that the sum of three-sevenths of the first number and one-third of the second number is equal to thirty-eight.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals (Plus (Div (Times 3 _smt0) 7) (Div (Times 1 _smt1) 3)) (Plus 30 8)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "55;57",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3014,
        "question": "find the two consecutive odd integers such that twice the smaller decreased by the larger equals 53",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Equals 53 (Minus (Times 2 _smt0) _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "13; 15",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3015,
        "question": "find two consecutive odd integers such that twice the lager is 17 more than the smaller",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "7;8;9",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3016,
        "question": "If the smallest of the three consecutive integer is added to twice the largest, the result is seven less than four times the middle. Find the numbers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "48",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3017,
        "question": "find the largest two-digit number which is equal to four times the sum of its digits",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "1632960",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3018,
        "question": "How many 8-digits whole numbers can be written with eight different digits, assuming that the leading digit cannot be zero?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "90000000 | 9E7",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3019,
        "question": "How many eight-digit telephone numbers are possible if the first digit must be nonzero?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-16",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3021,
        "question": "Eight times the sum of a number and -2 is the same as nine times the number.  Find the number.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 _smt0) (Equals (Times 8 (Plus _smt0 (Minus 0 2))) (Times 9 _smt0)))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "ans_no_result",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3022,
        "question": "Find three consecutive odd integers whose sum is three times the third integer",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-7; -5; -3",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3023,
        "question": "the sum of three consecutive odd integers is the same as five times the greatest of these integers. what are the integers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals (Times 5 (Max (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-2",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3024,
        "question": "Evaluate 3x + 7 when x = -3.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "10;4",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3025,
        "question": "The sum of two numbers is 6 less than twice the first number.  Their difference is 10 less than four times the second number.  Find each of the numbers",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "25; 10",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3026,
        "question": "the sum of 2 numbers is 15 less than twice the first number. their difference is 5 less than twice the second number. find each of the numbers",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-90",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3027,
        "question": "eight less than half a number is seven more than two thirds of the number.  find the number",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 _smt0) (Equals (Plus 7 (Div (Times 2 _smt0) 3)) (Minus (Times 0.5 _smt0) 8)))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "39",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3028,
        "question": "the sum of the digits of a two digit number is 12. if the digits are reversed, the number is 15 more than twice the original number. What is the original number?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{3; 8}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3029,
        "question": "The larger of two numbers is 2 more than twice the smaller. Ten times the smaller number is 2 less than 4 times the larger number.  Find the 2 numbers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "38",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3030,
        "question": "One fifth of 12 more than a certain number equals one-fourth of 2 more than the number. Find the number",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals _smt0 ?_x0) (Equals (Times 5 (Times 1 (Plus 2 ?_x0))) (Times 4 (Times 1 (Plus 12 _smt0)))))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "8;10;12",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3031,
        "question": "Find three consecutive even integers such that the sum of the first and third exceeds one-half the second by 15.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus _smt0 _smt2) (Plus (Times 0.5 _smt1) 15)) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "7;4;6;5;8",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3032,
        "question": "A man wanted to get into his work building, but he had forgotten his code. However, he did remember five clues. These are what those clues were:The fifth number plus the third number equals fourteen.The fourth number is one more than the second number.The first number is one less than twice the second number.The second number plus the third number equals ten.The sum of all five numbers is 30.What were the five numbers and in what order?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "62",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3033,
        "question": "The sum of the digits of a two-digit number is 8. If 16 is added to the original number, the result is 3 times the original number with its digits reversed. Find the original number.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-4;-2;0",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3034,
        "question": "find three consecutive even integers such that four times the second is eight less than the third.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals (Minus _smt2 8) (Times 4 _smt1)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "15",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3035,
        "question": "20% of the number is 3. Find the number?",
        "semantics": "(Equals (Times 20 ?_x0) (Times 100 3))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "4",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3036,
        "question": "5 times a number equals 20what is the number?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "60",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3037,
        "question": "15 is 25% of what number?",
        "semantics": "(Equals (Times 25 ?_x0) (Times 100 15))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "60",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3038,
        "question": "36 is 60% of what number?",
        "semantics": "(Equals (Times 60 ?_x0) (Times 100 36))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-21",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3039,
        "question": "Twice the difference of a number and 3 is equal to three times the sum of the number and 5. What is the number?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-11",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3040,
        "question": "Four times the difference of a number and one is equal to six times the sum of the number and three.  Find the number.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{4;1/2} | {4; 0.5}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3041,
        "question": "the product of two numbers is 2. The sum of one number and the reciprocal of the other is 6. Find the number?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "10",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3042,
        "question": "Three times an even integer is two less than 4 times the next lower even integer. Find the integer ?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "80; 10",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3043,
        "question": "The quotient of two numbers is 8 and their sum is 90. Find the numbers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "5",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3044,
        "question": "If 6 is added to a number, the result exceeds two times the number by 1. What is the number",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus (Times 2 _smt0) 1) (Plus 6 _smt0)) (Equals ?_x1 _smt0))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-4",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3045,
        "question": "16 more than a number is 20 more than twice the number.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "23/2 | 11.5",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3046,
        "question": "when 4 is added to 5 times a number,the number increases by 50. Find the number.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-16;-14;-12",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3047,
        "question": "Find 3 consecutive odd integers such that the smallest is 10 more than the sum of the other two integers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "124800",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3049,
        "question": "The sum of three consecutive even numbers is 150. What is the product of the numbers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) 150) (Equals ?_x1 (Product (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "4224",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3050,
        "question": "The sum of two consecutive even number is 130. Find the product of the two numbers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{18; 6} | {18; 6} or {-18/5; -6/5} | {18; 6} or {-3.6; -1.2}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3051,
        "question": "The sum of two numbers is twice their difference. The larger number is 6 more than twice the smaller. Find the numbers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus _smt0 _smt1) (Times 2 (Minus _smt1 _smt0))) (Equals _smt1 (Plus 6 (Times 2 _smt0))) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "5",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3052,
        "question": "The sum of a number and 25 times its reciprocal is 10. Find the number.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 _smt0) (Equals 10 (Plus _smt0 (Div (Times 25 1) _smt0))))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "2 or 5",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3053,
        "question": "the sum of a number and ten times its reciprocal equals seven? What is this number?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 _smt0) (Equals 7 (Plus _smt0 (Div (Times 10 1) _smt0))))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "2 or 1",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3056,
        "question": "The sum of a number and twice its reciprocal is 3. What is the number?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 _smt0) (Equals 3 (Plus _smt0 (Div (Times 2 1) _smt0))))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "428571",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3057,
        "question": "Given a six digit number whose last digit is 1. If you place 1 as the first digit the resulting number is 1/3 that of the original one. Determine the original number.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "3; 4; 5 or -1; 0; 1 or -5; -4; -3",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3058,
        "question": "What three consecutive numbers have a sum which is 1/5 of their product",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "525; 875",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3059,
        "question": "A sum of $1400 is to be divided between two people in the ratio 3:5. How much does each person receive?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "1 + 2(n - 1)n | 2n ^ 2 - 2n + 1 | n ^ 2 + (n - 1) ^ 2",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3060,
        "question": "Find the nth number in the sequence  1, 5, 13, 25, 41",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "35",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3061,
        "question": "The sum of the digits of a two-digit numeral is 8. If the digits are reversed, the new number is 18 greater than the original number. Find the original number.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "50; 10",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3062,
        "question": "There were 5 times as many boys as girls at the party. Also, the number of boys was 100 less than 15 times the number of girls. How many boys and girls came to the party?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "72",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3063,
        "question": "A two digit counting number has a value of 8 times the sum of its digits. If 6 times the units digit is 5 more than the tens digit, what is the number?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Times 6 (Mod (Div (Times 8 (Sum (Elements _smt0_d5 _smt0_d4 _smt0_d3 _smt0_d2 _smt0_d1 _smt0_d0))) 1) 10)) (Plus 5 (Mod (Div (Times 8 (Sum (Elements _smt0_d5 _smt0_d4 _smt0_d3 _smt0_d2 _smt0_d1 _smt0_d0))) 10) 10))) (Equals ?_x1 (Times 8 (Sum (Elements _smt0_d5 _smt0_d4 _smt0_d3 _smt0_d2 _smt0_d1 _smt0_d0)))) (Le (Times 8 (Sum (Elements _smt0_d5 _smt0_d4 _smt0_d3 _smt0_d2 _smt0_d1 _smt0_d0))) (Minus (Pow 10 2) 1)) (Le (Pow 10 (Minus 2 1)) (Times 8 (Sum (Elements _smt0_d5 _smt0_d4 _smt0_d3 _smt0_d2 _smt0_d1 _smt0_d0)))) (LessThan 0 (Times 8 (Sum (Elements _smt0_d5 _smt0_d4 _smt0_d3 _smt0_d2 _smt0_d1 _smt0_d0)))) (IsInteger (Times 8 (Sum (Elements _smt0_d5 _smt0_d4 _smt0_d3 _smt0_d2 _smt0_d1 _smt0_d0)))) (Equals (Sum (Elements (Times _smt0_d0 1) (Times _smt0_d1 10) (Times _smt0_d2 100) (Times _smt0_d3 1000) (Times _smt0_d4 10000) (Times _smt0_d5 100000))) (Times 8 (Sum (Elements _smt0_d5 _smt0_d4 _smt0_d3 _smt0_d2 _smt0_d1 _smt0_d0)))) (Le 0 _smt0_d5) (Le _smt0_d5 9) (IsInteger _smt0_d5) (Le 0 _smt0_d4) (Le _smt0_d4 9) (IsInteger _smt0_d4) (Le 0 _smt0_d3) (Le _smt0_d3 9) (IsInteger _smt0_d3) (Le 0 _smt0_d2) (Le _smt0_d2 9) (IsInteger _smt0_d2) (Le 0 _smt0_d1) (Le _smt0_d1 9) (IsInteger _smt0_d1) (Le 0 _smt0_d0) (Le _smt0_d0 9) (IsInteger _smt0_d0))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "61",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3064,
        "question": "The sum of the digits of a two-digit number is 7. The original two-digit number is 3 less than 4 times the number with its digits reversed. Find the original two-digit number.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "5;6;7",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3065,
        "question": "Find three consecutive positive integers such that the product of the first and third, minus the second, is 1 more than 4 times the third.",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (LessThan 0 _smt0) (LessThan 0 _smt1) (LessThan 0 _smt2) (Equals (Plus 1 (Times 4 _smt2)) (Minus (Times _smt0 _smt2) _smt1)) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-9;-7;-5;-3;-1",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3066,
        "question": "find five consecutive odd integers such that the sum of the first and fifth number is one less than three times the fourth number",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3 _smt4)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (IsInteger _smt3) (IsInteger _smt4) (Equals (Minus (Times 3 _smt3) 1) (Plus _smt0 _smt4)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_3 _smt3) (Equals ?_x0_4 _smt4))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "12 or -1",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3068,
        "question": "The sum of the number and its square is twelve times the next higher number. Find the no.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "36",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3069,
        "question": "what two-digit number is twice the product of its digits?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "8;9 or -9;-8",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3070,
        "question": "What two consecutive integers have cubes that differ by 217?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "15;17;19",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3071,
        "question": "Find three consecutive odd integers of which one half of the sum of the first and second equals the square of the difference of the third and the first.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "52; 13 or -52; -13",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3072,
        "question": "Which two numbers have a product of 676 and a quotient of 4",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{16; 2} or {-16; -2}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3073,
        "question": "the product of two numbers is 32 and their quotient is 8. find the numbers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "4",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3074,
        "question": "When fifteen is subtracted from four times the sum of seven and twice some number, the result is 45",
        "semantics": "(Equals 45 (Minus (Times 4 (Plus 7 (Times 2 _x0))) 15))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "13;14;15",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3075,
        "question": "find 3 consecutive integers such that the square of the third exceeds the sum of the second and the square of the first by 42",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "10;11;12;13",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3076,
        "question": "Find four consecutive integers such that twice the first subtracted from the sum of the other three integers is sixteen.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "10; 11; 12; 13",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3077,
        "question": "Find four consecutive integers such that twice the first subtracted from  the sum of the other three is 16.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "11;13 or -1;1",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3078,
        "question": "Find 2 consecutive odd integers whose product is one less than 6 times their sum.",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Equals (Times _smt0 _smt1) (Minus (Times 6 (Plus _smt0 _smt1)) 1)) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "22;24;26;28",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3079,
        "question": "Find four consecutive even integers such that the sum of twice the fourth integer and half the second integer is 68.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (IsInteger _smt3) (Equals 68 (Plus (Times 2 _smt3) (Times 0.5 _smt1))) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_3 _smt3))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "12",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3080,
        "question": "find a number which is 24 greater than its opposite",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "48",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3081,
        "question": "Find a number that is 96 greater than its opposite.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "5;6;7",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3082,
        "question": "Find three consecutive integers such that 4 times the largest exceeds three times the second by 10.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Times 4 (Max (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Plus (Times 3 _smt1) 10)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "19;20;21",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3083,
        "question": "Find three consecutive integers such that the sum of the first and twice the second is 17 more than twice the third",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Equals (Plus 17 (Times 2 _smt2)) (Plus _smt0 (Times 2 _smt1))) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{-3/13; -9/13} | {-0.231; -0.692}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3084,
        "question": "Twice the larger number is 3 more than five times the smaller number.  The sum of the 2 numbers is 4 times the larger number.  What are the two numbers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "28",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3085,
        "question": "When 28 is added to 3 times a number y and the sum is divided by 2, the result is 2 times the number y. What is the value of y?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus 28 (Times 3 _smt0)) (Times 2 (Times 2 _smt0))) (Equals ?_x2 _smt0))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "27",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3086,
        "question": "The product of the two-digit number and its tens digit is 54. Find the number if the sum of the digits when added to the number gives a result of 36?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "1 or 2",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3087,
        "question": "The sum of a number and twice its reciprocal is 3. Find the numbers",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus _smt0 (Div (Times 2 1) _smt0)) 3) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "25; 27",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3088,
        "question": "Find two consecutive odd integers such that the sum of the smaller and twice the larger is 79",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Equals 79 (Plus _smt0 (Times 2 _smt1))) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-276",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3089,
        "question": "One third of a number is -92. Find the number",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "2;4",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3090,
        "question": "The sum of two consecutive even integers is ten less than twice their product. Find their integers using factoring.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{6;10;14}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3091,
        "question": "Find  three positive integers whose sum is 30 and whose product is 840?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 30 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Equals 840 (Product (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (LessThan 0 _smt0) (LessThan 0 _smt1) (LessThan 0 _smt2) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-6;-4",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3092,
        "question": "The smaller of two consecutive even integers is 2 more than twice the larger. Find the numbers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "6",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3093,
        "question": "a number, twice that number, and one-third of that number are added. The result is 20. What is the original number?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-4;-2;0;2",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3094,
        "question": "Find four consecutive even integers such that four times the fourth decreased by one half the second is 9.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (IsInteger _smt3) (Equals 9 (Minus (Times 4 _smt3) (Times 0.5 _smt1))) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_3 _smt3))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "780",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3095,
        "question": "a three-digit number, which is divisible by 10, has a hundreds digit that is one less than its tens digit. the number also is 52 times the sum of its digits. find the number",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "25",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3096,
        "question": "if the sum of the consecutive integers from -22 through x is 72, what is the value of x",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "3",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3097,
        "question": "11 less than 4 times some number is the same as the quotient of the number and 3. Find the number",
        "semantics": "(Equals ?_x0 (Times 3 (Minus (Times 4 ?_x0) 11)))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{82;28}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3098,
        "question": "I have two secret numbers. Each has two digits. The secret numbers have the same digits, only reversed. The difference between the two numbers is 54, and the sum of the digits in each number is 10. what are my two secret numbers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "39; 93",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3099,
        "question": "The sum of the digits of a two digit number is 12. The number formed by interchanging the digits is 54 more than the original number. Find the original number and its reversal.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "4;5",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3100,
        "question": "the sum of two consecutive numbers is 9. If two times the 1st number less than 3 times the 2nd number is 7, what are the two numbers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "1",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3101,
        "question": "twice the result of subtracting an unknown number from five is eight. find the number",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "20",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3102,
        "question": "The difference between two numbers is 10. If the numbers are doubled, what is the difference between them?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "2 or -13/3 | 2 or -4.333",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3103,
        "question": "Three times the square of the number when added to seven times the number result in 26. What is the number ?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "20 or -120",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3104,
        "question": "When the number x is increased by x%, it becomes 24. Find x.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "3/2 or -4 | 1.5 or -4",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3105,
        "question": "If a number is multiplied by 5 more than twice that number, the result is 12. Find the number?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 12 (Times _smt0 (Plus 5 (Times 2 _smt0)))) (Equals ?_x1 _smt0))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "1",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3106,
        "question": "Find the natural number which when added to its square gives a times the next natural number ?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "22; 5",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3107,
        "question": "One number is 17 more than another.  If the greater number is increased by 3, the result is 5 times the smaller.  What are the numbers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals _smt0 (Plus 17 _smt1)) (Equals (Plus 3 (Max (Elements _smt0 _smt1))) (Times 5 (Min (Elements _smt0 _smt1)))) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{81; 14}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3108,
        "question": "The difference of two numbers is 67. The larger number is three less than six times the smaller number. Find the numbers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 67 (Minus _smt1 _smt0)) (Equals _smt1 (Minus (Times 6 _smt0) 3)) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{23; 7}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3109,
        "question": "The difference of two numbers is 16. the greater number is 5 less than 4 times the smaller number. find the #s?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-2; -1",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3111,
        "question": "find two consecutive integers such that the square of the sum of the two integers is 11 more than the smaller integer.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "4 or 2",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3113,
        "question": "Eight more than the square of a number is six times the number?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "51",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3114,
        "question": "the sum of the digits of a two-digit number is 6. if the digits are reversed, the new number is three times the original tens digit. find the original number",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "72",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3115,
        "question": "the sum of the digits of a two-digit number is 9. if 45 is subtracted from the number, the digits of the number are reversed. find the number.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "94",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3116,
        "question": "the tens digit of a two-digit number exceeds twice the units digit by 1. if the digits are reversed, the sum of the new number and the original number is 143. find the original number.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "35",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3117,
        "question": "A two digit number is 7 times its unit digit. If 18 is added to the number, its digits are reversed. Find the number.",
        "semantics": "(And (Le ?_x0 (Minus (Pow 10 2) 1)) (Le (Pow 10 (Minus 2 1)) ?_x0) (Equals _smt0 ?_x0) (Equals _smt0 (Times 7 (Mod (Div ?_x0 1) 10))))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "4",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3119,
        "question": "Five times the first of three consecutive even integers is four less than three times the third integer. Find the smallest even integer",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Times 5 _smt0) (Minus (Times 3 _smt2) 4)) (Equals ?_x1 (Min _x2)) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (IsInteger _x4) (IsInteger 2) (Equals (Mod _x4 2) 0))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "52",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3120,
        "question": "the sum of the digits of a 2-digit number is 7. The tens digit is one less than 3 times the units digit. Find the number.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus _smt1_d1 _smt1_d0) 7) (Le ?_x1 (Minus (Pow 10 2) 1)) (Le (Pow 10 (Minus 2 1)) ?_x1) (Equals (Plus (Times _smt1_d0 1) (Times _smt1_d1 10)) ?_x1) (Equals (Mod (Div ?_x1 10) 10) (Minus (Times 3 (Mod (Div ?_x1 1) 10)) 1)) (Le 0 _smt1_d1) (Le _smt1_d1 9) (IsInteger _smt1_d1) (Le 0 _smt1_d0) (Le _smt1_d0 9) (IsInteger _smt1_d0))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "99",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3121,
        "question": "The tens digit of a 2-digit number is 9 less than twice the units digit. If the sum of the 2 digits is 18, what is the number ?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "6; 7; 8",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3122,
        "question": "Find three consecutive integers such that 3 times the first integer plus the second integer minus 2 times the third integer is 9.",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Equals 9 (Minus (Plus (Times 3 _smt0) _smt1) (Times 2 _smt2))) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "57",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3123,
        "question": "four times the smallest of three consecutive odd integers is five more than three times the largest. What is the sum of these consecutive odd integers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Times 4 (Min (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Plus 5 (Times 3 _smt2))) (Equals ?_x2 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-5",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3124,
        "question": "Three times the opposite of a number is 40 greater than 5 times number. What is the number?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "16",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3125,
        "question": "Find a number that is 32 more than its opposite",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "180",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3126,
        "question": "the sum of a number and three times that number is 720. what is the number",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 _smt0) (Equals 720 (Plus _smt0 (Times 3 _smt0))))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "14",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3127,
        "question": "The sum of a number and seven times the number is 112. What is the number?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 _smt0) (Equals 112 (Plus _smt0 (Times 7 _smt0))))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "38.5 | 77/2",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3128,
        "question": "If 4a+3b=27 and 3a+4b=29, then 7a+7b/2=?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus (Times 7 a) (Div (Times 7 b) 2)) ?_x0) (Equals 27 (Plus (Times 4 a) (Times 3 b))) (Equals 29 (Plus (Times 3 a) (Times 4 b))))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "100",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3129,
        "question": "How many three digit numbers start with a prime digit, have an even digit in the middle, and an odd digit at the end?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "288",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3130,
        "question": "How many 3-digit positive integers are odd and do not contain the digit \"5\"?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "60",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3131,
        "question": "how many 3 digit even numbers can be made using the digits 1,2,3,4,6,7,if no digit is repeated?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "12",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3132,
        "question": "How many 3 digit numbers can you make using the digits 1,2,3, and 4 if the hundreds digit is prime and repetition of a digit is not permitted?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "8; 10; 12",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3133,
        "question": "Find 3 consecutive even numbers where the product of the smaller two numbers is 64 less than the square of the largest number",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Equals (Minus (Pow _smt2 2) 64) (Times _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "2 or 0",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3134,
        "question": "the square of a number is the same as twice the number. find the number",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 _smt0) (Equals (Times 2 _smt0) (Pow _smt0 2)))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "39",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3135,
        "question": "A two-digit number is increased by 54 when the digits are reversed. If the sum of the digits is 12, find the number.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "28",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3136,
        "question": "When one-half of a number is added to one-fourth of the number, the sum is twenty-one. What is the number?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus (Times 0.5 _smt0) (Div (Times 1 _smt0) 4)) (Plus 20 1)) (Equals ?_x1 _smt0))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-10 or 11",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3137,
        "question": "a number is 110 less than its square. find all such numbers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals _smt0 (Minus (Pow _smt0 2) 110)) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "5; 6; 7",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3138,
        "question": "Find 3 consecutive numbers where the product of the smaller two numbers is 19 less than the square of the largest number.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Equals (Minus (Pow _smt2 2) 19) (Times _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "6",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3139,
        "question": "if the difference between the smallest and the largest of five consecutive odd numbers is t, what is t-2",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-9; -7; -5; -3; -1",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3140,
        "question": "find five consecutive odd integers such that the sum of the first and fifth is one less than three times the fourth",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3 _smt4)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (IsInteger _smt3) (IsInteger _smt4) (Equals (Minus (Times 3 _smt3) 1) (Plus _smt0 _smt4)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_3 _smt3) (Equals ?_x0_4 _smt4))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-9; -7; -5; -3; -1",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3141,
        "question": "find 5 consecutive odd integers such that the sum of the first and fifth is one less than three times the fourth",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3 _smt4)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (IsInteger _smt3) (IsInteger _smt4) (Equals (Minus (Times 3 _smt3) 1) (Plus _smt0 _smt4)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_3 _smt3) (Equals ?_x0_4 _smt4))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "ans_no_result",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3142,
        "question": "Find four consecutive even integers such that the sum of the second and fourth be 74.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "15; 17; 19; 21; 23",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3143,
        "question": "what 5 consecutive odd numbers total 95",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 95 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3 _smt4))) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3 _smt4)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Le _smt2 _smt3) (Le _smt3 _smt4) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_3 _smt3) (Equals ?_x0_4 _smt4))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "29; 31; 33",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3144,
        "question": "Find 3 consecutive odd integers such that 3 times the 2nd minus the 3rd is 31 more than the first.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals (Plus 31 _smt0) (Minus (Times 3 _smt1) _smt2)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "87",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3145,
        "question": "i am a number that is greater than 81 but less than 95. the sum of my digits is 15. what number am i?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 (Plus (Times _smt0_d0 1) (Times _smt0_d1 10))) (LessThan 81 (Plus (Times _smt0_d0 1) (Times _smt0_d1 10))) (LessThan (Plus (Times _smt0_d0 1) (Times _smt0_d1 10)) 95) (Equals 15 (Plus _smt0_d1 _smt0_d0)) (Le 0 _smt0_d1) (Le _smt0_d1 9) (IsInteger _smt0_d1) (Le 0 _smt0_d0) (Le _smt0_d0 9) (IsInteger _smt0_d0))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "2178",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3146,
        "question": "I am a four-digit positive integer such that the sum of my digits is 18 and my digits reversed are exactly four times myself.  What number am I?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "11; 13; 15",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3147,
        "question": "find three consecutive odd integers such that the sum of the first, two times the second, and three times the third is 82",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals 82 (Sum (Elements _smt0 (Times 2 _smt1) (Times 3 _smt2)))) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "91; 93; 95",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3148,
        "question": "The sum of three consecutive odd integers is 89 more than twice the largest integer. Find the integers",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Plus 89 (Times 2 _smt2))) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "85",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3149,
        "question": "this two-digit number is less than 100.this number is odd.the sum of the digits in the ones place and the tens place is 13.the number in the ones place is less than the number in tens places.The number in the tens place is 2 less than 10.what is the answer?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-3/2 | -1.5",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3150,
        "question": "Twice the sum of a number and -6 equals -6 times the sum of the number and 4. Let n stand for the number. Solve for n",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-2; -1; 0; 1; 2",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3151,
        "question": "what are the 5 consecutive numbers that their sum equals their product???",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "4; 5; 6",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3152,
        "question": "find three consecutive integers such that the sum of one-half of the smallest and one-third of the largest is one less than the other integer",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus (Times 0.5 (Min (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Div (Times 1 (Max (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) 3)) (Minus _smt1 1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-10",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3153,
        "question": "The sum of half a number and that number's reciprocal is the same as 51 divided by the number. The number is negative. Find the number.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "12 or -12",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3154,
        "question": "The sum of one third of a number and its reciprocal is the same as 49 divided by the number. Find the number",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 _smt0) (Not (Equals _smt0 0)) (Equals 49 (Times _smt0 (Plus (Div (Times 1 _smt0) 3) (Div 1 _smt0)))))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "3588",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3155,
        "question": "What is the sum of the positive multiples of 13 that are less than 300?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 (Sum _x1)) (LessThan _x2 300) (LessThan 0 _x2) (IsInteger _x2) (IsInteger 13) (Equals (Mod _x2 13) 0))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "21; 23 or -23; -21 | -23; -21",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3156,
        "question": "the squares of 2 consecutive odd numbers differ by 88, what are the numbers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Difference (Elements (Pow _smt0 2) (Pow _smt1 2))) 88) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "27",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3157,
        "question": "A certain two-digit number has a value that that is three times the sum of its digits. The units digit is one more than three times the tens digit. Find the number.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-29; -8",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3159,
        "question": "The sum of two numbers is 8 less than the first number. Their difference is 5 less than twice the second number. Find each of the numbers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "14/13 | 1.077",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3161,
        "question": "Twice the difference of 7 times a number and 4 yields the same result as the same number increased by 6. What is the number?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "84",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3163,
        "question": "The tens digit of a two-digit number is twice the units digit.  If the digits are reversed, the new number is 36 less than the original number.  Find the number.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "6; 8",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3164,
        "question": "The product of two consecutive even numbers is 12 more than the square of the smaller number. Form an equation and solve it to find the numbers",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-16; -15; -14",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3165,
        "question": "Find three consecutive numbers such that the sum of one-fourth the first and one-fifth the second is five less than one-seventh the third.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus (Div (Times 1 _smt0) 4) (Div (Times 1 _smt1) 5)) (Minus (Div (Times 1 _smt2) 7) 5)) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "3/2 | 1.5",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3166,
        "question": "What number, when added to the number three or multiplied to the three, gives the same result?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "1.837 or -1.837",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3167,
        "question": "Find the value of T in this equation:   BT^2=F^3/Z?B=2,F=3,Z=4",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "537",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3168,
        "question": "I am a 3-digit numberAll my digits are oddI am less than 600I am greater than 400If you add my digits you get 15My last digit is 7What am I?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "10000",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3169,
        "question": "what is the sum of the first 100 odd numbers",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "250000",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3170,
        "question": "What is the sum of the first 500 odd numbers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "210",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3171,
        "question": "if the average of 20 different positive numbers is 20 then what is the greatest possible number among these 20 numbers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "5; 1",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3172,
        "question": "A+B+C+D=D+E+F+G=G+H+I=17 where each letter represent a distinct integer from 1 to 9. Find out what does letter D and G represent if letter A= 4",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "25",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3173,
        "question": "If 9n^2 - 30n + c is a perfect square for all integers n, what is the value of c?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "3",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3174,
        "question": "What is the least value of k if 3x^2 + 6x + k is never negative?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "81",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3175,
        "question": "Find the value of c that makes  x^2+18x+c  a perfect square trinomial.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-5; -4; -3",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3176,
        "question": "Find three consecutive integers such that -5 times the sum of the first and the third is 24 greater than 4 times the opposite of the second.",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Equals (Plus 24 (Times 4 (Minus 0 _smt1))) (Times (Minus 0 5) (Plus _smt0 _smt2))) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "12 or -12",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3177,
        "question": "Find this quantity: one half of the quantity multiplied by one third of the quantity equals 24.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "93",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3178,
        "question": "The tens digit of a two-digit number is 3 more than twice the units digit. If the digits are reversed, the new number is 54 less than the original number. Find the original number.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "2500",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3179,
        "question": "find the sum of odd numbers from 1 to 99, inclusive?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 (Sum _x1)) (Le 1 _x2) (Le _x2 99) (IsInteger _x2) (IsInteger (Plus 1 _x2)) (IsInteger 2) (Equals (Mod (Plus 1 _x2) 2) 0))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "1",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3180,
        "question": "If the expression x^2 - kx - 12 is equal to zero when x=4, what is the value of k?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 0 (Minus (Minus (Pow 4 2) (Times k 4)) 12)) (Equals ?_x0 k))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "45",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3181,
        "question": "A 3- digit number in which one digit is the average of the other two digits is called an average number.  456 is an average  number because 5 is the average of 4 and 6.  How many three digit average numbers are there?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "160",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3182,
        "question": "what is 8% of 2,000.",
        "semantics": "(Equals (Times 8 2000) (Times 100 ?_x0))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "0.4",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3183,
        "question": "what's 8% of 5.00?",
        "semantics": "(Equals (Times 8 5) (Times 100 ?_x0))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "1/6",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3184,
        "question": "One fourth of one third is the same as one half of what fraction?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "8/12",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3185,
        "question": "The denominator of a fraction exceeds the numerator by 4. When the fraction is reduced to lowest terms it is 2/3. What is the fraction?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "4",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3186,
        "question": "When the number n is multiplied by 4, the result is the same as when 4 is added to n. What is the value of 3n?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "4",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3187,
        "question": "When the number w is multiplied by 4, the result is the same as when 4 is added to w. What is the value of 3w?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "15; 17; 19 or -17; -15; -13",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3188,
        "question": "Four times the sum of three consecutive odd integers is seven hundred sixty-five less than three times the product of the larger two numbers. What are the three integers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "30",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3189,
        "question": "How many whole numbers less than 500 have seven as the sum of their digits?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "60",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3190,
        "question": "x + 20 = y + 80. What is the value of x-y.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus x 20) (Plus y 80)) (Equals ?_x0 (Minus x y)))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "20",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3191,
        "question": "Sum of 2 numbers is 35.3 times the larger number is the same as 4 times the smaller number. find the larger number.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "20% | 20",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3192,
        "question": "if a is 50% larger than c, and b is 25% larger than c, then a is what percent larger than b?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "210",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3193,
        "question": "The numbers a and b are consecutive positive integers, and a < square root of 200 < b.What is the value of the product of ab?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{36; 1} or {324; 289}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3194,
        "question": "which 2 perfect squares get a difference of 35?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "3",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3195,
        "question": "if 4 less than 3 times a certain number is 2 more than the number, what is the number",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals _smt0 ?_x0) (Equals (Plus 2 ?_x0) (Minus (Times 3 _smt0) 4)))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "15",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3196,
        "question": "when twice a number is decreased by 8, the result is the number increased by 7. find the number?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Minus (Times 2 _smt0) 8) (Plus _smt0 7)) (Equals ?_x1 _smt0))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "7/2 | 3.5",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3197,
        "question": "3 less than 5 times a number is 11 more than the number? Find the number.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 _smt0) (Equals (Plus 11 _smt0) (Minus (Times 5 _smt0) 3)))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-5",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3198,
        "question": "If x-y = 5 and x^2 + y ^ 2 = 15 what is the value of xy?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Minus x y) 5) (Equals 15 (Plus (Pow x 2) (Pow y 2))) (Equals ?_x0 (Times x y)))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "20",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3200,
        "question": "Using the equations below, find the value  of F if A= 5A+B=CC+D=EE+A=FB+D+F=30",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "7",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3201,
        "question": "the first three terms of an arithmetic sequence are (12-p), 2p, (4p-5) respectively where p is a constant.Find the value of p",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "47; 49; 51; 53",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3202,
        "question": "there are four consecutive odd integers. the sum of the first and the second numbers is 96. what are the integers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{2; 19; 79} or {2; 31; 67} or {2; 37; 61}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3203,
        "question": "write three prime numbers that add up to 100",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "4",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3204,
        "question": "If the product of -3 and the opposite of a number is decreased by 7, the result is 1 greater than the number.  What is the number?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "3; 10; 17",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3205,
        "question": "In an arithmetic series, the terms of the series are equally spread out. For example, in 1 + 5 + 9 + 13 + 17, consecutive terms are 4 apart. If the first term in an arithmetic series is 3, the last term is 136, and the sum is 1,390, what are the first 3 terms?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "31; 33; 35",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3206,
        "question": "Find three consecutive odd integers such that twice the sum of the second and the third is 43 more than three times the first.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals (Plus 43 (Times 3 _smt0)) (Times 2 (Plus _smt1 _smt2))) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "9/2 | 4.5",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3207,
        "question": "Suppose f is a function that satisfies 1/x f(-x)+ f(1/x) = 2x for all x different from 0. What is the value of f(2)?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "4.236",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3208,
        "question": "The sum of two numbers is 4. The sum of their squares is 18. WHat is the smaller of the two numbers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "4016016",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3209,
        "question": "what is the difference between the sum of the first 2004 positive integers and the sum of the next 2004 positive?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "3/2 | 1.5",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3210,
        "question": "the sum of 2/3 and four times a number is equal to 5/6 subtracted from five times the number. Find the number.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 _smt0) (Equals (Minus (Times 5 _smt0) (Div 5 6)) (Plus (Div 2 3) (Times 4 _smt0))))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "1 or 153",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3211,
        "question": "Solve the following number riddle.a.) I am a positive integer.b.) All my digits are odd.c.) I am equal to the sum of the cubes of my digits.d.) I am less than 300.Who am I?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "20",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3212,
        "question": "If 3x - 1 = 11, what is the value of x^2 + x?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 11 (Minus (Times 3 x) 1)) (Equals ?_x0 (Plus (Pow x 2) x)))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-22251821/1100 | -20228.928",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3213,
        "question": "Find the difference between the product of 26/22 and 3.09 and the sum of 3,507.00, 2.08, 11.50 and 16,712.00",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "20",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3214,
        "question": "What is 5/9 times 36?",
        "semantics": "(Equals (Times 5 36) (Times 9 ?_x0))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "250/3 | 83.333",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3215,
        "question": "what number is 5 sixths of 100?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "1/9 | 0.111",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3216,
        "question": "One of the roots of the equation 2x^2 - x + M = 0 is twice the other root. Find the value of M.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "9/10 | 0.9",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3217,
        "question": "5/6 of a number is 3/4.  What is the number?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Times 4 (Times 5 _smt0)) (Times 6 3)) (Equals ?_x1 _smt0))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "6",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3218,
        "question": "What is the value of x in the following equation?3x - 4(x + 1) + 10 = 0",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus (Minus (Times 3 x) (Times 4 (Plus x 1))) 10) 0) (Equals ?_x0 x))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "200",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3219,
        "question": "A whole number between 100 and 1000 is to be formed so that one of the digits is 6, and all the digits are different. How many numbers are possible.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-35",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3220,
        "question": "If 4x-2y= -10 and 3x-2y=10 what is the value for y?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Minus (Times 4 x) (Times 2 y)) (Minus 0 10)) (Equals 10 (Minus (Times 3 x) (Times 2 y))) (Equals ?_x0 y))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "1/2 | 0.5",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3221,
        "question": "The square of x is equal to 4 times the square of y. If x is 1 more than twice y, what is the value of x?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Pow (Plus 1 (Times 2 y)) 2) (Times 4 (Pow y 2))) (Equals ?_x0 (Plus 1 (Times 2 y))))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "12",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3222,
        "question": "if 2/3 of 3/4 of a number is 24, what is 1/4 of the same number?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Times 2 (Times 3 _smt0)) (Times 3 (Times 4 24))) (Equals (Times 1 _smt0) (Times 4 ?_x2)))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "42735",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3223,
        "question": "Three consecutive odd integers have a sum equal to 105. What is the product for these numbers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "27",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3224,
        "question": "The average of three consecutive multiples of 3 is a.The average of four consecutive multiples of 4 is a+27The average of the smallest and largest of these seven integers is 42.Determine the value of a.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "13 | -65",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3226,
        "question": "Five times a number is equal to another number. Their difference is 52. Find the smaller number.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Difference (Elements _smt0 (Times 5 _smt0))) 52) (Equals ?_x1 (Min (Elements _smt0 (Times 5 _smt0)))))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "0",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3227,
        "question": "If y = 3x + 2 and y = -4 -6x what is the value of y?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Minus (Minus 0 4) (Times 6 x)) (Plus (Times 3 x) 2)) (Equals ?_x0 (Minus (Minus 0 4) (Times 6 x))))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "13/24 | 0.542",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3228,
        "question": "The sum of two numbers is 26 and their product is 48. The sum of their reciprocals is?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus _smt0 _smt1) 26) (Equals (Times _smt0 _smt1) 48) (Equals (Plus (Div 1 _smt0) (Div 1 _smt1)) ?_x1) (Le _smt0 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "48",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3229,
        "question": "how many permutations of digits in the number 12345 will make an even number?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{1; -1; -3}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3230,
        "question": "Find the real number solutions of the equation x^3 + 3x^2 - x - 3 = 0",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "3584",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3233,
        "question": "how many 1/4 ounces are in 56 pounds?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "4",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3234,
        "question": "what is the value for x in the following linear system of equations?x - y = 52x + y = 7",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "0",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3235,
        "question": "What number minus one-half is equal to negative one-half ?",
        "semantics": "(Equals (Minus 0 0.5) (Minus ?_x0 0.5))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-1/12 | -0.0833",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3236,
        "question": "16 over 24 minus 18 over 24?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "52",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3237,
        "question": "The sum of the digits of a two digit number is 7. The tens' digit is 3 more than the ones' digit. What is the number?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus _smt1_d1 _smt1_d0) 7) (Equals (Mod (Div ?_x1 10) 10) (Plus 3 (Mod (Div ?_x1 1) 10))) (Le ?_x1 (Minus (Pow 10 2) 1)) (Le (Pow 10 (Minus 2 1)) ?_x1) (Equals (Plus (Times _smt1_d0 1) (Times _smt1_d1 10)) ?_x1) (Le 0 _smt1_d1) (Le _smt1_d1 9) (IsInteger _smt1_d1) (Le 0 _smt1_d0) (Le _smt1_d0 9) (IsInteger _smt1_d0))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-3",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3238,
        "question": "The quotient of -54 and 9, subtracted from 8 times a number, is -18. What's the number?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 _smt0) (Not (Equals (Times (Minus 8 9) _smt0) 0)) (Equals (Minus 0 54) (Times (Times (Minus 8 9) _smt0) (Minus 0 18))))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "8; 4; 2 or -8; 4; 2 or 8; 4; -2 or -8; 4; -2",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3239,
        "question": "find values of x, y, and z so that each expression x to the second power, y to the 3rd power, and z to the 6th power has a value of 64.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "7; 9; 11",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3240,
        "question": "Find three consecutive odd integers such that triple the middle integer is 5 more than twice the largest integer.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals (Plus 5 (Times 2 (Max (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)))) (Times 3 _smt1)) (IsInteger (Max (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "35",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3241,
        "question": "If xy= 7 and x-y= 5, then x^2y - xy^2 =?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Times x y) 7) (Equals (Minus x y) 5) (Equals (Minus (Times (Pow x 2) y) (Times x (Pow y 2))) ?_x0))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-8; -6",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3242,
        "question": "Tripling the greater of two consecutive even integers gives the same result as subtracting 10 from the lesser even integer. What are the integers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{3; -8} or {-3; 8}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3243,
        "question": "The product of two integers is -24 and the sum of the squares of these 2 integers is 73. What are the integers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Times _smt0 _smt1) (Minus 0 24)) (Equals (Plus (Pow _smt0 2) (Pow _smt1 2)) 73) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "60",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3245,
        "question": "If 30% of 40% of a positive # is equal to 20% of w% of the same #, what is the value of w?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "2",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3246,
        "question": "square root six over square root 7 multiplied by square root 14 over square root 3.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "6",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3247,
        "question": "if 4 is added to the square of a composite integer, the result is 14 less than 9 times that integer. find the integer.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{9; 4} or {11; 6}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3248,
        "question": "Two positive whole numbers differ by 5. When one is added to twenty times the smaller number, the result is the same as the square of the bigger number. Find two pairs of numbers for which this statement is true.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "9000",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3249,
        "question": "How many four-digit numbers can be formed using the digits 0,1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8, and 9 if the first digit cannot be 0? Repeated digits are allowed.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "24",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3250,
        "question": "a two digit number is equal to four times the sum of its digits. If it is increased by 3, the resulting number is equal to three times the sum of its digits. Find the original number.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "2",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3251,
        "question": "the equation is 10x - 19 = 9 - 4x.What's the value of x?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "3",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3252,
        "question": "Twelve less than 2 times a number is equal to 15 minus 7 times the number.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "15; 16 or -18; -17",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3253,
        "question": "the sum of 2 consecutive integers and their product is 271. find the integers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "342",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3254,
        "question": "The sum of the 32 terms in an arithmetic series is 5488 and the first term is 1. Find the last term in the series.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-1/12 | -0.083",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3255,
        "question": "Find the reciprocal of  (-1/2)(8/4)(12)",
        "semantics": "(And (Not (And (Not (Equals 4 0)) (Equals (Times (Times (Minus 0 0.5) 8) 12) (Times 4 0)))) (Equals (Times (Times (Times (Minus 0 0.5) 8) 12) ?_x0) (Times 4 1)))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "1435",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3256,
        "question": "What is the sum of the consecutive integers from 15 to 55 (inclusive)?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "66795",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3257,
        "question": "If every number between 1 and 365 were added together, what would the total be?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "4905",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3258,
        "question": "what is the sum of all 2-digit numbers from 10 to 99?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "1/5 | 0.2",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3259,
        "question": "The sum of two positive numbers is 20. What is the minimum value of the sum of their reciprocals?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "8",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3260,
        "question": "Find the value of k so that the equation will have exactly one rational solution?2x^2+8x+k=0",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "4368",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3261,
        "question": "the difference between two numbers is 2184. if the bigger number is 3 times the smaller number, find the sum of the two numbers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Minus (Times 3 _smt0) _smt0) 2184) (Equals ?_x1 (Plus _smt0 (Times 3 _smt0))))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "17",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3262,
        "question": "I think of a number, double it, add three, multiply the answer by three and then add on twice the number I first thought of. If the final answer is 145 what was the number I first thought of?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "3",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3263,
        "question": "consider the sequence A,B,C,D,E,F,G,H. The sum of any 3 consecutive terms is 14. If B=7 and F=4. what is D?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "17",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3264,
        "question": "if p+q=5 and 2pq=8, what is p^2+q^2?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus p q) 5) (Equals (Times 2 (Times p q)) 8) (Equals ?_x0 (Plus (Pow p 2) (Pow q 2))))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "1431",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3265,
        "question": "Find the sum of the terms in this arithmetic sequence :1,5,9,13...105",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "1089",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3266,
        "question": "Find the sum of 33 terms of an arithmetic progression whose middle term is 33.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-162",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3267,
        "question": "The first 3 terms of a geometric series sum to -189, and the next 3 terms sum to 7. What is the sum of the first 2 terms of the series?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-6",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3268,
        "question": "Seven more than the product of a number and four is negative seventeen. find the number.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus 7 (Times _smt0 4)) (Minus 0 17)) (Equals ?_x1 _smt0))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "4",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3269,
        "question": "The sum of two numbers is 28. Their products is 7.Find the sum of the reciprocals of the numbers!",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "3645",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3270,
        "question": "How many 7-digit telephone numbers are there if the number meets the following conditions?- the first digit is not 5 or 7- the second digit is 7- the fifth digit is 1- the last digit is 3- none of the digits is 6- the leading digit may not be 0 or 1",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-3; -1; 1; 3",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3271,
        "question": "find four consecutive odd integers such that 6 times the sum of the first and the third is 3 more than 5 times the opposite of the fourth.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (IsInteger _smt3) (Equals (Plus 3 (Times 5 (Minus 0 _smt3))) (Times 6 (Plus _smt0 _smt2))) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_3 _smt3))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "66660",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3272,
        "question": "what is the sum of all the four digit positive integers that can be written with the digits 1, 2, 3, and 4 if each digit must be used exactly once in each four digit positive integer.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "1 or -3/4 | 1 or -0.75",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3273,
        "question": "If you subtract a number from four times its square, the result is three? Find the number.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "10000",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3274,
        "question": "The sum of the first 100 positive whole numbers is 5050. what is the sum of the first 100 positive odd whole numbers ?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-10",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3276,
        "question": "find the common difference of an AP whose 1st term is 100 and the sum of whose first six terms is 5 times the sum of the next 6 terms?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "8/5 | 1.6",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3277,
        "question": "If (a+b)/a=6 and (b+c)/c=9 then what is the numerical value of a/c?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "35350",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3278,
        "question": "Find The sum of all integer multiples of 7 from 7 to 700",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "21000",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3279,
        "question": "Searching for the value of a variable in a fraction?15/630,000 = 0.50/b",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "12",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3280,
        "question": "nine times the reciprocal of a  number equals 3 times the  reciprocal of 4?Find the number.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 _smt0) (Not (Equals _smt0 0)) (Equals (Times _smt0 (Times 3 1)) (Times 4 (Times 9 1))))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "5/2 | 2.5",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3281,
        "question": "Two times the reciprocal of a number equals 28 times the reciprocal of 35. Find the number.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 _smt0) (Not (Equals _smt0 0)) (Equals (Times _smt0 (Times 28 1)) (Times 35 (Times 2 1))))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "5/3",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3282,
        "question": "If 2/3 is 1/2 of 4/5 of a certain number, then that number is what?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals _smt0 ?_x1) (Equals (Times 5 2) (Times 3 (Times 0.5 (Times 4 _smt0)))))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{4; 3}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3283,
        "question": "A number is 5 less than the square of the other number. The product of the two numbers is 12. What are the numbers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals _smt0 (Minus (Pow _smt1 2) 5)) (Equals 12 (Times _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "5",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3284,
        "question": "In an arithmetic  sequence, the 7th term minus the 1st term equals 18. The sum of the 1st and 7th term is -2. Find the 6th term.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "275",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3285,
        "question": "if the product of (2+3), (3+4), and (4+5) is equal to the sum of 40 and x then x=?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals x ?_x0) (Equals (Plus 40 x) (Product (Elements (Plus 2 3) (Plus 3 4) (Plus 4 5)))))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{17; 5}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3286,
        "question": "One number is seven more than twice another. If their sum is decreased by nine, the result is thirteen. Find the numbers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 13 (Minus (Plus _smt0 _smt1) 9)) (Equals _smt0 (Plus 7 (Times 2 _smt1))) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "49 or 67 or 85",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3288,
        "question": "the sum of my two digits is 13. I am not divisible by 2. List all the possible numbers I could be.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-3",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3289,
        "question": "what is the sum of the roots of the equation?: 2x^2+6x-7=0?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-216",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3290,
        "question": "What is the sum of the arithmetic sequence 152, 138, 124, ..., if there are 24 terms?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "75; 77",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3291,
        "question": "Find two consecutive odd numbers such that the sum of one-fifth of the smaller and four-sevenths of the larger is equal to fifty-nine.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals (Plus (Div (Times 1 _smt0) 5) (Div (Times 4 _smt1) 7)) (Plus 50 9)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "32",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3292,
        "question": "Find the number of positive integral divisors of 23625.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "18 or -2",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3293,
        "question": "the first three terms of an arithmetic series have a sum of 24 and a product of 312. what is the fourth term?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-1",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3294,
        "question": "The product of two consecutive integers is 2 less than the square of the smaller integer. Find the larger of the two integers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Times _smt0 _smt1) (Minus (Pow _smt0 2) 2)) (Equals ?_x1 (Max (Elements _smt0 _smt1))) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Le _smt0 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "228",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3296,
        "question": "Rhonda added 140 to one third of a number for a result of 216.What is the number?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "36625",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3297,
        "question": "Find the five digit number in which the first two digits are the square of the third digit and the last two digits are the square of the digit that is one less than the third digit. The sum of all the digits is 22.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "62",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3299,
        "question": "What is the number? the sum of the digits is 8.  The product is 12.   The number is between 30 and 90.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "189",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3300,
        "question": "If y= 4(2x-9)+25. what is the value of y when x=25?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "136/27 | 5.037",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3301,
        "question": "If the difference of a number and 5 is tripled, the result is 1/9. Find the number.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "12",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3303,
        "question": "what percent of 50 is 6?",
        "semantics": "(Equals (Times ?_x0 50) (Times 100 6))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "62.5",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3304,
        "question": "What percent of 80 is 50?",
        "semantics": "(Equals (Times ?_x0 80) (Times 100 50))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "56",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3306,
        "question": "The sum of 3 consecutive EVEN integers is 174. What is the first integer?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) 174) (Equals ?_x1 _smt0) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "23",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3307,
        "question": "The sum of three consecutive numbers is 72. What are the smallest of these numbers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) 72) (Equals ?_x1 (Min (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "355",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3308,
        "question": "What is the sum of five consecutive odd integers if the middle integer is 71?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "43",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3309,
        "question": "The sum of the digits of a 2-digit number is 7. If the digits are reversed, the new number is 9 less than the original number. Find the original number.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "5/2 | 2.5",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3310,
        "question": "The numerator of a fraction is 7 more than twice the denominator. The reciprocal of the fraction equals 0.4. Find the fraction.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "2/3",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3311,
        "question": "The denominator of a fraction is 1 more than the numerator. when (5/6) is added to the fraction, the terms of the fraction are reversed. what is the original fraction?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-7/2 | -3.5",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3312,
        "question": "A number plus five, divided by two, added to the quotient of that same number minus one, divided also by two, has a sum of that number minus one, divided by three.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{38; 28}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3313,
        "question": "Find 2 numbers whose difference is 10 and 1/6 of whose sum is 11.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "16",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3314,
        "question": "Take a number, multiply it by 8, subtract 8, divide by 12, and double the quotient. the result is 20. what is the number?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "6; 7; 8",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3315,
        "question": "3 times the first of three consecutive numbers is 4 more than 2 times the second. Find the numbers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Equals (Plus 4 (Times 2 _smt1)) (Times 3 _smt0)) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "ans_no_result",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3316,
        "question": "Five times the smallest of three consecutive integers is 10 more than twice the largest. Find the integers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "8",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3317,
        "question": "If the average of 4 and x is equal to the average of 2, 8, and x, what is the value of x?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Times (Sum (Elements 2 8 x)) 1) (Times 3 (Times (Plus 4 x) 0.5))) (Equals ?_x0 x))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "31",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3318,
        "question": "in  a sequence of 5 integers the third integer is the sum of the previous two. The fourth integer is the sum of the previous three and the fifth integer is the sum of the previous four. If the sum of the five integers is  248, what's the third integer in the sequence.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "5",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3319,
        "question": "If f(x) = 3x^2 - Bx + 4 and f(-1) = 12, what is the value of B?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 12 (Plus (Minus (Times 3 (Pow (Minus 0 1) 2)) (Times b (Minus 0 1))) 4)) (Equals ?_x0 b))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "27",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3320,
        "question": "what two digit number is three times the sum of its digits?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "88; 89; 90",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3322,
        "question": "Find three consecutive integers with a sum of 267.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 267 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "31; 32; 33",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3323,
        "question": "the sum of three consecutive integers is 96. find them.",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Equals 96 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "250; 251; 252",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3324,
        "question": "the sum of 3 consecutive numbers is 753. what are these numbers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Equals 753 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "23; 24; 25",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3325,
        "question": "The sum of three consecutive numbers is 72, find the three numbers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "21; 22; 23; 24",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3326,
        "question": "What are 4 consecutive integers such that the sum of the 2nd and the 4th is 17 less than thrice the 1st?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "54/91 | 0.593",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3327,
        "question": "what is 6/7 of 9/13?",
        "semantics": "(Equals (Times 6 9) (Times 7 (Times 13 ?_x0)))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{-20; -15} or {20; 15}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3328,
        "question": "The number 625 is the sum of the squares of two 2-digit numbers. The difference between the numbers is one third of one of these numbers and one quarter of the other. What are those two numbers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "17",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3329,
        "question": "If x+ 1=3, what is the value of x^4 +1?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus x 1) 3) (Equals ?_x0 (Plus (Pow x 4) 1)))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "7 or -7",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3330,
        "question": "you take the same number and multiply it by itself 6 times, and you get 117,649. what is the original number?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-6",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3331,
        "question": "What is the value of y in the solution for the system of equations?x + y = 10x + 2y = 4",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "4/5 | 0.8",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3332,
        "question": "Fifteen times the square of a non-zero number is equal to 12 times the number. What is the number?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "1475/9 | 163.889",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3333,
        "question": "What percent of 36 is 59?",
        "semantics": "(Equals (Times ?_x0 36) (Times 100 59))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "47184",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3334,
        "question": "I am a 5-digit number.My tens digit is the sum of my hundreds digit and thousands digit.My tens digit is twice my ones digit.My hundreds digit is 1 more than zero.My thousands digit is seven times my hundreds digit.My ten thousands digit is the same as my ones digit.What is the mystery number?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "54; 6",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3336,
        "question": "There are two numbers.The quotient of the numbers is 9.The difference of the numbers is 48.The sum of the numbers is 60.Find the numbers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "40",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3337,
        "question": "the mean of 6 numbers is 34. if five of the numbers are 13,25,36,41,49, what is the 6th number?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "2.5 or -0.4",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3339,
        "question": "a number is 2+1/10 more than its reciprocal. find the number.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "4.9185 | 4.919",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3340,
        "question": "Find the difference between the product of 21.33 and 2.04 and the sum of 1.115, 3.18, 22.0613, and 12.2384.",
        "semantics": "(Equals ?_x0 (Difference (Elements (Times 21.33 2.04) (Sum (Elements 1.115 3.18 22.0613 12.2384)))))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "91",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3341,
        "question": "the sum of two numbers is 20, the difference of the same two numbers is 6. what is the product of the two numbers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus _smt0 _smt1) 20) (Equals (Minus _smt1 _smt0) 6) (Equals ?_x1 (Times _smt0 _smt1)))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "5",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3342,
        "question": "What is the number that is one half of one quarter of one tenth of 400?",
        "semantics": "(Equals (Times 0.5 (Times 1 (Times 1 400))) (Times 4 (Times 10 ?_x0)))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "2.160 or -2.160",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3343,
        "question": "If three times the square of a certain number itself, the result is 14. Find the number?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "30",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3344,
        "question": "which number is the tenth part of a quarter of the fifth part of half 12,000?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "28; 12",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3345,
        "question": "The difference between two numbers is 16. Three times the larger number is seven times the smaller. What are the Numbers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 16 (Minus _smt1 _smt0)) (Equals (Times 7 _smt0) (Times 3 _smt1)) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "7.1",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3346,
        "question": "the difference of two numbers is tripled. the result is decreased by 1. If the lesser of the two numbers is 4, and the result is 8.3. Find the greater number x.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "8",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3347,
        "question": "If (x + 2)^2 equal 9, what is the value of (x + 1)(x + 3)?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 9 (Pow (Plus x 2) 2)) (Equals ?_x0 (Times (Plus x 1) (Plus x 3))))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "13",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3348,
        "question": "half m increased by 7+1/2 is 14. Find m.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus (Times 0.5 m) (Plus 7 0.5)) 14) (Equals ?_x0 m))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "75",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3349,
        "question": "What is the average value of 86, 74, 79, 62, 74?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "432/5 | 86.4",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3350,
        "question": "43 is 11 less than 5/8 times a number p. Find p.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 43 (Minus (Div (Times 5 _smt0) 8) 11)) (Equals ?_x0 _smt0))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "9; 10; 11",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3351,
        "question": "find three consecutive integers, the sum of whose squares is 59 more than three times the square of the smallest.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "571/12 | 47.583",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3352,
        "question": "What is the difference between 126+1/4 and 78+2/3?",
        "semantics": "(Equals ?_x0 (Difference (Elements (Plus 126 (Div 1 4)) (Plus 78 (Div 2 3)))))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{13; 6}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3353,
        "question": "The larger of two numbers is one more than twice the smaller. The sum of the numbers is 20 less than 3 times larger? Find the numbers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Max (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Plus 1 (Times 2 _smt0))) (Equals (Plus _smt0 _smt1) (Minus (Times 3 _smt1) 20)) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-5; -3; -1",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3354,
        "question": "find three consecutive odd integers such that twice the sum of the first and the second is equal to four times the sum of the second and the third.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "48",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3355,
        "question": "The difference between one-half of a number and one-sixth of the number is equal to ten more than one-eighth of that number. Find the number.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 _smt0) (Equals (Difference (Elements (Times 0.5 _smt0) (Div (Times 1 _smt0) 6))) (Plus 10 (Div (Times 1 _smt0) 8))))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "924",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3358,
        "question": "What is the sum of 6 \ufffd\ufffd 103 and 3 \ufffd\ufffd102?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-12",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3359,
        "question": "the product of two-thirds and a number is 4 more than the number. What is the number?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 _smt0) (Equals (Plus 4 _smt0) (Times (Div 2 3) _smt0)))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "0.667 or 1.5 | 2/3 or 3/2",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3360,
        "question": "find a rational number such that the sum of the number and its reciprocal is 2+1/6?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "12",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3361,
        "question": "The mean of six numbers is 5. A seventh number is added and the new mean is 6. Find the seventh number?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "18; 21; 25",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3362,
        "question": "the sum of 3 numbers equal 64. The second number is 3 more than the first. The third number is 11 less than twice the first. Find the numbers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals _smt1 (Plus 3 _smt0)) (Equals 64 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2))) (Equals _smt2 (Minus (Times 2 _smt0) 11)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "17; 19; 21",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3363,
        "question": "The sum of 3 consecutive odd integers is 40 more than the smallest. Find the integers?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Plus 40 _smt0)) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "3",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3364,
        "question": "the eighth power of a number divided by the fifth power of that number is 27. what is the number?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "72",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3365,
        "question": "The tens digit of a certain two-digit number is 1 more than 3 times the units digit. The original number is 9 less than 3 times the number formed by interchanging the digits. Find the original number.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "27",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3366,
        "question": "The sum of the digits of a two digit number is one third of the number. The units digit is 5 more than the tens digit. What is the number?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Mod (Div ?_x0 1) 10) (Plus 5 (Mod (Div ?_x0 10) 10))) (Le ?_x0 (Minus (Pow 10 2) 1)) (Le (Pow 10 (Minus 2 1)) ?_x0) (Equals (Plus (Times _smt1_d0 1) (Times _smt1_d1 10)) ?_x0) (Equals (Times 1 ?_x0) (Times 3 (Plus _smt1_d1 _smt1_d0))) (Le 0 _smt1_d1) (Le _smt1_d1 9) (IsInteger _smt1_d1) (Le 0 _smt1_d0) (Le _smt1_d0 9) (IsInteger _smt1_d0))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-70",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3367,
        "question": "If 3/5 of the number is 40 lesser than the 40 % of the same number, what is the 35% of that number ?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "6 or -6",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3368,
        "question": "what number multiplied by itself 4 times gives you 1296?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "7.899; 1.899 or -1.899; -7.899",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3369,
        "question": "Find two numbers such that 4 times the first number minus 4 times the second number equals 24 and twice the first number times the second number equals 30",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals 24 (Minus (Times 4 _smt0) (Times 4 _smt1))) (Equals 30 (Times (Times 2 _smt0) _smt1)) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "x = 280 | 280",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3371,
        "question": "The average (arithmetic mean) of t, u, v, w, and x is 120. If the average of t, u, v, and w is 80, what is the value of x?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Times (Sum (Elements t u v w x)) 1) (Times 5 120)) (Equals (Times (Sum (Elements t u v w)) 1) (Times 4 80)) (Equals ?_x0 x))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "18",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3372,
        "question": "If 30 is added to 1/3 of a number, the result is double the number.What is the number?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals (Plus 30 (Div (Times 1 _smt0) 3)) (Times 2 _smt0)) (Equals ?_x1 _smt0))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-15; -13; -11",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3373,
        "question": "Find 3 consecutive odd integers such that 4 less than twice the second has the same value as three times the number that is one more than the third.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals (Times 3 (Plus 1 _smt2)) (Minus (Times 2 _smt1) 4)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "15",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3374,
        "question": "a certain number decreased by 4 is equal to 8 increased by the quotient of the same number and 5. what is the number?",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals _smt0 ?_x0) (Equals (Minus _smt0 4) (Plus 8 (Div ?_x0 5))))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{74; 26}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3376,
        "question": "The average of two numbers is 50. One of the numbers is four less than three times as many as the other number. What are these two numbers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "8",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3377,
        "question": "Evaluate the expression (x^2 + y) - x when x = 2, and y = 6.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "62",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3378,
        "question": "What number is 50 more than 108 divided by 9?",
        "semantics": "(Equals ?_x0 (Plus 50 (Div 108 9)))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "(2x + 2) / (x(x + 2))",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3379,
        "question": "find the sum of the reciprocals of two consecutive even integers if the smaller integer is x.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "24; 26",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3380,
        "question": "Two consecutive even numbers are such that their sum is greater than 98 decreased by twice the larger. Find the smallest possible values for the integers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "4",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3381,
        "question": "three more than five times a number is less than 18. Find the largest integer for which this is true.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "29/32",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3382,
        "question": "A denominator is 3 plus the numerator of a fraction. If 4 is added to the denominator and 2 subtracted from the numerator, the resulting fraction is 3/4. Find the original fraction.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "(-4)/(-12)",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3383,
        "question": "A denominator is 3 times the numerator of a fraction. If 4 is added to the denominator and 2 subtracted from the numerator, the resulting fraction is 3/4.  Find the original fraction.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "64",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3384,
        "question": "If the sum of four consecutive even integers is less than 250, what is the greatest possible value for one of these even integers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "1/25 | 0.04",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3385,
        "question": "the sum of the number and its square root is 6/25,then find the number ?",
        "semantics": "(Equals 6 (Times 25 (Plus ?_x0 (Pow ?_x0 0.5))))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "71",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3386,
        "question": "I am less than 80 and greater than 60. The sum of my digit is 8. I am odd. What number am I?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "6;8",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3388,
        "question": "The sum of the reciprocals of two consecutive even integers is 7/24. Find these integers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Equals 7 (Times 24 (Plus (Div 1 _smt0) (Div 1 _smt1)))) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "125; 127; 129",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3389,
        "question": "The sum of three consecutive odd numbers is more than 375. Find the minimum values of these integers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "9/10",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3390,
        "question": "The denominator of a fraction is 1 more than the numerator. If the numerator is decreased by one and the denominator is increased by 2, the value of the fraction becomes 2/3. Find the fraction.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "1/9",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3391,
        "question": "The sum of the numerator and the denominator of a fraction is 10. If the numerator is multiplied by 3 and the denominator by 1/2, the fraction becomes 2/3. Find the fraction?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "3/4",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3392,
        "question": "If the numerator of a certain fraction is increased by 5 and the denominator is decreased by 1, the resulting fraction is 8/3.  However, if the numerator of the original fraction is doubled and the denominator is increased by 7, the resulting fraction is 6/11.  Find the original fraction.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{42;44;46;48;50} or {44;46;48;50;52} or {46;48;50;52;54}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3393,
        "question": "Find all the sets of five consecutive even integers whose sum is between 225 and 250",
        "semantics": "(And (LessThan 225 (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3 _smt4))) (LessThan (Sum (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3 _smt4)) 250) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2 _smt3 _smt4)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (IsInteger _smt3) (IsInteger _smt4) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Le _smt1 _smt2) (Le _smt2 _smt3) (Le _smt3 _smt4) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2) (Equals ?_x0_3 _smt3) (Equals ?_x0_4 _smt4))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "15; 17; 19",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3394,
        "question": "the sum of three consecutive odd integers is less than 54. what is the set of the largest three consecutive odd integers that fits this situation?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "5",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3395,
        "question": "In a set of four consecutive positive integers, the smallest integer is less than half the largest integer. What is the largest integer that could be in the set?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "4; 5; 6; 7  or 5; 6; 7; 8 or 6; 7; 8; 9",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3396,
        "question": "find all sets of four consecutive integers whose sum is between 22 and 30",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "4; 6",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3397,
        "question": "The sum of the reciprocals of 2 consecutive even integers is 5/12. Find the integers.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Equals 5 (Times 12 (Plus (Div 1 _smt0) (Div 1 _smt1)))) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "13; 14",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3398,
        "question": "find two consecutive integers such that the sum of their reciprocals is 27/182",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1)) (Equals 27 (Times 182 (Plus (Div 1 _smt0) (Div 1 _smt1)))) (Le _smt0 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "301",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3399,
        "question": "i am a 3 digit number divisible by 7 but not 2 the sum of my digits is 4",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "2; 4; 6",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3400,
        "question": "Find three consecutive even integers such that the product of the first and the third is 24 less than 9 times the second.",
        "semantics": "(And (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Equals (Minus (Times 9 _smt1) 24) (Times _smt0 _smt2)) (Equals ?_x0_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x0_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x0_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "88; 90",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3401,
        "question": "The sum of two consecutive even integers is at most 180. Find the pair of integers with the greatest sum.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "3; 4; 5",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3402,
        "question": "find three consecutive integers such that the product of -5 and the sum of the first two is 43 less than twice the second.",
        "semantics": "(And (IsInteger _smt0) (IsInteger _smt1) (IsInteger _smt2) (Consecutive (Elements _smt0 _smt1 _smt2)) (Equals (Minus (Times 2 _smt1) 43) (Times (Minus 0 5) (Plus _smt0 _smt1))) (Equals ?_x1_0 _smt0) (Equals ?_x1_1 _smt1) (Equals ?_x1_2 _smt2))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "121",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3403,
        "question": "The difference between an integer and its square root is 110, what is the integer?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "ans_no_result",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3404,
        "question": "Three divided by the difference of one and a number is as much as twice the same number",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "12/48",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3405,
        "question": "The ratio of the numerator to the denominator of a certain fraction is one to four. If three is added to the numerator and subtracted from the denominator, the new fraction reduces to one-third. What is the original fraction?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "16",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3406,
        "question": "If r is the remainder when 80 is divided by 9 and n is the remainder when r is divided by 3, what is the value of rn?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{4; 6} or {3; 6}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3409,
        "question": "The difference between the product and the sum of two different integers is equal to the sum of their GCD (greatest common divisor) and LCM (least common multiple). Find all these pairs of numbers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "4",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3410,
        "question": "twelve divided by the sum of x and 2 equals the quotient of 4 and the difference of x and 2. Find x.",
        "semantics": "(And (Equals ?_x0 x) (Not (Equals (Plus x 2) 0)) (Not (Equals (Difference (Elements x 2)) 0)) (Equals (Times (Plus x 2) 4) (Times (Difference (Elements x 2)) 12)))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{40; 50}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3411,
        "question": "the LCM of two numbers is 200 and their GCF is 10. The sum of the numbers is 90. Find the numbers.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{10; 2}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3412,
        "question": "find two numbers such that their product, their sum, and their difference have the ratio 5:3:2.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "ln2 | 0.693",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3413,
        "question": "Find the value of x which satisfies the equation e^(2x) + e^x - 6 = 0",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "1020",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3414,
        "question": "Take 1 less than the square of the sixth prime number and subtract this from the least common multiple of 44 and 54. What is the result?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "8",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3415,
        "question": "Find the number of terms in the following geometric sequence:-409.6, 102.4, -25.6,..., 0.025",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "4.087",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3416,
        "question": "if 2 raised to the power of X = 17, what's the value of x?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "9",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3417,
        "question": "if 5/n-1/2=3/(6n) what is the value of n",
        "semantics": "(And (Not (Equals (Times 6 n) 0)) (Equals 3 (Times (Times 6 n) (Minus (Div 5 n) 0.5))) (Equals ?_x0 n))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "19",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3418,
        "question": "What number can be added to both the numerator and the denominator of 16/37 to produce a fraction equal to 5/8?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "75",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3419,
        "question": "let x= 3^2x5^3x7^4 and Y=2^3x3x5^2. what is the greatest common factor of x and y?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "{25; 45} or {5; 225}",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3420,
        "question": "The GCF of two numbers is 5 and their LCM is 225. What are the numbers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "3/7",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3421,
        "question": "The numerator of a fraction is 4 less than the denominator. If 17 is added to each, the value of the fraction is 5/6. Find the original fraction.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-5",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3422,
        "question": "In the quadratic equation (k-2)x^2-5x+2k+3 =0, the roots are reciprocals of each other. Find the value of k.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "1",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3423,
        "question": "if x+y=0 and x is not equal to 0 then what is the value of x^2008 divided by y^2008?",
        "semantics": "(And (Not (Equals x 0)) (Equals (Plus x y) 0) (Not (Equals (Pow y 2008) 0)) (Equals (Pow x 2008) (Times (Pow y 2008) ?_x0)))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "14",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3424,
        "question": "what is the geometric mean of the number 4 and 49?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "97",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3425,
        "question": "what is a 2 digit number that when you divide by both 9 and 10 the remainder is 7?  it has to be a positive number.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "32",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3426,
        "question": "8 divided by 1/4 will be equal to which value?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "12/3",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3427,
        "question": "The numerator of a certain fraction is 4 times the denominator. If 6 is added to both the numerator and denominator, the resulting fraction is equivalent to 2. whAt was the original fraction.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "85; 87",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3428,
        "question": "Find two consecutive odd integers such that 4 times the smaller added to 3 times the larger gives a sum of 601.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "11; 9",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3429,
        "question": "The sum of two numbers is 20, and their sum is to their difference as 10 is to 1. What are the numbers?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "21",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3430,
        "question": "if 5^21 x 4^11= 2 x 10^n what is the value of n?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "80",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3431,
        "question": "Find the sum of a geometric sequence whose first term is 54, whose last (nth) term is 2, and whose common ratio is 1/3.",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "7371",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3432,
        "question": "Find the sum of the terms in the geometric series with a_1 = -9, r = -4, and a_n = 9,216?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "-16384",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3433,
        "question": "What is the 7th term of the geometric sequence where a1 = -4 and a5 = -1,024?",
        "semantics": "",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "18/7 | 2.571",
        "dbidOption": "web",
        "id": 3434,
        "question": "Suppose f(x)=4x-2 and g(x)=-2x+1. Find the value of f(5)/g(-3)?",
        "semantics": "(And (Not (Equals (Plus (Minus 0 (Times 2 (Minus 0 3))) 1) 0)) (Equals (Minus (Times 4 5) 2) (Times (Plus (Minus 0 (Times 2 (Minus 0 3))) 1) ?_x0)))",
        "tags": [
            "sigmadolphin-test",
            "algebra",
            "informal",
            "closed"
        ]
    }
]
